<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.48 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.519 0.378</pos>
			<maxSize>0.27</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.239 0.378" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1997</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Abuse</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>Abuse is a port of the classic dark 2D side-scrolling platform game originally developed by Crack dot Com and released in 1995 for MS-DOS. A Linux version was also made available at a later date. It had a few limitations the most restrictive of which was that it only ran on an 8-bit display, and only in a window.

This version of Abuse will run at any color depth and supports fullscreen mode, as well as many other new features. It features beautiful lighting, realistic animation and nasty alien-like creatures to destroy.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Abuse jest portem klasycznej mrocznej gry platformowej 2D z widokiem z boku, opracowanej pierwotnie przez Crack dot Com i wydanej w 1995 roku dla systemu MS-DOS. W późniejszym czasie udostępniono również wersję dla systemu Linux. Miała ona kilka ograniczeń, z których najbardziej restrykcyjnym było to, że działała tylko na 8-bitowym wyświetlaczu i tylko w oknie.

Ta wersja gry Abuse działa w dowolnej głębi kolorów i obsługuje tryb pełnoekranowy, a także wiele innych nowych funkcji. Zawiera piękne oświetlenie, realistyczną animację i paskudne, podobne do kosmitów stwory do zniszczenia.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Abuse — порт классического мрачного платформа, изначально разработанной Crack dot Com и выпущенной в 1995 году для MS-DOS. Версия для Linux стала доступна позже. У неё было несколько ограничений, наиболее строгим из которых было то, что она работала только на 8-битном дисплее и только в окне.

Эта версия Abuse будет работать с любой глубиной цвета и поддерживает полноэкранный режим, а также множество других новых функции. В нём красивое освещение, реалистичная анимация и инопланетные существа, которых нужно уничтожить.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Abuse est un portage du jeu classique de plateforme à défilement latéral en 2D développé à l'origine par Crack dot Com et sorti en 1995 pour MS-DOS. Une version Linux a également été mise à disposition ultérieurement. Il comportait quelques limitations, dont la plus contraignante était qu'il ne fonctionnait que sur un écran 8 bits, et uniquement dans une fenêtre.

Cette version d'Abuse fonctionne avec n'importe quelle profondeur de couleur et prend en charge le mode plein écran, ainsi que de nombreuses autres nouvelles fonctionnalités. Le jeu offre de superbes éclairages, des animations réalistes et de méchantes créatures extraterrestres à détruire.</text>
			<text lang="it">Abuse è una versione del classico gioco di piattaforme a scorrimento laterale in 2D sviluppato originariamente da Crack dot Com e pubblicato nel 1995 per MS-DOS. In seguito è stata resa disponibile anche una versione per Linux. Aveva alcune limitazioni, la più restrittiva delle quali era che funzionava solo su un display a 8 bit e solo in una finestra.

Questa versione di Abuse funziona con qualsiasi profondità di colore e supporta la modalità a schermo intero, oltre a molte altre nuove caratteristiche. È dotato di una ottima illuminazione, di animazioni realistiche e di creature aliene da distruggere.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
