<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.43</pos>
			<maxSize>0.25</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.43" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.43</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.43" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1992</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Entex</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Adventure Vision</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Entex Adventure Vision or Adventure Vision for short is a second generation portable video game console manufactured by Entex in 1982.
Games are controlled by a single joystick, and a set of four buttons, the buttons are located to the left and right of the joystick to allow left and right handed people to play.
The console does not use an LCD screen or external monitors, LEDs arranged in forty rows are used to display the image, giving a resolution of 153 x 40 pixels, another console that uses similar technology is Virtual Boy.

The technology used in the Entex Adventure Vision, required a large amount of power, hence it needed, up to four D batteries. An A/C adapter could also be used to power the console.
On top of the console, there are special shelves where cartridges can be stored.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Entex Adventure Vision lub skrótowo Adventure Vision – przenośna konsola gier wideo drugiej generacji wyprodukowana przez firmę Entex w 1982 roku.
Gry kontrolowane są za pomocą pojedynczego joysticka, i zestawu czterech przycisków, przyciski znajdują się z lewej i prawej strony od joysticka, aby umożliwić grę osobom lewo i praworęcznym.
Konsola nie korzysta, z ekranu LCD lub zewnętrznych monitorów, do wyświetlania obrazu służą diody LED ustawione w czterdziestu rzędach, dając rozdzielczość 153 x 40 pikseli, kolejną konsolą, która używa podobnej technologii jest Virtual Boy.
Technologia wykorzystana w Entex Adventure Vision, wymagała dużej ilości energii, stąd też potrzebowała, aż czterech baterii D. Do zasilania konsoli można było użyć także zasilacza A/C.
Na górze konsoli, znajdują się specjalne półki, w których można składować kartridże.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Самодостаточная (с собственным экраном) игровая консоль с играми на картриджах, выпущенная компанией Entex Industries в 1982 году. Стала второй игровой системой компании, после Entex select-a-game, выпущенной в 1981 году.

Консоль не имела коммерческого успеха и была снята с производства в 1983 году. Было выпущено около 50 000 экземпляров и всего четыре игры. Несмотря на это, благодаря ряду использованных в консоли необычных решений и её редкости консоль сохраняет некоторую известность среди любителей и коллекционеров старых игровых систем. В настоящее время консоль поддерживается многосистемным эмулятором MAME. Также была создана FPGA-реплика системы.

Технические характеристики:
- Процессор: микроконтроллер Intel 8048 на частоте 733 кГц
- Звук: National Semiconductor COP411L на частоте 52.6 кГц
- ОЗУ: 64 байт в составе 8048 и 1 КБ на плате
- ПЗУ: 1 КБ в составе 8048, 512 байт в составе COP411L и 4 КБ в картридже
- Управление: джойстик и четыре кнопки, продублированные по сторонам от джойстика
- Графика: монохромный экран с разрешением 150×40 пикселей</text>
			<text lang="es">Entex Adventure Vision o Adventure Vision para abreviar es una videoconsola portátil de segunda generación fabricada por Entex en 1982.
Los juegos se controlan mediante un único joystick y un conjunto de cuatro botones, situados a izquierda y derecha del joystick para que puedan jugar tanto diestros como zurdos.
La consola no utiliza una pantalla LCD ni monitores externos, se utilizan LED dispuestos en cuarenta filas para mostrar la imagen, lo que da una resolución de 153 x 40 píxeles, otra consola que utiliza una tecnología similar es Virtual Boy.

La tecnología utilizada en la Entex Adventure Vision, requería una gran cantidad de energía, por lo que necesitaba, hasta cuatro pilas D. También se puede utilizar un adaptador de corriente alterna para alimentar la consola.
En la parte superior de la consola, hay estantes especiales donde se pueden guardar los cartuchos.</text>
			<text lang="de">Entex Adventure Vision oder kurz Adventure Vision ist eine tragbare Videospielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die 1982 von Entex hergestellt wurde.
Die Spiele werden mit einem einzigen Joystick und vier Tasten gesteuert. Die Tasten befinden sich links und rechts vom Joystick, damit Links- und Rechtshänder spielen können.
Die Konsole verwendet keinen LCD-Bildschirm oder externe Monitore, sondern in vierzig Reihen angeordnete LEDs, die eine Auflösung von 153 x 40 Pixeln haben. Eine andere Konsole, die eine ähnliche Technologie verwendet, ist der Virtual Boy.

Die Technologie, die im Entex Adventure Vision zum Einsatz kam, benötigte eine große Menge an Strom, so dass bis zu vier D-Batterien benötigt wurden. Die Konsole kann auch über einen Wechselstromadapter mit Strom versorgt werden.
Auf der Oberseite der Konsole gibt es spezielle Fächer, in denen Kassetten aufbewahrt werden können.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Entex Adventure Vision ou Adventure Vision en abrégé est une console de jeux vidéo portable de deuxième génération fabriquée par Entex en 1982.
Les jeux sont contrôlés par un seul joystick et un ensemble de quatre boutons. Les boutons sont situés à gauche et à droite du joystick pour permettre aux gauchers et aux droitiers de jouer.
La console n'utilise pas d'écran LCD ou de moniteurs externes, des LED disposées en quarante rangées sont utilisées pour afficher l'image, ce qui donne une résolution de 153 x 40 pixels. Une autre console qui utilise une technologie similaire est le Virtual Boy.

La technologie utilisée dans l'Entex Adventure Vision nécessitait une grande quantité d'énergie, et donc jusqu'à quatre piles D. Un adaptateur secteur pouvait également être utilisé. Un adaptateur secteur peut également être utilisé pour alimenter la console.
Sur le dessus de la console, il y a des étagères spéciales où les cartouches peuvent être stockées.</text>
			<text lang="it">Entex Adventure Vision o Adventure Vision in breve è una console portatile per videogiochi di seconda generazione prodotta da Entex nel 1982.
I giochi sono controllati da un singolo joystick e da una serie di quattro pulsanti, situati a sinistra e a destra del joystick, per consentire il gioco a mancini e destrorsi.
La console non utilizza uno schermo LCD o monitor esterni, bensì LED disposti su quaranta file per visualizzare l'immagine, con una risoluzione di 153 x 40 pixel; un'altra console che utilizza una tecnologia simile è il Virtual Boy.

La tecnologia utilizzata nell'Entex Adventure Vision richiedeva una grande quantità di energia, per cui erano necessarie fino a quattro batterie D. Per alimentare la console si poteva usare anche un adattatore A/C.
Sulla parte superiore della console sono presenti speciali ripiani in cui è possibile riporre le cartucce.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
