<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.51 0.368</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.23 0.368" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1985</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Commodore</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Amiga</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Amiga is a family of personal computers introduced by Commodore in 1985. The original model was one of a number of 16/32- and 32-bit computers that featured 256 KB or more of RAM, mouse-based GUIs, and significantly improved graphics and audio over 8-bit systems. This wave included the Atari ST—released the same year—Apple's Macintosh, and later the Apple IIGS. Based on the Motorola 68000 microprocessor, the Amiga differed from its contemporaries through the inclusion of custom hardware to accelerate graphics and sound, including sprites and a blitter, and a pre-emptive multitasking operating system called AmigaOS.

The Amiga 1000 was released in July 1985, but a series of production problems kept it from becoming widely available until early 1986. The best selling model, the Amiga 500, introduced in 1987 (along with the more expandable / professional oriented Amiga 2000) became one of the leading home computers of the late 1980s and early 1990s with four to six million sold. The A3000 was introduced in 1990, followed by the A500+, and the A600 in March 1992. Finally, the A1200 and the A4000 were released in late 1992. The platform became particularly popular for gaming and programming demos. It also found a prominent role in the desktop video, video production, and show control business, leading to video editing systems such as the Video Toaster. The Amiga's native ability to simultaneously play back multiple digital sound samples made it a popular platform for early tracker music software. The relatively powerful processor and ability to access several megabytes of memory enabled the development of 3D rendering packages, including LightWave 3D, Imagine, Aladdin4D, TurboSilver and Traces, a predecessor to Blender.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Amiga (hiszp. amiga – przyjaciółka) – marka komputerów produkowanych od 1985 r. między innymi przez firmę Commodore, popularna w XX wieku. Po bankructwie Commodore marka została przejęta przez firmę Escom, a następnie przez Gateway. W końcu wyłoniła się samodzielna firma Amiga INC, która po bankructwie sprzedała wszelkie prawa firmie KMOS. Z kolei KMOS zmienił nazwę na Amiga Inc.
Systemem operacyjnym Amigi jest AmigaOS z interfejsem Workbench. W momencie wydania AmigaOS był jednym z pierwszych systemów wielozadaniowych na komputery osobiste, znacznie przewyższającym pod tym względem systemy operacyjne produkowane w tamtych latach, na przykład Windows produkowany przez Microsoft.

Przez lata system Amigi stale ewoluował. Najbardziej znaczące zmiany nastąpiły przy wydaniu wersji 3.x, która w wersji 3.9 była ostatnią obsługującą procesory linii 68k. Wersja 4 systemu została przepisana całkowicie pod procesory PowerPC i jest obecnie nadal rozwijana przez firmę Hyperion Entertainment. Najnowsza wersja AmigaOS oznaczona jest numerem 4.1 i pojawiło się do niej uaktualnienie Update 1.

Istnieją również bazujące na AmigaOS systemy rozwijane niezależnie. Zalicza się do nich AROS Research Operating System (AROS) oraz MorphOS. Dla komputerów Amiga powstały również dystrybucje Linuksa oraz NetBSD.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L’Amiga est une famille d’ordinateurs personnels commercialisée par Commodore International entre 1985 et 1994. Dans les années 1990, il est très populaire sur la scène démo, parmi les amateurs de jeux vidéo et dans l'industrie de la vidéo. Dans les années 1980, l'Amiga offrait en standard un affichage plus coloré et plus animé, un meilleur son et un système d'exploitation (multitâche avec interface graphique) plus avancé que la plupart de ses concurrents.

En neuf ans de commercialisation, une dizaine de modèles sont proposés au public et aux professionnels. La version la plus célèbre reste l'Amiga 500, sorti en 1987, vendu à plus d'un million d'exemplaires en Allemagne. Commodore est placé en faillite en 1994, signant la fin de leur production.

Les logiciels n'étant pas compatibles avec ceux de ses concurrents, l'Amiga devait disposer de ses propres programmes de jeu vidéo, traitement de texte, de musique assistée par ordinateur, de dessin, etc. la machine de Commodore est restée longtemps une référence dans la scène démo, parvenant encore à surpasser des démos PC à l’Assembly 2006.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Семейство домашних персональных компьютеров и операционных систем к ним, разработанные Amiga Corporation.

Разработка компьютера началась в 1982 году, в городе Лос-Гатос (Калифорния, США). Кроме 7 миллионов долларов, которые было решено потратить на самофинансирование, у разработчиков имелся значительный опыт в конструировании как аппаратуры, так и программного обеспечения: один из них — Джей Майнер — был разработчиком специализированных микросхем для домашних компьютеров, другой — Роберт Дж. Микал — был известным программистом компании WMS Industries; Дэйв Морс и Карл Сэсенрес также не были новичками. Целью стало создание компьютера, далеко превосходившего бы любые существовавшие на тот момент времени компьютерные системы, предназначенные, в первую очередь, для домашнего использования. Первоначально проект назывался Хай-Торо (Hi-Toro), затем было решено сменить название на более лаконичное и привлекательное — Amiga (с исп.«подружка»). Разработка происходила в обстановке строжайшей секретности и прикрывалась параллельной разработкой манипулятора «доска для серфинга» с обратной связью.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>