<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.36</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.45 0.49</origin>
			<pos>0.4815 0.402</pos>
			<maxSize>0.215</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2015 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.36</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.45 0.49</origin>
			<pos>0.4815 0.402</pos>
			<maxSize>0.215</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2015 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1978</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>APF Electronics</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>M-1000</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The APF Microcomputer System is a second generation 8-bit cartridge-based home video game console released in October 1978 by APF Electronics Inc. with six cartridges. The console is often referred to M-1000 or MP-1000, which are the two model numbers of the console. The APF-MP1000 comes built-in with the game Rocket Patrol. The APF-MP1000 is a part of the APF Imagination Machine.

It is the successor to the APF TV Fun line of first generation consoles.</text>
			<text lang="pl">APF Microcomputer System to 8-bitowa domowa konsola do gier wideo drugiej generacji, wydana w październiku 1978 roku przez APF Electronics Inc. z sześcioma kartridżami. Konsola jest często określana jako M-1000 lub MP-1000, które są dwoma numerami modelu konsoli. Do konsoli APF-MP1000 dołączona jest gra Rocket Patrol. APF-MP1000 jest częścią APF Imagination Machine.

Jest następcą linii konsol APF TV Fun pierwszej generacji.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка второго поколения, представляет собой 8-битную домашнюю игровую приставку.

Является преемником линейки консолей APF TV Fun, относящихся к первому поколению. Выпущена в октябре 1978 компанией APF Electronics Inc. с шестью игровыми картриджами. Устройство упоминается как M-1000 или MP-1000, поскольку это номера модели консоли.</text>
			<text lang="es">El APF Microcomputer System es una videoconsola doméstica de 8 bits basada en cartuchos de segunda generación lanzada en octubre de 1978 por APF Electronics Inc. con seis cartuchos. A menudo se hace referencia a la consola como M-1000 o MP-1000, que son los dos números de modelo de la consola. La APF-MP1000 viene incorporada con el juego Rocket Patrol. La APF-MP1000 forma parte de la APF Imagination Machine.

Es la sucesora de la línea APF TV Fun de consolas de primera generación.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das APF Microcomputer System ist eine 8-Bit-Cartridge-basierte Heimvideospielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die im Oktober 1978 von APF Electronics Inc. mit sechs Cartridges veröffentlicht wurde. Die Konsole wird oft als M-1000 oder MP-1000 bezeichnet, was die beiden Modellnummern der Konsole sind. Die APF-MP1000 wird mit dem Spiel Rocket Patrol ausgeliefert. Die APF-MP1000 ist ein Teil der APF Imagination Machine.

Sie ist der Nachfolger der APF-TV-Fun-Reihe der ersten Konsolengeneration.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'APF Microcomputer System est une console de jeu vidéo de salon de deuxième génération à cartouche 8 bits lancée en octobre 1978 par APF Electronics Inc. avec six cartouches. La console est souvent appelée M-1000 ou MP-1000, qui sont les deux numéros de modèle de la console. L'APF-MP1000 est livrée avec le jeu Rocket Patrol. L'APF-MP1000 fait partie de l'APF Imagination Machine.

Elle succède à la ligne de consoles de première génération APF TV Fun.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'APF Microcomputer System è una console per videogiochi domestici a 8 bit di seconda generazione, rilasciata nell'ottobre 1978 da APF Electronics Inc. con sei cartucce. La console viene spesso indicata come M-1000 o MP-1000, che sono i due numeri di modello della console. L'APF-MP1000 veniva fornito con il gioco Rocket Patrol. L'APF-MP1000 fa parte della APF Imagination Machine.

È il successore della linea di console APF TV Fun di prima generazione.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O sistema de microcomputador APF é um console de videogame doméstico de 8 bits de segunda geração, lançado em outubro de 1978 pela APF Electronics Inc. com seis cartuchos. O console é frequentemente chamado de M-1000 ou MP-1000, que são os dois números do modelo do console. O console APF-MP1000 inclui o jogo Rocket Patrol. O APF-MP1000 faz parte do APF Imagination Machine.

É o sucessor da linha de consoles APF TV Fun de primeira geração.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
