<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.285</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.425</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.363</pos>
			<maxSize>0.232</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.363" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.285</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.425</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.363</pos>
			<maxSize>0.212</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.363" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1988</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Zavod BRA</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Apogee BK-01</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Apogee BK-01, also known as Apogey BK-01, is a Soviet 8-bit personal computer that was built on the Radio 86RK basis and released in 1988. It features a KR580VM80A microprocessor with a clock speed of 1.78 MHz, 64 kB of memory (including 56.25 kB user-available RAM), and a text mode video display. The later version, Apogee BK-01C, introduced color support.

This computer was primarily used for educational purposes and basic computing tasks, and it supported a variety of software, including games and applications for advanced mathematics and statistics.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Apogee BK-01, também conhecido como Apogey BK-01, é um computador pessoal soviético de 8 bits que foi construído com base no Radio 86RK e lançado em 1988. Tem um microprocessador KR580VM80A com uma velocidade de relógio de 1,78 MHz, 64 kB de memória (incluindo 56,25 kB de RAM disponível para o utilizador) e um ecrã de vídeo em modo de texto. A versão posterior, Apogee BK-01C, introduziu o suporte de cor.

Este computador foi usado principalmente para fins educacionais e tarefas básicas de computação, e suportava uma variedade de software, incluindo jogos e aplicações para matemática avançada e estatística.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'Apogee BK-01, noto anche come Apogey BK-01, è un personal computer sovietico a 8 bit costruito sulla base del Radio 86RK e rilasciato nel 1988. È dotato di un microprocessore KR580VM80A con una velocità di clock di 1,78 MHz, 64 kB di memoria (compresi 56,25 kB di RAM disponibile per l'utente) e un display video in modalità testo. La versione successiva, Apogee BK-01C, ha introdotto il supporto del colore.

Questo computer veniva utilizzato principalmente per scopi didattici e per attività di calcolo di base e supportava una serie di software, tra cui giochi e applicazioni per la matematica avanzata e la statistica.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Apogee BK-01, également connu sous le nom d'Apogey BK-01, est un ordinateur personnel soviétique de 8 bits construit sur la base du Radio 86RK et commercialisé en 1988. Il est équipé d'un microprocesseur KR580VM80A cadencé à 1,78 MHz, d'une mémoire de 64 Ko (dont 56,25 Ko de RAM disponible pour l'utilisateur) et d'un écran vidéo en mode texte. La version ultérieure, Apogee BK-01C, a introduit la prise en charge de la couleur.

Cet ordinateur était principalement utilisé à des fins éducatives et pour des tâches informatiques de base, et il prenait en charge une variété de logiciels, y compris des jeux et des applications pour les mathématiques avancées et les statistiques.</text>
			<text lang="de">er Apogee BK-01, auch bekannt als Apogey BK-01, ist ein sowjetischer 8-Bit-Personalcomputer, der auf der Basis des Radio 86RK gebaut und 1988 herausgebracht wurde. Er verfügt über einen KR580VM80A-Mikroprozessor mit einer Taktfrequenz von 1,78 MHz, 64 kB Speicher (einschließlich 56,25 kB benutzerverfügbarem RAM) und eine Videoanzeige im Textmodus. Die spätere Version, Apogee BK-01C, unterstützt nun auch Farbe.

Dieser Computer wurde in erster Linie für Bildungszwecke und grundlegende Rechenaufgaben verwendet und unterstützte eine Vielzahl von Software, darunter Spiele und Anwendungen für höhere Mathematik und Statistik.</text>
			<text lang="es">l Apogee BK-01, también conocido como Apogey BK-01, es un ordenador personal soviético de 8 bits que se construyó sobre la base del Radio 86RK y salió a la venta en 1988. Incorpora un microprocesador KR580VM80A con una velocidad de reloj de 1,78 MHz, 64 kB de memoria (incluyendo 56,25 kB de RAM disponible para el usuario) y una pantalla de vídeo en modo texto. La versión posterior, Apogee BK-01C, introdujo soporte de color.

Este ordenador se utilizaba principalmente para fines educativos y tareas informáticas básicas, y admitía una gran variedad de software, incluidos juegos y aplicaciones para matemáticas avanzadas y estadística.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Апогей БК-01, также известный как Апогей БК-01 - советский 8-битный персональный компьютер, созданный на базе Радио-86РК и выпущенный в 1988 году. Имеет микропроцессор КР580ВМ80А с тактовой частотой 1,78 МГц, 64 кб памяти (из них 56,25 кб - доступная пользователю) и видеодисплей с текстовым режимом. В более поздней версии, Apogee BK-01C, появилась поддержка цвета.

Этот компьютер использовался в основном в образовательных целях и для решения базовых вычислительных задач. Он поддерживал разнообразное программное обеспечение, включая игры и приложения для углубленного изучения математики и статистики.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Apogee BK-01, znany również jako Apogey BK-01, to radziecki 8-bitowy komputer osobisty zbudowany na bazie Radia 86RK i wydany w 1988 roku. Wyposażono go w mikroprocesor KR580VM80A o częstotliwości taktowania 1,78 MHz, 64 kB pamięci (w tym 56,25 kB pamięci RAM dostępnej dla użytkownika) oraz wyświetlacz wideo z trybem tekstowym. Późniejsza wersja, Apogee BK-01C, wprowadziła obsługę kolorów.

Komputer ten był używany głównie do celów edukacyjnych i podstawowych zadań obliczeniowych, a także obsługiwał różnorodne oprogramowanie, w tym gry i aplikacje do zaawansowanej matematyki i statystyki.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
