<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.49</pos>
			<maxSize>0.475</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.49" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>2007</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Apple</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>iOS</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>iOS (formerly iPhone OS or iPhone Operating System) is a mobile operating system created and developed by Apple Inc. exclusively for its hardware. It is the operating system that powers many of the company's mobile devices, including the iPhone and iPod Touch; the term also included the versions running on iPads until iPadOS was introduced in 2019. It is the world's second-most widely installed mobile operating system, after Android. It is the basis for three other operating systems made by Apple: iPadOS, tvOS, and watchOS. It is proprietary software, although some parts of it are open source under the Apple Public Source License and other licenses.</text>
			<text lang="pl">iOS (dawniej iPhone OS lub iPhone Operating System) to mobilny system operacyjny stworzony i rozwijany przez firmę Apple Inc. wyłącznie dla jej sprzętu. Jest to system operacyjny, który obsługuje wiele urządzeń mobilnych firmy, w tym iPhone'a i iPoda Touch; termin ten obejmował również wersje działające na iPadach do czasu wprowadzenia systemu iPadOS w 2019 roku. Jest to drugi, po Androidzie, najczęściej instalowany mobilny system operacyjny na świecie. Stanowi podstawę dla trzech innych systemów operacyjnych firmy Apple: iPadOS, tvOS i watchOS. Jest to oprogramowanie prawnie zastrzeżone, choć niektóre jego części są udostępniane na zasadach licencji Apple Public Source License i innych licencji open source.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Мобильная операционная система для смартфонов, электронных планшетов, носимых проигрывателей, разрабатываемая и выпускаемая американской компанией Apple. Выпущена в 2007 году; первоначально — для iPhone и iPod touch, позже — для таких устройств, как iPad. В 2014 году появилась поддержка автомобильных мультимедийных систем Apple CarPlay. В отличие от Android (Google), выпускается только для устройств, производимых фирмой Apple.

В iOS используется ядро XNU, основанное на микроядре Mach и содержащее программный код, разработанный компанией Apple, а также код из ОС NeXTSTEP и FreeBSD. Ядро iOS почти идентично ядру настольной операционной системы Apple macOS (ранее называвшейся OS X). Начиная с самой первой версии iOS работает только на планшетных компьютерах и смартфонах с процессорами архитектуры ARM.</text>
			<text lang="it">iOS (precedentemente iPhone OS o iPhone Operating System) è un sistema operativo mobile creato e sviluppato da Apple Inc. esclusivamente per il suo hardware. È il sistema operativo che alimenta molti dei dispositivi mobili dell'azienda, tra cui l'iPhone e l'iPod Touch; il termine includeva anche le versioni in esecuzione sugli iPad fino all'introduzione di iPadOS nel 2019. È il secondo sistema operativo mobile più installato al mondo, dopo Android. È la base di altri tre sistemi operativi di Apple: iPadOS, tvOS e watchOS. È un software proprietario, anche se alcune sue parti sono open source sotto la Apple Public Source License e altre licenze.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
