<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.32</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.355</pos>
			<maxSize>0.25</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.355" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.32</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.355</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.355" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1986</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Apple</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Apple IIGS</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Apple IIGS (styled as IIgs), the fifth and most powerful of the Apple II family, is a 16-bit personal computer produced by Apple Computer. While featuring the Macintosh look and feel, and resolution and color similar to the Amiga and Atari ST, it remains compatible with earlier Apple II models. The "GS" in the name stands for "Graphics and Sound," referring to its enhanced multimedia hardware, especially its state-of-the-art audio.

The microcomputer is a radical departure from any previous Apple II, with a 16-bit 65C816 microprocessor, direct access to megabytes of random-access memory (RAM), and mouse. It is the first computer from Apple with a color graphical user interface (color was introduced on the Macintosh II six months later) and Apple Desktop Bus interface for keyboards, mice, and other input devices. It is the first personal computer with a wavetable synthesis chip, using technology from Ensoniq.

The IIGS set forth a promising future and evolutionary advancement of the Apple II line, but Apple increasingly focused on the Macintosh platform. Apple ceased IIGS production in December 1992.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Apple IIGS to model 16-bitowego komputera produkowanego w drugiej połowie lat osiemdziesiątych przez firmę Apple. Model ten był zgodny z rodziną komputerów Apple II.

Dane techniczne
- procesor: W65C816
- przestrzeń adresowa: 16 MB (256 stron po 64 kB)
- tryb pracy procesora zgodny z procesorem 65C02A stosowanym we wcześniejszych modelach, m.in. Apple IIc
- RAM: 256 kB (z możliwością rozbudowy do 8MB)
- ROM: 128 kB (z możliwością rozbudowy do 1 MB): zawierał procedury systemowe, przerwań, obsługi urządzeń, transmisji danych sieci - AppleTalk, interpreter Applesoft Basic
- stacje dyskietek dołączane zewnętrznie:
    2x3,5” 800 kB
    2x5,25” 140 kB (zapewniające możliwość przenoszenia oprogramowania z wcześniejszych modeli serii Apple II)
- złącze RS 232
- tryby grafiki zgodne z Apple IIc
- dodatkowe tryby graficzne
    200x320 punktów 16 kolorów z palety 4096 kolorów
    200x690 punktów 9 kolorów
    200x640 w 16 kolorach z pewnymi ograniczeniami
- układ dźwiękowy DOC firmy Ensoniq
- klawiatura QWERTY z wydzieloną klawiaturą numeryczną</text>
			<text lang="ru">В 1986 году семейство Apple II пополнилось радикально новой моделью: — Apple IIGS. 16-разрядный микропроцессор 65C816 на частоте 2,8 МГц с 24-разрядной адресацией позволял адресовать 8 МБ памяти без переключений банков памяти, как это было на старых моделях. Два совершенно новых графических режима с палитрой в 4096 цветов; хотя лишь 16 цветов из общей палитры в 800 (в разрешении 640 × 200) или из палитры в 3200 (в разрешении 320 × 200) могли использоваться одновременно в одной строке. При этом уникальной особенностью Apple IIGS была возможность задавать своё разрешение (640 или 320 точек) для каждой строки экрана.

Apple IIGS стоит в стороне от остальных моделей семейства Apple II, но и выводит эту платформу к следующему поколению компьютеров, сохраняя при этом почти полную обратную совместимость со всем семейством. Секрет этой совместимости — в специальной микросхеме Mega II, которая содержит всю функциональность Apple IIe, что, совместно с режимом эмуляции 65C02 в микропроцессоре 65C816 обеспечивало полную совместимость для существующего программного обеспечения.

В отличие от остальных компьютеров семейства Apple II, в конструкции Apple IIGS использовалась отдельная от системного блока клавиатура, подключаемая по интерфейсу ADB (совместимая также с компьютерами Macintosh того времени).</text>
			<text lang="es">El Apple IIGS (conocido como IIgs), el quinto y más potente de la familia Apple II, es un ordenador personal de 16 bits fabricado por Apple Computer. Aunque presenta el aspecto y la sensación de Macintosh, y una resolución y color similares a los de Amiga y Atari ST, sigue siendo compatible con los modelos anteriores de Apple II. Las siglas "GS" significan "Graphics and Sound" (gráficos y sonido), en referencia a su hardware multimedia mejorado, especialmente su audio de última generación.

El microordenador supone un cambio radical respecto a cualquier Apple II anterior, con un microprocesador 65C816 de 16 bits, acceso directo a megabytes de memoria de acceso aleatorio (RAM) y ratón. Es el primer ordenador de Apple con interfaz gráfica de usuario en color (el color se introdujo en el Macintosh II seis meses después) e interfaz Apple Desktop Bus para teclados, ratones y otros dispositivos de entrada. Es el primer ordenador personal con un chip de síntesis de tabla de ondas, que utiliza tecnología de Ensoniq.

El IIGS auguraba un futuro prometedor y un avance evolutivo de la línea Apple II, pero Apple se centró cada vez más en la plataforma Macintosh. Apple cesó la producción del IIGS en diciembre de 1992.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Apple IIGS (als IIgs bezeichnet), das fünfte und leistungsstärkste Modell der Apple II Familie, ist ein 16-Bit-Personalcomputer von Apple Computer. Obwohl er das Macintosh-Aussehen und -Gefühl sowie eine ähnliche Auflösung und Farbgebung wie der Amiga und der Atari ST aufweist, bleibt er mit früheren Apple II-Modellen kompatibel. Das "GS" im Namen steht für "Graphics and Sound" (Grafik und Sound) und bezieht sich auf die verbesserte Multimedia-Hardware, insbesondere die hochmoderne Audioausstattung.

Der Mikrocomputer unterscheidet sich radikal von allen früheren Apple II, mit einem 16-Bit 65C816 Mikroprozessor, direktem Zugriff auf Megabytes Arbeitsspeicher (RAM) und Maus. Er ist der erste Computer von Apple mit einer farbigen grafischen Benutzeroberfläche (Farbe wurde sechs Monate später mit dem Macintosh II eingeführt) und einer Apple Desktop Bus-Schnittstelle für Tastaturen, Mäuse und andere Eingabegeräte. Er ist der erste Personal Computer mit einem Wavetable-Synthese-Chip, der Technologie von Ensoniq verwendet.

Der IIGS stellte eine vielversprechende Zukunft und evolutionäre Weiterentwicklung der Apple II Linie dar, aber Apple konzentrierte sich zunehmend auf die Macintosh Plattform. Apple stellte die Produktion des IIGS im Dezember 1992 ein.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Apple IIGS (stylé comme IIgs), le cinquième et le plus puissant de la famille Apple II, est un ordinateur personnel 16 bits produit par Apple Computer. Tout en présentant l'aspect et la convivialité du Macintosh, ainsi qu'une résolution et des couleurs similaires à celles de l'Amiga et de l'Atari ST, il reste compatible avec les modèles Apple II antérieurs. Le "GS" dans le nom signifie "Graphics and Sound", en référence à son matériel multimédia amélioré, en particulier son audio de pointe.

Ce micro-ordinateur se démarque radicalement de tous les Apple II précédents, avec un microprocesseur 65C816 16 bits, un accès direct à des mégaoctets de mémoire vive (RAM) et une souris. C'est le premier ordinateur d'Apple doté d'une interface graphique couleur (la couleur a été introduite sur le Macintosh II six mois plus tard) et d'une interface Apple Desktop Bus pour les claviers, souris et autres périphériques d'entrée. C'est le premier ordinateur personnel doté d'une puce de synthèse à table d'ondes, utilisant la technologie d'Ensoniq.

L'IIGS laissait présager un avenir prometteur et une évolution de la gamme Apple II, mais Apple s'est de plus en plus concentré sur la plate-forme Macintosh. Apple a cessé la production de l'IIGS en décembre 1992.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'Apple IIGS (in stile IIgs), il quinto e più potente della famiglia Apple II, è un personal computer a 16 bit prodotto da Apple Computer. Pur avendo l'aspetto del Macintosh e una risoluzione e un colore simili a quelli dell'Amiga e dell'Atari ST, rimane compatibile con i precedenti modelli di Apple II. La sigla "GS" sta per "Graphics and Sound" (grafica e suono) e si riferisce all'hardware multimediale potenziato, in particolare all'audio all'avanguardia.

Il microcomputer si discosta radicalmente da qualsiasi Apple II precedente, con un microprocessore 65C816 a 16 bit, accesso diretto a megabyte di memoria ad accesso casuale (RAM) e mouse. Fu il primo computer Apple con un'interfaccia grafica a colori (il colore verrà introdotto sul Macintosh II sei mesi dopo) e un'interfaccia Apple Desktop Bus per tastiere, mouse e altri dispositivi di input. Fu anche il primo personal computer con un chip di sintesi wavetable, che utilizza la tecnologia Ensoniq.

L'IIGS rappresentava un futuro promettente e un progresso evolutivo della linea Apple II, ma Apple si concentrò sempre più sulla piattaforma Macintosh. Apple cessò la produzione dell'IIGS nel dicembre 1992.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Apple IIGS foi um modelo de computador de 16 bits produzido pela Apple na segunda metade da década de 1980. Este modelo era compatível com a família de computadores Apple II.

Especificações técnicas
- processador: W65C816
- espaço de endereçamento: 16 MB (256 páginas de 64 kB)
- modo de operação do processador compatível com o processador 65C02A usado em modelos anteriores, como o Apple IIc
- RAM: 256 kB (com possibilidade de expansão para 8 MB)
- ROM: 128 kB (com possibilidade de expansão para 1 MB): continha procedimentos do sistema, interrupções, gerenciamento de dispositivos, transmissão de dados da rede - AppleTalk, interpretador Applesoft Basic
- unidades de disquete externas:
    2x3,5” 800 kB
    2x5,25” 140 kB (permitindo a transferência de software de modelos anteriores da série Apple II)
- conector RS 232
- modos de gráfico compatíveis com Apple IIc
- modos de gráfico adicionais
    200x320 pontos 16 cores de uma paleta de 4096 cores
    200x690 pontos 9 cores
    200x640 em 16 cores com algumas limitações
- chip de som DOC da Ensoniq
- teclado QWERTY com teclado numérico separado</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
