<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.34</pos>
			<maxSize>0.2</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.34" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>2015</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Arduboy</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>The Arduboy is a handheld game console with open source software, based on the Arduino hardware platform.

The original version of the Arduboy was 1.6 millimetres (0.063 in) thick, with the height and width of a credit card, and was initially designed by Kevin Bates as an electronic business card.

In preparation for a consumer version, the developer moved to Shenzhen, China to work on the Arduboy at the HAX accelerator.

Later consumer versions replaced the first version's touch-sensitive panels by physical buttons, and include a protective plastic case, raising the thickness to 5 millimetres (0.20 in).

A non-production smaller formfactor "Arduboy Mini" was demonstrated in 2019. Another non-production system, the "Arduboy Nano" was demonstrated in 2021 with an smaller formfactor than the Arduboy Mini.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Arduboy to przenośna konsola do gier z oprogramowaniem open source, oparta na platformie sprzętowej Arduino.

Oryginalna wersja Arduboya miała grubość 1,6 milimetra (0,063 cala), wysokość i szerokość karty kredytowej i została początkowo zaprojektowana przez Kevina Batesa jako elektroniczna wizytówka.

W ramach przygotowań do wersji konsumenckiej deweloper przeniósł się do Shenzhen w Chinach, aby pracować nad Arduboyem w akceleratorze HAX.

Późniejsze wersje konsumenckie zastąpiły panele dotykowe pierwszej wersji fizycznymi przyciskami i zawierały ochronną plastikową obudowę, zwiększając grubość do 5 milimetrów (0,20 cala).

Nieprodukcyjny mniejszy formfactor "Arduboy Mini" został zademonstrowany w 2019 roku. Kolejny system nieprodukcyjny, "Arduboy Nano" został zademonstrowany w 2021 roku z mniejszym formfactorem niż Arduboy Mini.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Descriptions. Pls send me it in Discord.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Портативная игровая консоль с открытым исходным кодом, основанная на аппаратной платформе Arduino.

Первоначальная версия Arduboy имела толщину 1,6 миллиметра (0,063 дюйма), высоту и ширину кредитной карты, и изначально была разработана Кевином Бейтсом как электронная визитная карточка.

Для подготовки потребительской версии разработчик переехал в Шэньчжэнь, Китай, чтобы работать над Arduboy в HAX accelerator.

В более поздних потребительских версиях сенсорные панели первой версии были заменены на физические кнопки, а защитный пластиковый корпус увеличил толщину до 5 миллиметров (0,20 дюйма).

В 2019 году была продемонстрирована несерийная система "Arduboy Mini" меньшего форм-фактора. Еще одна несерийная система, "Arduboy Nano", была продемонстрирована в 2021 году с меньшим форм-фактором, чем Arduboy Mini.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
