<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
  <formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
  <view name="system">
    <image name="background1" extra="true">
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
      </storyboard>
    </image>
    <image name="background" extra="true">
      <zIndex>90</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
      </storyboard>
    </image>
    <video name="videocrton" extra="true">
      <path>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_ON.mp4</path>
      <delay>0</delay>
      <loops>0</loops>
      <effect>none</effect>
      <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
      <pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
      <maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
      <zIndex>26</zIndex>
    </video>
    <video name="videobox" extra="true">
      <path>{random}</path>
      <path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
      <!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
      <path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
      <default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
      <delay>0</delay>
      <effect>none</effect>
      <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
      <pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
      <maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
      <zIndex>25</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
      </storyboard>
    </video>
    <text name="TextDate" extra="true">
      <pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
      <text>1993</text>
      <fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
      <color>666666</color>
      <fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
      <zIndex>140</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
      </storyboard>
    </text>
    <text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
      <pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
      <text>Atari</text>
      <fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
      <color>FFFFFF</color>
      <fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
      <zIndex>140</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
      </storyboard>
    </text>
    <text name="TextName" extra="true">
      <pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
      <size>0.5 0</size>
      <text>Jaguar</text>
      <fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
      <color>FFFFFF</color>
      <fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
      <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
      <zIndex>140</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
      </storyboard>
    </text>
    <text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
      <size>0.5 0</size>
      <pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
      <text>The Atari Jaguar is a home video game console developed by Atari Corporation and released in North America in November 1993. Part of the fifth generation of video game consoles, it competed with the 16-bit Sega Genesis and Super NES and the 32-bit 3DO Interactive Multiplayer which launched the same year. Despite its two custom 32-bit processors – Tom and Jerry – in addition to a Motorola 68000, Atari marketed it as the world's first 64-bit game system, emphasizing its 64-bit bus. The Jaguar launched with Cybermorph as the pack-in game.

Development on the Atari Jaguar started in the early 1990s by Flare Technology which also designed the cancelled Atari Panther console. The multi-chip architecture, hardware bugs, and lacking developer support tools made game development difficult. Underwhelming sales further contributed to the console's lack of third-party support. The game library comprised only 50 licensed titles, plus another 13 games on the Jaguar CD.

Atari attempted to extend the lifespan of the system with the Atari Jaguar CD add-on and marketing the Jaguar as the low-cost next generation console, with a price tag over $100 less than any of its competitors. With the release of the Sega Saturn and Sony PlayStation in 1995, sales of the Jaguar continued to fall. It sold no more than 250,000 units before it was discontinued in 1996. The commercial failure of the Jaguar prompted Atari to leave the console market.</text>
      <text lang="pl">Atari Jaguar – konsola gier wideo piątej generacji produkcji Atari, która została wydana w 1993 roku.

Po premierze w listopadzie 1993 została dobrze przyjęta w prasie fachowej, jednak z powodu złej polityki Atari (m.in. brak gier) poniosła porażkę rynkową: sprzedano ok. 250 000 egzemplarzy. W zamierzeniu konsola miała być rywalem produktów Sega Genesis i Super Nintendo Entertainment System, lecz przyczyniła się do odejścia firmy Atari z rynku sprzętu komputerowego. Ponad 110 projektów będących w fazie produkcji nigdy nie zostało wydanych.

Dane techniczne:
- procesor Motorola 68000 16/32-bit – ogólny procesor sterujący, częstotliwość 13,295 MHz.
- pamięć RAM uwspólniona– 2 MB, szyna 64-bitowa; wykorzystano cztery 16-bitowe kości DRAM działające w trybie „fast page” (FPM),
- nośnik (kartridż) – pojemność do 6 MB (teoretycznie), 4 MB (praktycznie – ograniczenie zestawów developerskich)
- przepustowość magistrali: 106,4 MB/s</text>
      <text lang="ru">Игровая консоль, выпущенная в ноябре 1993 года компанией Atari. В своё время являлась мощной платформой следующего (пятого по счёту) поколения телевизионных игровых приставок. Поступила в продажу по цене 249,99 долларов. Рекламировалась как «первая 64-битная система», что было рекламной уловкой — CPU и GPU приставки имели RISC-подобную 32-битную архитектуру, 64-битным был графический сопроцессор «Том».

Однако для приставки было выпущено ограниченное число игр, большинство из которых были низкого качества, что отрицательно сказалось на продажах консоли. К причинам провала также можно отнести неудачно выбранный носитель (картридж), неудобный джойстик и ценовую политику. Конкуренция с другими приставками, особенно использовавшими CD-диски как PlayStation, обрекла Atari Jaguar на провал. В период с конца 1993 по конец 1995 года было продано всего 125 тыс. экземпляров.

И хотя производителем были предприняты попытки привлечь к консоли интерес покупателей, выпустив в спешном порядке адаптер для чтения компакт-дисков Atari Jaguar CD, устройство для сохранения состояния игры Memory Track и устройство для совместной игры на двух приставках JagLink, эти действия не смогли повысить продажи. Претерпев серьёзные убытки, Atari была вынуждена покинуть рынок игровых приставок.</text>
      <text lang="it">L'Atari Jaguar è una console per videogiochi domestica sviluppata da Atari Corporation e rilasciata in Nord America nel novembre 1993. Appartenente alla quinta generazione di console per videogiochi, era in concorrenza con il Sega Genesis e il Super NES a 16 bit e con il 3DO Interactive Multiplayer a 32 bit, lanciato lo stesso anno. Nonostante i due processori personalizzati a 32 bit - Tom e Jerry - oltre a un Motorola 68000, Atari lo commercializzò come il primo sistema di gioco a 64 bit al mondo, enfatizzando il suo bus a 64 bit. Il Jaguar fu lanciato con Cybermorph come gioco in dotazione.

Lo sviluppo dell'Atari Jaguar iniziò all'inizio degli anni '90 da parte di Flare Technology, che progettò anche la console Atari Panther cancellata. L'architettura multi-chip, i bug hardware e la mancanza di strumenti di supporto per gli sviluppatori resero difficile lo sviluppo dei giochi. Le vendite deludenti contribuirono ulteriormente alla mancanza di supporto da parte di terzi. La libreria di giochi comprendeva solo 50 titoli su licenza, più altri 13 giochi sul CD Jaguar.

Atari cercò di prolungare la vita del sistema con il CD aggiuntivo Atari Jaguar e commercializzando il Jaguar come console di nuova generazione a basso costo, con un prezzo inferiore di oltre 100 dollari rispetto a tutti i suoi concorrenti. Con l'uscita del Sega Saturn e della Sony PlayStation nel 1995, le vendite del Jaguar continuarono a diminuire. Non vendette più di 250.000 unità prima di essere dismessa nel 1996. Il fallimento commerciale del Jaguar spinse Atari ad abbandonare il mercato delle console.</text>
      <fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
      <color>666666</color>
      <fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
      <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
      <zIndex>140</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
      </storyboard>
    </text>
  </view>
</theme>
