<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.237</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.208 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.227</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.208 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Atari</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>5200</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Atari 5200 SuperSystem or simply Atari 5200 is a home video game console introduced in 1982 by Atari, Inc. as a higher-end complement for the popular Atari Video Computer System. The VCS was renamed to the Atari 2600 at the time of the 5200's launch. The 5200 was created to compete with the Intellivision, but wound up a direct competitor of the ColecoVision shortly after its release. While the Coleco system shipped with the first home version of Nintendo's Donkey Kong, the pack-in game for the 5200 was 1978's Super Breakout which had already appeared on the Atari VCS and Atari 8-bit computers in 1978 and 1979 respectively.

The 5200's internal hardware is almost identical to that of Atari's Atari 8-bit family, although software is not directly compatible between the two systems. The 5200's controllers have an analog joystick and a numeric keypad along with start, pause, and reset buttons. The 360-degree non-centering joystick was touted as offering more control than the eight-way Atari CX40 joystick of the 2600, but it was a focal point for criticism.

On May 21, 1984, during a press conference at which the Atari 7800 was introduced, company executives revealed that the 5200 had been discontinued after just two years on the market. Total sales of the 5200 were reportedly in excess of 1 million units, far short of its predecessor's sales of over 30 million.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Atari 5200 – konsola gier wideo wprowadzona do sprzedaży w 1982 przez Atari. Została stworzona, aby rywalizować z Mattel Intellivision, ale wkrótce po wydaniu 5200 rywalizowała również z ColecoVision. Była ona bardziej zaawansowana technologicznie i opłacalna cenowo niż jakakolwiek dostępna wówczas konsola.

Dane techniczne:
- CPU: indywidualny 8-bitowy MOS 6502C @ 1,79 MHz
- koprocesory: 3 indywidualne chipy VLSI
- rozdzielczość ekranu: 320 × 192 (możliwość projektowania dowolnych trybów, np. z większą rozdzielczością), 16 wyświetlanych kolorów (spośród 256)
- GPU: GTIA
- dźwięk: 4-kanałowy dźwięk z chipu POKEY, który jednocześnie obsługiwał również I/O
- RAM: 16 kB
- ROM: do 64 kB (kartridże do 32 kB)</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка компании Atari, выпущенная на рынок в 1982 году в качестве замены получившей широкую известность Atari 2600. Модель 5200 была создана для конкуренции с Mattel Intellivision, но вскоре после выпуска приставки оказалось, что она скорее конкурирует с ColecoVision. Некоторые изъяны, допущенные при проектировании, оказали сильное влияние на удобство использования системы, из-за чего модель в целом можно признать неудачной.

Выбирая название новой системы, разработчики просто удвоили число 2600. Модель Atari 5200, выпущенная в 1982 году, имела 4 порта джойстика (большинство систем того времени предлагали только два), новый контроллер с аналоговым джойстиком и цифровой клавиатурой, четырьмя кнопками «огня» и кнопками Start / Pause / Reset. С приставкой впервые поставлялось устройство «TV switchbox» для подключения к телевизору — когда приставка включалась, телевизор автоматически переключался с антенного сигнала на сигнал с приставки; раньше для переключения нужно было сделать это выключателем на коробке коннектора.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Atari 5200 SuperSystem o simplemente Atari 5200 es una videoconsola doméstica introducida en 1982 por Atari, Inc. como complemento de gama alta para el popular Atari Video Computer System. El VCS pasó a llamarse Atari 2600 en el momento del lanzamiento de la 5200. La 5200 se creó para competir con la Intellivision, pero acabó siendo competidora directa de la ColecoVision poco después de su lanzamiento. Mientras que la consola Coleco incluía la primera versión doméstica de Donkey Kong de Nintendo, el juego incluido en el pack de la 5200 era Super Breakout de 1978, que ya había aparecido en la Atari VCS y en los ordenadores Atari de 8 bits en 1978 y 1979 respectivamente.

El hardware interno del 5200 es casi idéntico al de la familia Atari de 8 bits, aunque el software no es directamente compatible entre los dos sistemas. Los mandos del 5200 tienen un joystick analógico y un teclado numérico junto con botones de inicio, pausa y reinicio. El joystick de 360 grados sin centrado se promocionó por ofrecer más control que el joystick Atari CX40 de ocho direcciones de la 2600, pero fue un foco de críticas.

El 21 de mayo de 1984, durante una conferencia de prensa en la que se presentó la Atari 7800, los ejecutivos de la compañía revelaron que la 5200 había sido descatalogada tras sólo dos años en el mercado. Según los informes, las ventas totales de la 5200 superaron el millón de unidades, muy lejos de los más de 30 millones de su predecesora.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Atari 5200 SuperSystem oder einfach Atari 5200 ist eine Heimvideospielkonsole, die 1982 von Atari, Inc. als höherwertige Ergänzung zum beliebten Atari Video Computer System eingeführt wurde. Das VCS wurde zum Zeitpunkt der Markteinführung des 5200 in Atari 2600 umbenannt. Das 5200 wurde entwickelt, um mit dem Intellivision zu konkurrieren, wurde aber kurz nach seiner Veröffentlichung zu einem direkten Konkurrenten des ColecoVision. Während das Coleco-System mit der ersten Heimversion von Nintendos Donkey Kong ausgeliefert wurde, lag dem 5200 das Spiel Super Breakout aus dem Jahr 1978 bei, das bereits 1978 und 1979 auf dem Atari VCS und dem Atari 8-Bit-Computer erschienen war.

Die interne Hardware des 5200 ist fast identisch mit der der Atari 8-Bit-Familie, auch wenn die Software nicht direkt zwischen den beiden Systemen kompatibel ist. Die Controller des 5200 verfügen über einen analogen Joystick und ein numerisches Tastenfeld sowie Start-, Pause- und Reset-Tasten. Der 360-Grad-Joystick ohne Zentrierung wurde damit angepriesen, dass er mehr Kontrolle als der Acht-Wege-Atari-CX40-Joystick des 2600 biete, aber er war ein Brennpunkt der Kritik.

Am 21. Mai 1984, während einer Pressekonferenz, auf der der Atari 7800 vorgestellt wurde, gaben die Verantwortlichen des Unternehmens bekannt, dass der 5200 nach nur zwei Jahren auf dem Markt eingestellt worden war. Die Gesamtverkäufe des 5200 betrugen Berichten zufolge mehr als 1 Million Stück, was weit hinter den Verkäufen seines Vorgängers von über 30 Millionen zurückblieb.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Atari 5200 SuperSystem ou simplement Atari 5200 est une console de jeu vidéo de salon introduite en 1982 par Atari, Inc. comme complément haut de gamme du populaire Atari Video Computer System (VCS). Le VCS a été rebaptisé Atari 2600 au moment du lancement de la 5200. Le 5200 a été créé pour concurrencer l'Intellivision, mais est devenu un concurrent direct de la ColecoVision peu après sa sortie. Alors que la ColecoVision était livrée avec la première version domestique de Donkey Kong de Nintendo, le jeu livré avec le 5200 était Super Breakout de 1978, qui était déjà apparu sur les ordinateurs Atari VCS et Atari 8-bit en 1978 et 1979 respectivement.

Le matériel interne du 5200 est presque identique à celui de la famille Atari 8-bit, bien que les logiciels ne soient pas directement compatibles entre les deux systèmes. Les manettes du 5200 comportent un joystick analogique et un clavier numérique, ainsi que des boutons de démarrage, de pause et de réinitialisation. Le joystick non centré à 360 degrés a été présenté comme offrant plus de contrôle que le joystick Atari CX40 à huit directions du 2600, mais il a fait l'objet de nombreuses critiques.

Le 21 mai 1984, lors d'une conférence de presse au cours de laquelle l'Atari 7800 a été présenté, les dirigeants de la société ont révélé que le 5200 avait été abandonné après seulement deux ans sur le marché. Les ventes totales du 5200 auraient dépassé le million d'unités, bien loin des 30 millions d'unités vendues par son prédécesseur.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'Atari 5200 SuperSystem o semplicemente Atari 5200 è una console per videogiochi domestici introdotta nel 1982 da Atari, Inc. come complemento di fascia alta per il popolare Atari Video Computer System. Il VCS fu rinominato Atari 2600 al momento del lancio del 5200. Il 5200 fu creato per competere con l'Intellivision, ma finì per diventare un concorrente diretto del ColecoVision poco dopo la sua uscita. Mentre la console Coleco veniva fornita con la prima versione casalinga di Donkey Kong di Nintendo, il gioco in confezione per il 5200 era Super Breakout del 1978, già apparso sui computer Atari VCS e Atari 8-bit rispettivamente nel 1978 e nel 1979.

L'hardware interno del 5200 è quasi identico a quello della famiglia Atari 8-bit, anche se il software non è direttamente compatibile tra i due sistemi. I controller del 5200 hanno un joystick analogico e un tastierino numerico, oltre ai pulsanti di avvio, pausa e reset. Il joystick non centrato a 360 gradi è stato pubblicizzato come in grado di offrire un maggiore controllo rispetto al joystick a otto vie Atari CX40 del 2600, ma è stato oggetto di critiche.

Il 21 maggio 1984, durante la conferenza stampa di presentazione dell'Atari 7800, i dirigenti dell'azienda rivelarono che il 5200 era stato ritirato dal mercato dopo soli due anni. Le vendite totali del 5200 sarebbero state superiori a 1 milione di unità, ben al di sotto delle vendite del suo predecessore, che avevano superato i 30 milioni.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Atari 5200 – console de videogame lançada em 1982 pela Atari. Foi criada para competir com a Mattel Intellivision, mas logo após o lançamento da 5200 também rivalizava com a ColecoVision. Era tecnologicamente mais avançada e economicamente mais viável do que qualquer console disponível na época.

Especificações:
- CPU: MOS 6502C de 8 bits @ 1,79 MHz
- coprocessadores: 3 chips VLSI individuais
- resolução de tela: 320 × 192 (possibilidade de design de modos personalizados, como com maior resolução), 16 cores exibidas (de 256)
- GPU: GTIA
- som: som de 4 canais do chip POKEY, que também controlava I/O
- RAM: 16 kB
- ROM: até 64 kB (cartuchos de até 32 kB)</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
