<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.4995 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.252</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2195 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.4995 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.242</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2195 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1993</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Atari</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Jaguar</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Atari Jaguar is a home video game console developed by Atari Corporation and released in North America in November 1993. Part of the fifth generation of video game consoles, it competed with the 16-bit Sega Genesis and Super NES and the 32-bit 3DO Interactive Multiplayer which launched the same year. Despite its two custom 32-bit processors – Tom and Jerry – in addition to a Motorola 68000, Atari marketed it as the world's first 64-bit game system, emphasizing its 64-bit bus. The Jaguar launched with Cybermorph as the pack-in game.

Development on the Atari Jaguar started in the early 1990s by Flare Technology which also designed the cancelled Atari Panther console. The multi-chip architecture, hardware bugs, and lacking developer support tools made game development difficult. Underwhelming sales further contributed to the console's lack of third-party support. The game library comprised only 50 licensed titles, plus another 13 games on the Jaguar CD.

Atari attempted to extend the lifespan of the system with the Atari Jaguar CD add-on and marketing the Jaguar as the low-cost next generation console, with a price tag over $100 less than any of its competitors. With the release of the Sega Saturn and Sony PlayStation in 1995, sales of the Jaguar continued to fall. It sold no more than 250,000 units before it was discontinued in 1996. The commercial failure of the Jaguar prompted Atari to leave the console market.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Atari Jaguar – konsola gier wideo piątej generacji produkcji Atari, która została wydana w 1993 roku.

Po premierze w listopadzie 1993 została dobrze przyjęta w prasie fachowej, jednak z powodu złej polityki Atari (m.in. brak gier) poniosła porażkę rynkową: sprzedano ok. 250 000 egzemplarzy. W zamierzeniu konsola miała być rywalem produktów Sega Genesis i Super Nintendo Entertainment System, lecz przyczyniła się do odejścia firmy Atari z rynku sprzętu komputerowego. Ponad 110 projektów będących w fazie produkcji nigdy nie zostało wydanych.

Dane techniczne:
- procesor Motorola 68000 16/32-bit – ogólny procesor sterujący, częstotliwość 13,295 MHz.
- pamięć RAM uwspólniona– 2 MB, szyna 64-bitowa; wykorzystano cztery 16-bitowe kości DRAM działające w trybie „fast page” (FPM),
- nośnik (kartridż) – pojemność do 6 MB (teoretycznie), 4 MB (praktycznie – ograniczenie zestawów developerskich)
- przepustowość magistrali: 106,4 MB/s</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая консоль, выпущенная в ноябре 1993 года компанией Atari. В своё время являлась мощной платформой следующего (пятого по счёту) поколения телевизионных игровых приставок. Поступила в продажу по цене 249,99 долларов. Рекламировалась как «первая 64-битная система», что было рекламной уловкой — CPU и GPU приставки имели RISC-подобную 32-битную архитектуру, 64-битным был графический сопроцессор «Том».

Однако для приставки было выпущено ограниченное число игр, большинство из которых были низкого качества, что отрицательно сказалось на продажах консоли. К причинам провала также можно отнести неудачно выбранный носитель (картридж), неудобный джойстик и ценовую политику. Конкуренция с другими приставками, особенно использовавшими CD-диски как PlayStation, обрекла Atari Jaguar на провал. В период с конца 1993 по конец 1995 года было продано всего 125 тыс. экземпляров.

И хотя производителем были предприняты попытки привлечь к консоли интерес покупателей, выпустив в спешном порядке адаптер для чтения компакт-дисков Atari Jaguar CD, устройство для сохранения состояния игры Memory Track и устройство для совместной игры на двух приставках JagLink, эти действия не смогли повысить продажи. Претерпев серьёзные убытки, Atari была вынуждена покинуть рынок игровых приставок.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Atari Jaguar es una videoconsola doméstica desarrollada por Atari Corporation y lanzada en Norteamérica en noviembre de 1993. Perteneciente a la quinta generación de consolas de videojuegos, compitió con la Sega Genesis y la Super NES de 16 bits y la 3DO Interactive Multiplayer de 32 bits, lanzada el mismo año. A pesar de sus dos procesadores personalizados de 32 bits -Tom y Jerry- además de un Motorola 68000, Atari la comercializó como el primer sistema de juego de 64 bits del mundo, haciendo hincapié en su bus de 64 bits. El Jaguar se lanzó con Cybermorph como juego incluido.

El desarrollo de la Atari Jaguar comenzó a principios de los 90 por parte de Flare Technology, que también diseñó la cancelada consola Atari Panther. La arquitectura multichip, los fallos de hardware y la falta de herramientas de desarrollo dificultaron la creación de juegos. Las decepcionantes ventas contribuyeron a la falta de apoyo de terceros a la consola. La biblioteca de juegos sólo incluía 50 títulos con licencia, además de otros 13 juegos en el CD de Jaguar.

Atari intentó prolongar la vida útil del sistema con el complemento Atari Jaguar CD y comercializando la Jaguar como la consola de bajo coste de la próxima generación, con un precio de más de 100 dólares menos que cualquiera de sus competidoras. Con el lanzamiento de la Sega Saturn y la Sony PlayStation en 1995, las ventas de la Jaguar siguieron cayendo. No llegó a vender más de 250.000 unidades antes de dejar de fabricarse en 1996. El fracaso comercial de la Jaguar llevó a Atari a abandonar el mercado de las consolas.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Atari Jaguar ist eine Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch, die von der Atari Corporation entwickelt und im November 1993 in Nordamerika veröffentlicht wurde. Als Teil der fünften Generation von Videospielkonsolen konkurrierte er mit dem 16-Bit Sega Genesis und Super NES sowie dem 32-Bit 3DO Interactive Multiplayer, der im selben Jahr auf den Markt kam. Trotz seiner zwei speziellen 32-Bit-Prozessoren - Tom und Jerry - zusätzlich zu einem Motorola 68000, vermarktete Atari ihn als das weltweit erste 64-Bit-Spielsystem und betonte seinen 64-Bit-Bus. Der Jaguar kam mit dem Spiel Cybermorph als Beigabe auf den Markt.

Die Entwicklung des Atari Jaguar begann Anfang der 1990er Jahre durch Flare Technology, das auch die eingestellte Atari Panther-Konsole entwickelte. Die Multi-Chip-Architektur, Hardware-Fehler und fehlende Tools zur Unterstützung der Entwickler erschwerten die Entwicklung von Spielen. Die enttäuschenden Verkaufszahlen trugen zusätzlich dazu bei, dass die Konsole von Drittanbietern nicht unterstützt wurde. Die Spielebibliothek umfasste nur 50 lizenzierte Titel und weitere 13 Spiele auf der Jaguar-CD.

Atari versuchte, die Lebensdauer des Systems mit dem Atari Jaguar CD-Add-on zu verlängern und den Jaguar als preisgünstige Konsole der nächsten Generation zu vermarkten, die über 100 Dollar weniger kostete als alle anderen. Mit dem Erscheinen des Sega Saturn und der Sony PlayStation im Jahr 1995 gingen die Verkaufszahlen des Jaguar weiter zurück. Bis zu seiner Einstellung im Jahr 1996 wurden nicht mehr als 250.000 Einheiten verkauft. Der kommerzielle Misserfolg des Jaguar veranlasste Atari, den Konsolenmarkt zu verlassen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Atari Jaguar est une console de jeux vidéo de salon développée par Atari Corporation et commercialisée en Amérique du Nord en novembre 1993. Faisant partie de la cinquième génération de consoles de jeux vidéo, elle était en concurrence avec les consoles 16 bits Sega Genesis et Super NES, ainsi qu'avec la console 32 bits 3DO Interactive Multiplayer, lancée la même année. Malgré ses deux processeurs 32 bits personnalisés - Tom et Jerry - en plus d'un Motorola 68000, Atari l'a commercialisée comme la première console de jeu 64 bits au monde, en mettant l'accent sur son bus 64 bits. La Jaguar a été lancée avec Cybermorph comme jeu d'entrée de gamme.

Le développement de l'Atari Jaguar a commencé au début des années 1990 par Flare Technology, qui a également conçu la console Atari Panther, qui a été annulée. L'architecture multi-puces, les bogues matériels et le manque d'outils d'assistance aux développeurs ont rendu le développement de jeux difficile. Les ventes décevantes ont également contribué à l'absence de soutien de la part de tiers. La bibliothèque de jeux ne comprenait que 50 titres sous licence, plus 13 autres jeux sur le CD Jaguar.

Atari a tenté de prolonger la durée de vie de la console avec le module d'extension Atari Jaguar CD et en commercialisant la Jaguar comme la console de nouvelle génération à bas prix, avec un prix inférieur de plus de 100 dollars à celui de tous ses concurrents. Avec la sortie de la Sega Saturn et de la Sony PlayStation en 1995, les ventes de la Jaguar ont continué à chuter. Elle ne s'est pas vendue à plus de 250 000 exemplaires avant d'être abandonnée en 1996. L'échec commercial de la Jaguar a incité Atari à quitter le marché des consoles.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'Atari Jaguar è una console per videogiochi domestica sviluppata da Atari Corporation e rilasciata in Nord America nel novembre 1993. Appartenente alla quinta generazione di console per videogiochi, era in concorrenza con il Sega Genesis e il Super NES a 16 bit e con il 3DO Interactive Multiplayer a 32 bit, lanciato lo stesso anno. Nonostante i due processori personalizzati a 32 bit - Tom e Jerry - oltre a un Motorola 68000, Atari lo commercializzò come il primo sistema di gioco a 64 bit al mondo, enfatizzando il suo bus a 64 bit. Il Jaguar fu lanciato con Cybermorph come gioco in dotazione.

Lo sviluppo dell'Atari Jaguar iniziò all'inizio degli anni '90 da parte di Flare Technology, che progettò anche la console Atari Panther cancellata. L'architettura multi-chip, i bug hardware e la mancanza di strumenti di supporto per gli sviluppatori resero difficile lo sviluppo dei giochi. Le vendite deludenti contribuirono ulteriormente alla mancanza di supporto da parte di terzi. La libreria di giochi comprendeva solo 50 titoli su licenza, più altri 13 giochi sul CD Jaguar.

Atari cercò di prolungare la vita del sistema con il CD aggiuntivo Atari Jaguar e commercializzando il Jaguar come console di nuova generazione a basso costo, con un prezzo inferiore di oltre 100 dollari rispetto a tutti i suoi concorrenti. Con l'uscita del Sega Saturn e della Sony PlayStation nel 1995, le vendite del Jaguar continuarono a diminuire. Non vendette più di 250.000 unità prima di essere dismessa nel 1996. Il fallimento commerciale del Jaguar spinse Atari ad abbandonare il mercato delle console.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
