<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5005 0.33</pos>
			<maxSize>0.271</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2205 0.33" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text></text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>Light Gun</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>A light gun is a pointing device for computers and a control device for arcade and video games, typically shaped to resemble a pistol. In aviation and shipping, it can also be a directional signal lamp.

Modern screen-based light guns work by building an optical sensor into the gun, which receives its input from the light emitted by on-screen target(s). The first device of this type, the light pen, was used on the MIT Whirlwind computer.

The light gun and its ancestor the light pen are now rarely used as pointing devices due largely to the popularity of the mouse and changes in monitor display technology—conventional light guns work only with CRT monitors.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le tir au pistolet optique ou light gun shooter (également appelé light gun game ou gun game), est un genre de jeu vidéo comparable à celui du jeu de tir dans lequel l'élément principal de conception est de viser et tirer avec un pistolet optique.

Les jeux de ce genre s'articulent autour de protagonistes et objets inanimés marqués comme cibles de tir. Les jeux de tir au pistolet optique proposent généralement des thématiques d'action ou d'horreur dont certains jeux peuvent employer un traitement humoristique et parodique de ces conventions.

Ce type de jeu emploie des périphériques appelés « Pistolets optiques », nommés ainsi car ils utilisent des capteurs lumineux. Des jeux mécaniques utilisant des pistolets optiques ont existé dès les années 1930, même si leur fonctionnement était différent de celui du jeu vidéo. Durant les années 1970, les jeux mécaniques sont remplacés par des jeux vidéo électroniques. Parmi les jeux les plus populaires, Duck Hunt émergea dans les années 1980. Virtua Cop, suivi par Time Crisis, portèrent le genre dans les années 1990. Dès 2000, le jeu de tir au pistolet optique perdit en popularité, entravé par des problèmes de compatibilité. Cependant, il existe encore un marché de niche pour ce genre de nos jours.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Световой пистолет — указывающее устройство для компьютеров и телевизионных игровых приставок. Данное устройство позволяет «стрелять» в экран телевизора, с соответствующей реакцией «попал-промахнулся».

На массовый рынок световой пистолет вышел вместе с приставкой Magnavox Odyssey. Ружьё Shooting Gallery («тир») стало необязательным аксессуаром для этой приставки. Впоследствии пистолетом снабжали приставки NES, Sega Megadrive, SNES. Для приставок типа NES он был обязательным в наборе, вкупе с джойстиками и картриджем.

Пистолет применялся в играх Duck Hunt, Clay Shooting и некоторых боевиках.

Переход на HD-телевизоры, начавшийся в середине 1990-х, закрыл самую простую разновидность пистолета, к тому же развитие геймдизайна создало новые жанры и усложнило геймплей имеющихся — с пистолетом такое провернуть сложно (хотя несколько раз пытались: например, в Time Crisis под ногами игрока была педаль). Ностальгирующие геймеры испытывают различные конструкции, но ни одна из них не стала новым стандартом.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>