<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-left" extra="true">
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.3 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.1 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.305 0.45</pos>
			<minSize>0.1 0.3</minSize>
			<rotation>14</rotation>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>27</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.025 0.45" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-right" extra="true">
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.6 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.8 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.69 0.45</pos>
			<minSize>0.1 0.3</minSize>
			<rotation>-14</rotation>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>27</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.41 0.45" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.47</pos>
			<maxSize>0.175</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.23</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.184</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.47" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video-left" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.2 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.392 0.48</pos>
			<maxSize>0.14</maxSize>
			<rotation>-76</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.112 0.48" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video-right" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.8 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.607 0.48</pos>
			<maxSize>0.14</maxSize>
			<rotation>76</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.327 0.48" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/teknoparrot.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/teknoparrot.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise169.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.47</pos>
			<maxSize>0.162</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.22</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.182</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.47" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<video name="videobox2" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/teknoparrot-right.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/teknoparrot-right.mp4</path>
			<audio>false</audio>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.8 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.621 0.47</pos>
			<maxSize>0.14</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.2</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.16</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<rotation>0</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.341 0.47" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<video name="videobox3" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/teknoparrot-left.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/teknoparrot-left.mp4</path>
			<audio>false</audio>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.2 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.38 0.47</pos>
			<maxSize>0.14</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.2</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.16</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<rotation>0</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.1 0.47" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2023</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sleyk Industries</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<text>Batoparrot</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Conceived initially as a parody system intent on making fun of the exclusivity and long-believed monopolistic ideals of Teknoparrot, (a Windows-based modern arcade game emulator) Batoparrot began as a simple idea to bring a few Teknoparrot playable games to Batocera, using the arcade game's PC counterpart as a substitute for the game's arcade counterpart in Linux. The idea being, that any Teknoparrot games that have a PC counterpart will be added to Batoparrot and fully playable in Batocera. In this regard,  Batoparrot is merely a parody system, in that it is using PC games that are already playable in Wine as a launch point to start the games. Of course, PC games are sometimes developed much differently to arcade games, (besides pure ports) and treating them as if they are fully-fledged arcade games will certainly draw the ire of arcade game purists. As such, those familiar with the layout and makeup of a true arcade game can easily spot the difference, but most users, due to the liking of the system, and their stance against the concept of Teknoparrot‘s exclusivity, along with its difficulty to setup and it’s monopolistic “pay-for-play” structure, simply do not care about the distinction, and continue to use it all the same. As such, playing PC based arcade developed games in this manner has its limitations, but also its advantages, as many games released for PC, based off their arcade original, generally have built in improvements and updates that make the game better than it's often older arcade counterpart; and in this very real sense, Batoparrot can even be seen as superior to Teknoparrot. 
			
As for the parody system's limitations, it is well-known, that since the system uses PC counterparts of arcade games playable by Teknoparrot, the system will only have as many titles that are released and playable on PC, of which many Teknoparrot playable games are still exclusive to their modern arcade systems without any current PC release. However, over time, many of the arcade games playable by Teknoparrot are slowly getting a PC counterpart and release, and as such, they can be added to Batoparrot and playable through Wine in Batocera. Although initially a parody concept, Batoparrot continues to do very well. As it is now, Batoparrot stands as a form of protest against the closed-source, monopolistic and profit-driven nature of Teknoparrot, and continues to be used by the Linux and Batocera communities. The person behind the concept of the parody system, Sleyk, vows to keep adding games to its repertoire, solely based on principle, keeping a strict adherence to only adding modern arcade games playable by Teknoparrot that are released for PC, until Teknoparrot gets an official Linux based UI, and gives up its pay-for-play profit-driven structure.
	</text>
			<text lang="pl">Początkowo Batoparrot został pomyślany jako system parodiujący, mający na celu wyśmiewanie się z ekskluzywności i monopolistycznych ideałów Teknoparrot (nowoczesnego emulatora gier zręcznościowych opartego na systemie Windows). Początkowo Batoparrot był prostym pomysłem na przeniesienie kilku grywalnych gier Teknoparrot do Batocery, używając odpowiednika gry zręcznościowej na PC jako substytutu odpowiednika gry zręcznościowej w systemie Linux. Chodzi o to, że wszystkie gry Teknoparrot, które mają swój odpowiednik na PC, zostaną dodane do Batoparrot i będą w pełni grywalne w Batocera. Pod tym względem Batoparrot jest jedynie parodią systemu, ponieważ wykorzystuje gry PC, które są już grywalne w Wine, jako punkt startowy do uruchamiania gier. Oczywiście, gry na PC są czasami tworzone znacznie inaczej niż gry zręcznościowe (poza czystymi portami), a traktowanie ich tak, jakby były pełnoprawnymi grami zręcznościowymi, z pewnością wywoła gniew purystów gier zręcznościowych. W związku z tym osoby zaznajomione z układem i składem prawdziwej gry zręcznościowej mogą łatwo dostrzec różnicę, ale większość użytkowników, ze względu na sympatię do systemu i ich stanowisko przeciwko koncepcji wyłączności Teknoparrot, wraz z jego trudnościami w konfiguracji i monopolistyczną strukturą "pay-for-play", po prostu nie dba o to rozróżnienie i nadal używa go tak samo. W związku z tym granie w gry zręcznościowe na PC w ten sposób ma swoje ograniczenia, ale także zalety, ponieważ wiele gier wydanych na PC, opartych na ich zręcznościowym oryginale, zazwyczaj ma wbudowane ulepszenia i aktualizacje, które sprawiają, że gra jest lepsza niż jej często starszy odpowiednik zręcznościowy; i w tym bardzo realnym sensie Batoparrot może być nawet postrzegany jako lepszy od Teknoparrot. 
			
Jeśli chodzi o ograniczenia systemu parodii, dobrze wiadomo, że ponieważ system wykorzystuje pecetowe odpowiedniki gier zręcznościowych, w które można grać za pomocą Teknoparrot, system będzie miał tylko tyle tytułów, które zostały wydane i grywalne na PC, z których wiele gier Teknoparrot jest nadal dostępnych wyłącznie na ich nowoczesnych systemach zręcznościowych bez żadnych aktualnych wydań na PC. Jednak z biegiem czasu wiele gier zręcznościowych, w które można grać w Teknoparrot, powoli zyskuje odpowiedniki i wydania na PC, dzięki czemu można je dodać do Batoparrot i grać w nie za pośrednictwem Wine w Batocera. Choć początkowo był to pomysł na parodię, Batoparrot nadal radzi sobie bardzo dobrze. W obecnej formie Batoparrot jest formą protestu przeciwko zamkniętemu źródłu, monopolistycznej i nastawionej na zysk naturze Teknoparrot i nadal jest używany przez społeczności Linuksa i Batocera. Osoba stojąca za koncepcją systemu parodii, Sleyk, przysięga dodawać gry do swojego repertuaru, wyłącznie w oparciu o zasady, ściśle przestrzegając dodawania tylko nowoczesnych gier zręcznościowych, w które można grać za pomocą Teknoparrot, które zostały wydane na PC, dopóki Teknoparrot nie otrzyma oficjalnego interfejsu użytkownika opartego na systemie Linux i nie zrezygnuje ze swojej struktury opartej na zyskach.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Batoparrot изначально задумывался как пародийная система, призванная высмеять эксклюзивность и долгое время считавшиеся монополистическими идеалы Teknoparrot (эмулятора современных аркадных игр на базе Windows). Batoparrot начинался как простая идея привнести несколько игр Teknoparrot в Batocera, используя PC-аналог аркадной игры как замену ее аркадного аналога в Linux. Идея заключается в том, что все игры Teknoparrot, имеющие аналог на ПК, будут добавлены в Batoparrot и полностью доступны для игры в Batocera. В этом отношении Batoparrot является лишь пародийной системой, поскольку использует PC-игры, которые уже воспроизводятся в Wine, в качестве точки запуска игр. Конечно, игры для ПК иногда разрабатываются совсем не так, как аркадные игры (помимо чистых портов), и отношение к ним как к полноценным аркадным играм, безусловно, вызовет гнев пуристов аркадных игр. Те, кто знаком с устройством и структурой настоящей аркадной игры, легко заметят разницу, но большинство пользователей, в силу симпатий к системе и своей позиции против эксклюзивности "Текнопаррота", сложности его настройки и монопольной структуры "плати за игру", просто не обращают внимания на это различие и продолжают пользоваться им, как и прежде. Таким образом, игра на ПК в аркадные игры имеет не только свои ограничения, но и преимущества, поскольку многие игры, выпущенные для ПК на основе аркадного оригинала, как правило, имеют встроенные улучшения и обновления, которые делают игру лучше, чем ее зачастую более старый аркадный аналог, и в этом смысле Batoparrot можно считать даже лучше Teknoparrot. 
			
Что касается ограничений пародийной системы, то, как известно, поскольку система использует PC-аналоги аркадных игр, воспроизводимых Teknoparrot, в ней будет только то количество игр, которое выпущено и воспроизводится на PC, а многие игры, воспроизводимые Teknoparrot, по-прежнему являются эксклюзивом для современных аркадных систем без какого-либо текущего PC-релиза. Однако со временем многие аркадные игры, воспроизводимые в Teknoparrot, постепенно обретают аналог на ПК, и их можно добавить в Batoparrot и играть в них через Wine in Batocera. Несмотря на то, что изначально Batoparrot был пародийным проектом, он продолжает успешно развиваться. В своем нынешнем виде Batoparrot является формой протеста против закрытого исходного кода, монополистической и ориентированной на прибыль природы Teknoparrot и продолжает использоваться сообществами Linux и Batocera. Человек, стоящий за концепцией пародийной системы, Sleyk, клянется продолжать пополнять ее репертуар играми, руководствуясь исключительно принципиальными соображениями, строго придерживаясь принципа добавления только современных аркадных игр, воспроизводимых Teknoparrot и выпущенных для ПК, пока Teknoparrot не получит официальный пользовательский интерфейс на базе Linux и не откажется от своей структуры, ориентированной на получение прибыли по принципу pay-for-play.</text>
			<text lang="es">Concebido inicialmente como un sistema paródico que pretende burlarse de la exclusividad y de los ideales monopolísticos de Teknoparrot (un emulador de juegos arcade moderno basado en Windows), Batoparrot comenzó como una simple idea para llevar a Batocera algunos juegos jugables de Teknoparrot, utilizando la contrapartida para PC del juego arcade como sustituto de la contrapartida arcade del juego en Linux. La idea es que cualquier juego de Teknoparrot que tenga una contrapartida para PC se añada a Batoparrot y sea totalmente jugable en Batocera. En este sentido, Batoparrot no es más que un sistema paródico, en el sentido de que utiliza juegos de PC que ya son jugables en Wine como punto de partida para iniciar los juegos. Por supuesto, los juegos de PC a veces se desarrollan de forma muy diferente a los juegos arcade, (aparte de los puros ports) y tratarlos como si fueran juegos arcade en toda regla seguramente provocará la ira de los puristas de los juegos arcade. Así, aquellos familiarizados con el diseño y la composición de un verdadero juego arcade pueden notar fácilmente la diferencia, pero la mayoría de los usuarios, debido al gusto por el sistema, y su postura en contra del concepto de exclusividad de Teknoparrot, junto con su dificultad para configurarlo y su estructura monopolística de "pago por jugar", simplemente no se preocupan por la distinción, y continúan usándolo igualmente. Por tanto, jugar a juegos arcade desarrollados para PC de esta forma tiene sus limitaciones, pero también sus ventajas, ya que muchos juegos lanzados para PC, basados en su original arcade, suelen incorporar mejoras y actualizaciones que hacen que el juego sea mejor que su homólogo arcade, a menudo más antiguo; y en este sentido muy real, Batoparrot puede incluso considerarse superior a Teknoparrot. 
			
En cuanto a las limitaciones del sistema de parodia, es bien sabido que, dado que el sistema utiliza homólogos para PC de juegos arcade jugables por Teknoparrot, el sistema sólo tendrá tantos títulos como hayan sido lanzados y sean jugables en PC, de los cuales muchos juegos jugables por Teknoparrot siguen siendo exclusivos de sus sistemas arcade modernos sin ningún lanzamiento actual para PC. Sin embargo, con el tiempo, muchos de los juegos arcade jugables por Teknoparrot están consiguiendo poco a poco una contrapartida y lanzamiento en PC, y como tal, pueden ser añadidos a Batoparrot y jugables a través de Wine en Batocera. Aunque inicialmente era un concepto paródico, Batoparrot sigue funcionando muy bien. Tal y como es ahora, Batoparrot se erige como una forma de protesta contra la naturaleza monopolística, lucrativa y de código cerrado de Teknoparrot, y sigue siendo utilizado por las comunidades Linux y Batocera. La persona detrás del concepto del sistema de parodia, Sleyk, se compromete a seguir añadiendo juegos a su repertorio, basándose únicamente en principios, manteniendo una estricta adherencia a sólo añadir juegos arcade modernos jugables por Teknoparrot que sean lanzados para PC, hasta que Teknoparrot consiga una interfaz de usuario oficial basada en Linux, y renuncie a su estructura de pago por juego con ánimo de lucro.</text>
			<text lang="de">Batoparrot wurde ursprünglich als Parodie-System konzipiert, das sich über die Exklusivität und die lange geglaubten monopolistischen Ideale von Teknoparrot (einem Windows-basierten modernen Arcade-Spiel-Emulator) lustig machen sollte. Batoparrot begann als einfache Idee, ein paar spielbare Teknoparrot-Spiele zu Batocera zu bringen, indem das PC-Gegenstück des Arcade-Spiels als Ersatz für das Arcade-Gegenstück in Linux verwendet wurde. Die Idee ist, dass alle Teknoparrot-Spiele, die ein PC-Pendant haben, zu Batoparrot hinzugefügt werden und in Batocera vollständig spielbar sind. In dieser Hinsicht ist Batoparrot lediglich ein Parodie-System, da es PC-Spiele, die bereits in Wine spielbar sind, als Startpunkt verwendet, um die Spiele zu starten. Natürlich werden PC-Spiele manchmal ganz anders entwickelt als Arcade-Spiele (abgesehen von reinen Portierungen), und sie so zu behandeln, als wären sie vollwertige Arcade-Spiele, wird sicherlich den Zorn von Arcade-Spiel-Puristen auf sich ziehen. Diejenigen, die mit dem Layout und dem Aufbau eines echten Arcade-Spiels vertraut sind, können den Unterschied leicht erkennen, aber den meisten Benutzern ist der Unterschied aufgrund der Vorliebe für das System und ihrer Ablehnung des Konzepts der Teknoparrot-Exklusivität sowie der schwierigen Einrichtung und der monopolistischen "Pay-for-Play"-Struktur einfach egal, und sie nutzen es trotzdem weiter. Daher hat das Spielen von PC-basierten Arcade-Spielen auf diese Weise seine Grenzen, aber auch seine Vorteile, da viele Spiele, die für den PC veröffentlicht werden und auf ihrem Arcade-Original basieren, in der Regel Verbesserungen und Aktualisierungen eingebaut haben, die das Spiel besser machen als sein oft älteres Arcade-Gegenstück; und in diesem sehr realen Sinne kann Batoparrot sogar als besser als Teknoparrot angesehen werden. 
			
Was die Einschränkungen des Parodie-Systems angeht, so ist bekannt, dass das System nur so viele Titel enthält, wie auf dem PC spielbar sind, da das System PC-Pendants von Arcade-Spielen verwendet, die auf Teknoparrot spielbar sind, von denen viele spielbare Teknoparrot-Spiele immer noch exklusiv für ihre modernen Arcade-Systeme ohne aktuelle PC-Veröffentlichung sind. Im Laufe der Zeit werden jedoch viele der Arcade-Spiele, die auf Teknoparrot spielbar sind, nach und nach auf dem PC veröffentlicht und können so zu Batoparrot hinzugefügt und über Wine in Batocera spielbar gemacht werden. Obwohl es sich ursprünglich um ein parodistisches Konzept handelte, ist Batoparrot nach wie vor sehr erfolgreich. In seiner jetzigen Form stellt Batoparrot eine Form des Protests gegen die geschlossene, monopolistische und profitorientierte Natur von Teknoparrot dar und wird weiterhin von der Linux- und Batocera-Gemeinschaft genutzt. Die Person, die hinter dem Konzept des Parodie-Systems steht, Sleyk, schwört, weiterhin Spiele zu seinem Repertoire hinzuzufügen, allein aus Prinzip. Er hält sich strikt daran, nur moderne Arcade-Spiele hinzuzufügen, die mit Teknoparrot spielbar sind und für den PC veröffentlicht wurden, bis Teknoparrot eine offizielle Linux-basierte Benutzeroberfläche bekommt und seine Pay-for-Play-Profit-getriebene Struktur aufgibt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Conçu initialement comme un système parodique destiné à se moquer de l'exclusivité et des idéaux monopolistiques de Teknoparrot (un émulateur de jeux d'arcade moderne basé sur Windows), Batoparrot a commencé comme une simple idée d'apporter quelques jeux jouables sur Teknoparrot à Batocera, en utilisant la contrepartie PC du jeu d'arcade comme substitut de la contrepartie arcade du jeu sous Linux. L'idée est que tous les jeux Teknoparrot qui ont une contrepartie PC seront ajoutés à Batoparrot et entièrement jouables dans Batocera. À cet égard, Batoparrot n'est qu'un système parodique, dans la mesure où il utilise des jeux PC qui sont déjà jouables dans Wine comme point de départ pour démarrer les jeux. Bien sûr, les jeux PC sont parfois développés de manière très différente des jeux d'arcade (en dehors des ports purs) et les traiter comme s'ils étaient des jeux d'arcade à part entière attirera certainement l'ire des puristes des jeux d'arcade. En tant que tel, ceux qui sont familiers avec la disposition et la composition d'un vrai jeu d'arcade peuvent facilement faire la différence, mais la plupart des utilisateurs, en raison du goût du système et de leur position contre le concept d'exclusivité du Teknoparrot, ainsi que de sa difficulté d'installation et de sa structure monopolistique de "paiement pour jouer", ne se soucient tout simplement pas de la distinction, et continuent à l'utiliser tout de même. Ainsi, jouer à des jeux d'arcade sur PC de cette manière a ses limites, mais aussi ses avantages, car de nombreux jeux sortis sur PC, basés sur leur original d'arcade, ont généralement des améliorations et des mises à jour intégrées qui rendent le jeu meilleur que son homologue d'arcade souvent plus ancien ; et dans ce sens très réel, Batoparrot peut même être considéré comme supérieur à Teknoparrot. 
			
En ce qui concerne les limites du système de parodie, il est bien connu qu'étant donné que le système utilise les contreparties PC des jeux d'arcade jouables par le Teknoparrot, le système n'aura que le nombre de titres sortis et jouables sur PC, parmi lesquels de nombreux jeux jouables par le Teknoparrot sont encore exclusifs à leurs systèmes d'arcade modernes et ne sont pas encore sortis sur PC. Cependant, au fil du temps, de nombreux jeux d'arcade jouables sur Teknoparrot sortent peu à peu sur PC et peuvent donc être ajoutés à Batoparrot et jouables par le biais de Wine in Batocera. Bien qu'il s'agisse à l'origine d'un concept parodique, Batoparrot continue de très bien fonctionner. Aujourd'hui, Batoparrot est une forme de protestation contre la nature fermée, monopolistique et axée sur le profit de Teknoparrot, et continue d'être utilisé par les communautés Linux et Batocera. La personne à l'origine du concept du système de parodie, Sleyk, s'engage à continuer d'ajouter des jeux à son répertoire, uniquement par principe, en s'en tenant strictement à n'ajouter que des jeux d'arcade modernes jouables par Teknoparrot et sortis sur PC, jusqu'à ce que Teknoparrot obtienne une interface utilisateur officielle basée sur Linux et abandonne sa structure payante axée sur le profit.</text>
			<text lang="it">Concepito inizialmente come un sistema parodistico volto a prendere in giro l'esclusività e gli ideali monopolistici a lungo creduti di Teknoparrot (un emulatore di giochi arcade moderni basato su Windows), Batoparrot è nato come una semplice idea per portare alcuni giochi giocabili su Teknoparrot in Batocera, utilizzando la controparte per PC del gioco arcade come sostituto della controparte arcade del gioco in Linux. L'idea è che tutti i giochi Teknoparrot che hanno una controparte per PC saranno aggiunti a Batoparrot e completamente giocabili in Batocera. A questo proposito, Batoparrot è semplicemente un sistema parodistico, in quanto utilizza giochi per PC già giocabili in Wine come punto di lancio per avviare i giochi. Naturalmente, i giochi per PC sono talvolta sviluppati in modo molto diverso dai giochi arcade (a parte i puri porting) e trattarli come se fossero giochi arcade a tutti gli effetti attirerà sicuramente le ire dei puristi dei giochi arcade. Chi ha familiarità con il layout e la struttura di un vero gioco arcade può facilmente notare la differenza, ma la maggior parte degli utenti, a causa della simpatia del sistema e della loro posizione contro il concetto di esclusività di Teknoparrot, insieme alla sua difficoltà di configurazione e alla sua struttura monopolistica "pay-for-play", semplicemente non si preoccupa della distinzione e continua a usarlo lo stesso. Per questo motivo, giocare ai giochi arcade per PC in questo modo ha i suoi limiti, ma anche i suoi vantaggi: molti giochi rilasciati per PC, basati sull'originale arcade, hanno in genere miglioramenti e aggiornamenti che rendono il gioco migliore rispetto alla controparte arcade, spesso più vecchia; in questo senso, Batoparrot può essere considerato superiore a Teknoparrot. 
			
Per quanto riguarda le limitazioni del sistema di parodia, è noto che, poiché il sistema utilizza le controparti per PC dei giochi arcade giocabili da Teknoparrot, il sistema avrà solo altrettanti titoli rilasciati e giocabili su PC, di cui molti giochi giocabili da Teknoparrot sono ancora un'esclusiva dei loro moderni sistemi arcade senza alcuna versione attuale per PC. Tuttavia, nel corso del tempo, molti dei giochi arcade giocabili su Teknoparrot stanno lentamente ottenendo una controparte e un rilascio su PC e, pertanto, possono essere aggiunti a Batoparrot e giocabili attraverso Wine in Batocera. Anche se inizialmente si trattava di una parodia, Batoparrot continua ad avere successo. Così com'è ora, Batoparrot rappresenta una forma di protesta contro la natura closed-source, monopolistica e orientata al profitto di Teknoparrot e continua a essere utilizzato dalle comunità Linux e Batocera. La persona che ha ideato il sistema parodistico, Sleyk, promette di continuare ad aggiungere giochi al suo repertorio, unicamente sulla base di principi, attenendosi rigorosamente all'aggiunta di soli giochi arcade moderni giocabili da Teknoparrot e rilasciati per PC, fino a quando Teknoparrot non otterrà un'interfaccia utente ufficiale basata su Linux e rinuncerà alla sua struttura a pagamento orientata al profitto.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>