<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.49 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.49 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1981</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Commodore</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>VIC-20</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Commodore VIC-20 (known as the VC-20 in Germany and the VIC-1001 in Japan) is an 8-bit home computer that was sold by Commodore Business Machines. The VIC-20 was announced in 1980, roughly three years after Commodore's first personal computer, the PET. The VIC-20 was the first computer of any description to sell one million units. It was described as "one of the first anti-spectatorial, non-esoteric computers by design...no longer relegated to hobbyist/enthusiasts or those with money, the computer Commodore developed was the computer of the future.

The VIC-20 was called VC-20 in Germany because the pronunciation of VIC with a German accent sounds like the German expletives "fick" or "wichsen". The term VC was marketed as though it was an abbreviation of VolksComputer ("people's computer," similar to Volkswagen and Volksempfänger).</text>
			<text lang="pl">Commodore VIC-20 (w Niemczech VC20, w Japonii VIC-1001) – komputer domowy produkowany przez firmę Commodore, posiadający 5 kB pamięci RAM i procesor MOS 6502. Jest pierwszym komputerem domowym, którego liczba sprzedanych sztuk wyniosła ponad milion egzemplarzy (w sumie sprzedano ponad 2,5 miliona jednostek).

VIC-20 wyposażony był w 8-bitowy mikroprocesor MOS Technology 6502, znany z mikrokomputera Commodore PET. Układ grafiki, MOS VIC, udostępniał tryb tekstowy: 22 kolumny x 23 wiersze, a także tryb graficzny – w rozdzielczości 176x184 pikseli z 3 bitami na piksel. Obudowa komputera była później używana w Commodore 64 i Commodore 16. VIC-20 został wprowadzony do sprzedaży na początku 1981, po premierze na Pokazie Elektroniki Komputerowej w czerwcu 1980.</text>
			<text lang="ru">8-битный домашний компьютер, выпускавшийся компанией Commodore Business Machines. VIC-20 был анонсирован в июне 1980, примерно через три года после выпуска Commodore PET. Это первый в мире компьютер, продажи которого превысили миллион экземпляров. Всего было реализовано более 2,5 миллионов компьютеров этой модели. В ходе конкурентной борьбы цена упала с $299,95 до $55 (ниже себестоимости), но это с лихвой окупалось за счёт продаж программного обеспечения и аксессуаров.

Commodore VIC-20 был оснащён 8-разрядным микропроцессором CSG/MOS 6502 с тактовой частотой 1,0227 МГц. В качестве видеоконтроллера и звукогенератора использовалась микросхема VIC (Video Interface Chip 6560/6561). VIC позволял отображать цветную графику с разрешением 176×184 пикселей или 23 строчки по 22 символа и воспроизводить трёхголосный звук в диапазоне трёх октав. Объём ОЗУ составлял 5,5 КБ, из которых пользователю было доступно 3583 байт, а 2 КБ использовалось для системных нужд, в частности для отображения видео. Выпускались картриджи для расширения памяти объёмом от 3 до 64 КБ. В 16 КБ ПЗУ был прошит интерпретатор Бейсика и KERNAL (операционная система низкого уровня).

К VIC-20 можно было подключать джойстик, принтер VIC 1515, VIC Modem и другие периферийные устройства. В качестве внешней памяти использовались картриджи, магнитофонные компакт-кассеты с фирменным накопителем Commodore Datasette или дисковод Commodore 1540 для дискет размером 5¼" объёмом около 170 КБ.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Commodore VIC-20 (conocido como VC-20 en Alemania y VIC-1001 en Japón) es un ordenador doméstico de 8 bits comercializado por Commodore Business Machines. El VIC-20 fue anunciado en 1980, aproximadamente tres años después del primer ordenador personal de Commodore, el PET. El VIC-20 fue el primer ordenador de cualquier tipo en vender un millón de unidades. Fue descrito como "uno de los primeros ordenadores antiespectadores, no esotéricos por diseño... ya no relegado a los aficionados/entusiastas o a los que tienen dinero, el ordenador desarrollado por Commodore era el ordenador del futuro".

El VIC-20 se llamó VC-20 en Alemania porque la pronunciación de VIC con acento alemán suena como los improperios alemanes "fick" o "wichsen". El término VC se comercializó como si fuera una abreviatura de VolksComputer ("ordenador del pueblo", similar a Volkswagen y Volksempfänger).</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Commodore VIC-20 (in Deutschland als VC-20 und in Japan als VIC-1001 bekannt) ist ein 8-Bit-Heimcomputer, der von Commodore Business Machines verkauft wurde. Der VIC-20 wurde 1980 angekündigt, etwa drei Jahre nach dem ersten Personal Computer von Commodore, dem PET. Der VIC-20 war der erste Computer, von dem eine Million Stück verkauft wurden. Er wurde als "einer der ersten antispektakulären, nicht-esoterischen Computer beschrieben... der von Commodore entwickelte Computer war der Computer der Zukunft und nicht mehr nur etwas für Hobbyisten/Enthusiasten oder Leute mit Geld.

Der VIC-20 wurde in Deutschland VC-20 genannt, weil die Aussprache von VIC mit deutschem Akzent wie die deutschen Schimpfwörter "fick" oder "wichsen" klingt. Der Begriff VC wurde so vermarktet, als sei er eine Abkürzung für VolksComputer (ähnlich wie Volkswagen und Volksempfänger).</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Commodore VIC-20 (connu sous le nom de VC-20 en Allemagne et de VIC-1001 au Japon) est un ordinateur domestique 8 bits vendu par Commodore Business Machines. Le VIC-20 a été annoncé en 1980, environ trois ans après le premier ordinateur personnel de Commodore, le PET. Le VIC-20 a été le premier ordinateur, toutes catégories confondues, à se vendre à un million d'exemplaires. Il a été décrit comme "l'un des premiers ordinateurs anti-spectateurs, non ésotériques de par sa conception... n'étant plus relégué aux amateurs/enthousiastes ou à ceux qui ont de l'argent, l'ordinateur développé par Commodore était l'ordinateur de l'avenir".

Le VIC-20 était appelé VC-20 en Allemagne parce que la prononciation de VIC avec un accent allemand ressemble aux jurons allemands "fick" ou "wichsen". Le terme VC a été commercialisé comme s'il s'agissait d'une abréviation de VolksComputer ("ordinateur du peuple", similaire à Volkswagen et Volksempfänger).</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Commodore VIC-20 (noto come VC-20 in Germania e VIC-1001 in Giappone) è stato un home computer a 8 bit venduto da Commodore Business Machines. Il VIC-20 fu annunciato nel 1980, circa tre anni dopo il primo personal computer di Commodore, il PET. Il VIC-20 è stato il primo computer di qualsiasi tipo a vendere un milione di unità. È stato descritto come "uno dei primi computer anti-speculatori, non esoterici per concezione... non più relegato agli hobbisti/entusiasti o a chi ha soldi, il computer sviluppato da Commodore era il computer del futuro".

Il VIC-20 era chiamato VC-20 in Germania perché la pronuncia di VIC con accento tedesco assomiglia alle imprecazioni tedesche "fick" o "wichsen". Il termine VC fu commercializzato come se fosse un'abbreviazione di VolksComputer ("computer del popolo", simile a Volkswagen e Volksempfänger).</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
