<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.518 0.33</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.238 0.33" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1982</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>Commodore
64</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.40</pos>
			<text>The Commodore 64, also known as the C64 or the CBM 64, is an 8-bit home computer introduced in January 1982 by Commodore International (first shown at the Consumer Electronics Show, in Las Vegas, January 7–10, 1982). It has been listed in the Guinness World Records as the highest-selling single computer model of all time, with independent estimates placing the number sold between 12.5 and 17 million units. Volume production started in early 1982, marketing in August for US$595 (equivalent to $1,576 in 2019). Preceded by the Commodore VIC-20 and Commodore PET, the C64 took its name from its 64 kilobytes (65,536 bytes) of RAM. With support for multicolor sprites and a custom chip for waveform generation, the C64 could create superior visuals and audio compared to systems without such custom hardware.

The C64 dominated the low-end computer market (except in the UK) for most of the 1980s. For a substantial period (1983–1986), the C64 had between 30% and 40% share of the US market and two million units sold per year, outselling IBM PC compatibles, Apple computers, and the Atari 8-bit family of computers. Sam Tramiel, a later Atari president and the son of Commodore's founder, said in a 1989 interview, "When I was at Commodore we were building 400,000 C64s a month for a couple of years." In the UK market, the C64 faced competition from the BBC Micro and the ZX Spectrum, but the C64 was still the second most popular computer in the UK after the ZX Spectrum.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Commodore 64 est un ordinateur personnel conçu par Commodore Business Machines Inc. en 1982, sous l'égide de Jack Tramiel. Il fut la première machine vendue à plusieurs millions d'exemplaires (de 17 à 25 millions selon les estimations), et il reste le modèle d'ordinateur personnel le plus vendu à ce jour, selon le Livre Guinness des records.

En 2011, une société basée en Floride a mis en vente un « Commodore 64 » reprenant le boîtier d'origine et compatible PC.

En 2017, Retro Games Ltd. annonce une réédition du Commodore 64, « The C64 Mini », une version miniaturisée de l'ordinateur personnel, dont la distribution doit être assurée par Koch Media. Celle-ci est basée sur le processeur Allwinner A20, comporte 256 Mo de RAM, 256 Mo de flash pour le système et, pour la connectique, un port HDMI, ainsi 2 ports USB, le clavier intégré étant ici uniquement représentatif, mais ne fonctionnant pas.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Домашний компьютер с 64 КБ оперативной памяти. Выпущен на рынок компанией Commodore International в августе 1982 года по цене 595 долларов. За всё время выпуска Commodore 64 (1982—1994) было продано более 15 млн компьютеров. Согласно книге рекордов Гиннесса, Commodore 64 стал лидером продаж среди моделей компьютеров.

C64 можно было подключить непосредственно к телевизору и играть в игры, в той же манере, как это делалось с игровыми приставками, такими как Atari 2600. В отличие от других компьютеров, распространявшихся только через авторизованных дилеров, Commodore также нацеливался на крупные магазины и магазины игрушек. Считается, что ценовая политика Commodore 64 стала одной из основных причин сокращения рынка игровых приставок в 1983 году.

Для Commodore 64 было создано порядка 10 тыс. различных программ, включая средства разработки, офисные приложения и игры.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>