<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2021</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Cannonball</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>CannonBall is a souped up game engine for the OutRun arcade game. The original 68000 and Z80 assembler code has been rewritten in C++. This makes it possible to make improvements suitable for modern platforms, such as higher frame rate at 60 FPS, higher resolution sprite scaling, wide screen support, new game modes and so on.

It requires the original ROMs, as these contain elements including the graphics and audio data.</text>
			<text lang="pl">CannonBall to zmodernizowany silnik gry dla gry zręcznościowej OutRun. Oryginalny kod asemblera 68000 i Z80 został przepisany w C++. Umożliwia to wprowadzenie ulepszeń odpowiednich dla nowoczesnych platform, takich jak wyższa częstotliwość odświeżania 60 FPS, skalowanie sprite'ów w wyższej rozdzielczości, obsługa szerokiego ekranu, nowe tryby gry itd.

Wymaga ona oryginalnych pamięci ROM, ponieważ zawierają one elementy, w tym grafikę i dźwięk.</text>
			<text lang="ru">CannonBall — усовершенствованный игровой движок для аркадной игры OutRun. Исходный ассемблерный код 68000 и Z80 был переписан на C++. Это позволяет вносить улучшения, подходящие для современных платформ, включая более высокую частоту кадров и поддержку широкоэкранного режима. Для этого требуются оригинальные ромы, поскольку они содержат элементы, включая графику и аудиоданные.</text>
			<text lang="es">CannonBall es un motor de juego mejorado para el juego arcade OutRun. El código ensamblador original de 68000 y Z80 ha sido reescrito en C++. Esto hace posible realizar mejoras adecuadas para las plataformas modernas, como una mayor velocidad de fotogramas a 60 FPS, un escalado de sprites de mayor resolución, soporte para pantallas anchas, nuevos modos de juego, etc.

Requiere las ROM originales, ya que éstas contienen elementos como los datos gráficos y de audio.</text>
			<text lang="de">CannonBall ist eine aufgemotzte Spiel-Engine für das OutRun Arcade-Spiel. Der ursprüngliche 68000- und Z80-Assembler-Code wurde in C++ umgeschrieben. Dies ermöglicht Verbesserungen, die für moderne Plattformen geeignet sind, wie z.B. eine höhere Bildwiederholrate von 60 FPS, eine höhere Skalierung der Sprites, Unterstützung für Breitbildschirme, neue Spielmodi und so weiter.

Es werden die Original-ROMs benötigt, da diese Elemente einschließlich der Grafik- und Audiodaten enthalten.</text>
			<text lang="fr">CannonBall est un moteur de jeu amélioré pour le jeu d'arcade OutRun. Le code assembleur 68000 et Z80 d'origine a été réécrit en C++. Cela permet d'apporter des améliorations adaptées aux plates-formes modernes, telles qu'une fréquence d'images plus élevée (60 FPS), une meilleure résolution des sprites, la prise en charge des écrans larges, de nouveaux modes de jeu, etc.

Il nécessite les ROMs d'origine, qui contiennent des éléments tels que les données graphiques et audio.</text>
			<text lang="it">CannonBall è un motore di gioco potenziato per il gioco arcade OutRun. Il codice assembler originale per 68000 e Z80 è stato riscritto in C++. In questo modo è stato possibile apportare miglioramenti adatti alle piattaforme moderne, come una frequenza di fotogrammi più elevata a 60 FPS, la scalatura degli sprite a risoluzione più alta, il supporto per lo schermo largo, nuove modalità di gioco e così via.

Richiede le ROM originali, che contengono elementi come i dati grafici e audio.</text>
			<text lang="pt">CannonBall é um motor de jogo modernizado para o jogo de arcade OutRun. O código original em assembly 68000 e Z80 foi reescrito em C++. Isso permite a introdução de melhorias adequadas para plataformas modernas, como taxa de atualização mais alta de 60 FPS, dimensionamento de sprites em alta resolução, suporte para tela panorâmica, novos modos de jogo, etc.

Ela exige as ROMs originais, pois elas contêm elementos, incluindo gráficos e áudio.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
