<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.26</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.325</pos>
			<maxSize>0.254</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.325" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.26</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.325</pos>
			<maxSize>0.244</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.325" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1987</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Mattel</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Captain Power</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Saturday morning TV program Captain Power and the Soldiers of the Future, which aired from 1987-88, was a science fiction/action television series that ran for 22 episodes in Canadian/American syndication. A toy line was also produced by Mattel, and during each episode there was a segment that included visual and audio material which interacted with the toys.

The first interactive toy and game for the series was a toy XT-7 jet with a video cassette. There were three tapes in all: &quot;Future Force Training,&quot; &quot;Bio-Dread Strike Mission,&quot; and &quot;Raid On Volcania.&quot; The tapes had openings and closings in live action with the cast of the television show. The actual mission itself was animated and took place in the jet cockpit from the first-person point of view of the pilot/player.
The XT-7 also could interact with the live-action television broadcast in the same manner. Since the &quot;game&quot; was only a VHS tape, the missions played out the same way every time.

Other interactive objects in this series were the &quot;Phantom Stryker&quot; Bio-Dread ship, the &quot;Interlocker Throne&quot; for Lord Dread, which consisted of a stationary tank on a tripod and an optional target viewer that could be taken on and off, and the &quot;Power On&quot; platform in which one could plug the Captain Power figure. Whenever the transformation was triggered on the television screen or the base was fired at by one of the other vehicles, the toy would immediately trigger the &quot;Power On&quot; sequence causing the chest of the figure to glow.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il programma televisivo del sabato mattina Captain Power and the Soldiers of the Future, andato in onda nel 1987-88, era una serie televisiva di fantascienza/azione composta da 22 episodi in syndication canadese/americana. Una linea di giocattoli è stata prodotta dalla Mattel e durante ogni episodio c'era un segmento che includeva materiale visivo e audio che interagiva con i giocattoli.

Il primo giocattolo e gioco interattivo della serie fu un jet XT-7 giocattolo con una videocassetta. C'erano tre cassette in tutto: &quot;Addestramento della Forza Futura&quot;, &quot;Missione d'attacco Bio-Dread&quot; e &quot;Raid su Volcania&quot;. Le cassette avevano aperture e chiusure in live action con il cast della serie televisiva. La missione vera e propria era animata e si svolgeva nella cabina di pilotaggio del jet dal punto di vista del pilota/giocatore in prima persona.
L'XT-7 poteva interagire allo stesso modo con la trasmissione televisiva in diretta. Poiché il &quot;gioco&quot; era solo un nastro VHS, le missioni si svolgevano sempre allo stesso modo.

Altri oggetti interattivi di questa serie erano la nave Bio-Dread &quot;Phantom Stryker&quot;, il &quot;Trono Interlocker&quot; per Lord Dread, che consisteva in un serbatoio fisso su un treppiede e in un visore opzionale per il bersaglio che poteva essere acceso e spento, e la piattaforma &quot;Power On&quot; in cui si poteva inserire la figura di Captain Power. Ogni volta che la trasformazione veniva attivata sullo schermo televisivo o la base veniva sparata da uno degli altri veicoli, il giocattolo attivava immediatamente la sequenza di &quot;accensione&quot;, facendo brillare il petto della figura.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'émission télévisée du samedi matin Captain Power and the Soldiers of the Future, diffusée de 1987 à 1988, était une série télévisée de science-fiction et d'action qui a duré 22 épisodes en syndication canadienne/américaine. Une ligne de jouets a également été produite par Mattel, et chaque épisode comportait un segment avec du matériel visuel et audio qui interagissait avec les jouets.

Le premier jouet et jeu interactif de la série était un jet XT-7 avec une cassette vidéo. Il y avait trois cassettes en tout : &quot;Future Force Training&quot;, &quot;Bio-Dread Strike Mission&quot; et &quot;Raid On Volcania&quot;. Les cassettes comportaient des ouvertures et des fermetures en action réelle avec les acteurs de l'émission de télévision. La mission elle-même était animée et se déroulait dans le cockpit de l'avion, du point de vue du pilote/joueur à la première personne.
Le XT-7 pouvait également interagir avec l'émission télévisée en direct de la même manière. Comme le &quot;jeu&quot; n'était qu'une cassette VHS, les missions se déroulaient toujours de la même manière.

Les autres objets interactifs de cette série étaient le vaisseau Bio-Dread &quot;Phantom Stryker&quot;, le &quot;Interlocker Throne&quot; pour Lord Dread, qui se composait d'un réservoir stationnaire sur un trépied et d'une visionneuse de cible optionnelle qui pouvait être mise en place et retirée, et la plate-forme &quot;Power On&quot; dans laquelle on pouvait brancher la figurine de Captain Power. Chaque fois que la transformation était déclenchée sur l'écran de télévision ou que la base était attaquée par l'un des autres véhicules, le jouet déclenchait immédiatement la séquence &quot;Power On&quot;, qui faisait briller la poitrine de la figurine.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Samstagmorgen-Fernsehsendung Captain Power and the Soldiers of the Future, die von 1987-88 ausgestrahlt wurde, war eine Science-Fiction/Action-Fernsehserie, die 22 Episoden lang in kanadischer/amerikanischer Syndication lief. Von Mattel wurde auch eine Spielzeugserie produziert, und in jeder Folge gab es ein Segment mit Bild- und Tonmaterial, das mit den Spielzeugen interagierte.

Das erste interaktive Spielzeug und Spiel für die Serie war ein Spielzeug-XT-7-Jet mit einer Videokassette. Insgesamt gab es drei Kassetten: &quot;Future Force Training&quot;, &quot;Bio-Dread Strike Mission&quot; und &quot;Raid On Volcania&quot;. Die Kassetten enthielten Eröffnungs- und Schlussszenen in Live-Action mit den Darstellern der Fernsehserie. Die eigentliche Mission selbst war animiert und fand im Cockpit des Jets aus der Ich-Perspektive des Piloten/Spielers statt.
Die XT-7 konnte auf die gleiche Weise mit der Live-Action-Fernsehsendung interagieren. Da es sich bei dem &quot;Spiel&quot; nur um eine VHS-Kassette handelte, liefen die Missionen jedes Mal auf die gleiche Weise ab.

Weitere interaktive Objekte in dieser Serie waren das Bio-Dread-Schiff &quot;Phantom Stryker&quot;, der &quot;Interlocker-Thron&quot; für Lord Dread, der aus einem stationären Panzer auf einem Stativ und einem optionalen Zielsucher bestand, der an- und abgenommen werden konnte, und die &quot;Power On&quot;-Plattform, in die man die Captain Power-Figur einstecken konnte. Immer wenn die Verwandlung auf dem Fernsehbildschirm ausgelöst oder die Basis von einem der anderen Fahrzeuge beschossen wurde, löste das Spielzeug sofort die &quot;Power On&quot;-Sequenz aus, wodurch die Brust der Figur aufleuchtete.</text>
			<text lang="es">El programa de televisión de los sábados por la mañana Capitán Power y los Soldados del Futuro, emitido entre 1987 y 1988, fue una serie de televisión de ciencia ficción y acción que se emitió durante 22 episodios en sindicación canadiense/estadounidense. Mattel también produjo una línea de juguetes, y durante cada episodio había un segmento que incluía material visual y sonoro que interactuaba con los juguetes.

El primer juguete y juego interactivo de la serie fue un jet XT-7 de juguete con una cinta de vídeo. Había tres cintas en total: &quot;Entrenamiento de la Fuerza Futura&quot;, &quot;Misión de ataque Bio-Dread&quot; e &quot;Incursión en Volcania&quot;. Las cintas tenían aperturas y cierres en acción real con el reparto de la serie de televisión. La misión en sí estaba animada y se desarrollaba en la cabina del jet desde el punto de vista en primera persona del piloto/jugador.
El XT-7 también podía interactuar de la misma manera con la emisión de televisión en directo. Como el &quot;juego&quot; era sólo una cinta VHS, las misiones se desarrollaban siempre de la misma manera.

Otros objetos interactivos de esta serie eran la nave Bio-Dread &quot;Phantom Stryker&quot;, el &quot;Interlocker Throne&quot; para Lord Dread, que consistía en un tanque estacionario sobre un trípode y un visor de objetivos opcional que se podía poner y quitar, y la plataforma &quot;Power On&quot; en la que se podía enchufar la figura del Capitán Power. Cada vez que se activaba la transformación en la pantalla de televisión o uno de los otros vehículos disparaba contra la base, el juguete activaba inmediatamente la secuencia &quot;Power On&quot;, haciendo que el pecho de la figura brillara.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Субботняя утренняя телепередача &quot;Капитан Пауэр и солдаты будущего&quot;, выходившая в эфир в 1987-88 годах, была научно-фантастическим/боевым телесериалом, который длился 22 эпизода в канадско-американской синдикации. Компания Mattel также выпускала линию игрушек, и в каждом эпизоде был сегмент, включающий визуальные и аудиоматериалы, которые взаимодействовали с игрушками.

Первой интерактивной игрушкой и игрой для сериала стал игрушечный самолет XT-7 с видеокассетой. Всего было три кассеты: &quot;Future Force Training&quot;, &quot;Bio-Dread Strike Mission&quot; и &quot;Raid On Volcania&quot;. Кассеты открывались и закрывались живым действием с участием актеров телешоу. Сама миссия была анимирована и проходила в кабине самолета с точки зрения пилота/игрока от первого лица.
XT-7 также мог взаимодействовать с телевизионной трансляцией в реальном времени. Поскольку &quot;игра&quot; была всего лишь кассетой VHS, миссии каждый раз проходили одинаково.

Другими интерактивными объектами в этой серии были корабль Био-Дреда &quot;Фантом Страйкер&quot;, &quot;Трон Интерлокера&quot; для Лорда Дреда, состоящий из стационарного танка на треноге и дополнительного устройства для наблюдения за мишенями, которое можно было снимать и снимать, и платформа &quot;Power On&quot;, в которую можно было вставить фигурку Капитана Пауэра. Каждый раз, когда на экране телевизора происходила трансформация или база подвергалась обстрелу со стороны одного из других транспортных средств, игрушка немедленно включала режим &quot;Power On&quot;, в результате чего грудь фигурки светилась.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Program telewizyjny Captain Power and the Soldiers of the Future, emitowany w sobotni poranek w latach 1987-88, był serialem science fiction/akcji, który był emitowany przez 22 odcinki w kanadyjskiej/amerykańskiej dystrybucji. Linia zabawek została również wyprodukowana przez Mattel, a podczas każdego odcinka pojawiał się segment zawierający materiały wizualne i dźwiękowe, które wchodziły w interakcję z zabawkami.

Pierwszą interaktywną zabawką i grą w serialu był zabawkowy odrzutowiec XT-7 z kasetą wideo. W sumie były trzy kasety: &quot;Future Force Training&quot;, &quot;Bio-Dread Strike Mission&quot; i &quot;Raid On Volcania&quot;. Kasety miały otwarcia i zamknięcia w akcji na żywo z obsadą programu telewizyjnego. Sama misja była animowana i odbywała się w kokpicie odrzutowca z pierwszoosobowego punktu widzenia pilota/gracza.
XT-7 mógł również wchodzić w interakcje z transmisją telewizyjną na żywo w ten sam sposób. Ponieważ &quot;gra&quot; była tylko taśmą VHS, misje rozgrywały się za każdym razem w ten sam sposób.

Innymi interaktywnymi obiektami w tej serii były statek Bio-Dread &quot;Phantom Stryker&quot;, &quot;Tron Interlockera&quot; dla Lorda Dreada, który składał się ze stacjonarnego zbiornika na statywie i opcjonalnego celownika, który można było włączać i wyłączać, oraz platforma &quot;Power On&quot;, do której można było podłączyć figurkę Kapitana Powera. Za każdym razem, gdy transformacja została uruchomiona na ekranie telewizora lub baza została ostrzelana przez jeden z innych pojazdów, zabawka natychmiast uruchamiała sekwencję &quot;Power On&quot;, powodując świecenie klatki piersiowej figurki.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>