<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2004</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Cave Story</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Cave Story is a 2004 Metroidvania platform-adventure game for Microsoft Windows. It was developed over five years by Japanese developer Daisuke "Pixel" Amaya in his free time. Cave Story features 2D platform mechanics and is reminiscent of the games Amaya played in his youth, such as Metroid and Castlevania (both released in 1986). After its initial self-published release, the game slowly gained popularity on the internet. It received widespread critical acclaim for many polished aspects of its design, such as its compelling characters, setting, story, and gameplay. Cave Story is considered by many as the quintessential indie game because of its one-man development team and influence on the gaming world.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Cave Story (jap. 洞窟物語 Dōkutsu Monogatari) – darmowa gra komputerowa (freeware) opublikowana w grudniu 2004 roku. Została stworzona przez Daisuke Amayę, znanego również pod jego pseudonimem artystycznym "Pixel". Cave Story jest przygodową grą akcji podobną do Castlevanii i Metroida. Ulepszona wersja o tytule Cave Story+ została wydana w listopadzie 2011 roku w usłudze Steam oraz w październiku 2012 roku na Nintendo 3DS. 20 czerwca 2017 Cave Story + zostało wydane na Nintendo Switch.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Cave Story — бесплатная компьютерная игра в жанре метроидвания, созданная японским программистом Дайсукэ Амаей (творческий псевдоним Pixel) в свободное время и выпущенная в декабре 2004 года. Спустя некоторое время игра получила популярность в Интернете. Cave Story описывается многими игровыми изданиями как одна из самых значимых инди-игр, выделяя, что над ней трудился лишь один человек, и учитывая её влияние на игровую индустрию.</text>
			<text lang="es">Cave Story es un juego de aventuras y plataformas metroidvania de 2004 para Microsoft Windows. Fue desarrollado durante cinco años por el desarrollador japonés Daisuke "Pixel" Amaya en su tiempo libre. Cave Story presenta una mecánica de plataformas en 2D y recuerda a los juegos a los que Amaya jugó en su juventud, como Metroid y Castlevania (ambos publicados en 1986). Tras su autopublicación inicial, el juego fue ganando popularidad poco a poco en Internet. Recibió elogios generalizados de la crítica por muchos aspectos pulidos de su diseño, como sus atractivos personajes, ambientación, historia y jugabilidad. Cave Story es considerado por muchos la quintaesencia de los juegos independientes por su equipo de desarrollo unipersonal y su influencia en el mundo de los videojuegos.</text>
			<text lang="de">Cave Story ist ein Metroidvania-Plattform-Adventure-Spiel aus dem Jahr 2004 für Microsoft Windows. Es wurde über fünf Jahre vom japanischen Entwickler Daisuke "Pixel" Amaya in seiner Freizeit entwickelt. Cave Story zeichnet sich durch eine 2D-Plattformmechanik aus und erinnert an die Spiele, die Amaya in seiner Jugend gespielt hat, wie Metroid und Castlevania (beide 1986 veröffentlicht). Nach seiner ersten Veröffentlichung im Eigenverlag wurde das Spiel im Internet langsam populär. Es erhielt viel Lob von der Kritik für die vielen ausgefeilten Aspekte seines Designs, wie z. B. die fesselnden Charaktere, das Setting, die Geschichte und das Gameplay. Cave Story wird aufgrund seines Ein-Mann-Entwicklerteams und seines Einflusses auf die Spielewelt von vielen als der Inbegriff eines Indie-Spiels angesehen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Cave Story est un jeu de plateforme et d'aventure Metroidvania de 2004 pour Microsoft Windows. Il a été développé pendant cinq ans par le développeur japonais Daisuke "Pixel" Amaya pendant son temps libre. Cave Story présente des mécanismes de plate-forme en 2D et rappelle les jeux auxquels Amaya a joué dans sa jeunesse, tels que Metroid et Castlevania (tous deux sortis en 1986). Après sa publication initiale en auto-publication, le jeu a lentement gagné en popularité sur Internet. Il a été largement salué par la critique pour les nombreux aspects soignés de sa conception, tels que ses personnages fascinants, son cadre, son histoire et sa jouabilité. Cave Story est considéré par beaucoup comme la quintessence du jeu indépendant en raison de son équipe de développement composée d'un seul homme et de son influence sur le monde du jeu.</text>
			<text lang="it">Cave Story è un gioco platform-adventure Metroidvania del 2004 per Microsoft Windows. È stato sviluppato per cinque anni dallo sviluppatore giapponese Daisuke "Pixel" Amaya nel suo tempo libero. Cave Story è caratterizzato da meccaniche platform 2D e ricorda i giochi a cui Amaya giocava in gioventù, come Metroid e Castlevania (entrambi usciti nel 1986). Dopo l'iniziale pubblicazione autonoma, il gioco ha lentamente guadagnato popolarità su Internet. Ha ricevuto ampi consensi dalla critica per molti aspetti curati del suo design, come i personaggi, l'ambientazione, la storia e il gameplay. Cave Story è considerato da molti come la quintessenza del gioco indipendente, grazie al suo team di sviluppo composto da un solo uomo e alla sua influenza sul mondo dei videogiochi.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Cave Story (jap. 洞窟物語 Dōkutsu Monogatari) – um jogo de computador gratuito (freeware) publicado em dezembro de 2004. Foi criado por Daisuke Amaya, também conhecido por seu pseudônimo artístico "Pixel". Cave Story é um jogo de ação e aventura semelhante a Castlevania e Metroid. Uma versão aprimorada intitulada Cave Story+ foi lançada em novembro de 2011 no Steam e em outubro de 2012 para Nintendo 3DS. Em 20 de junho de 2017, Cave Story + foi lançado para Nintendo Switch.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
