<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.26</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.376</pos>
			<maxSize>0.2</maxSize>
			<rotation/>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.376" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.26</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.376</pos>
			<maxSize>0.17</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<rotation/>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.376" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Commodore</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>CBM-II</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Commodore CBM-II series is a short-lived range of 8-bit personal computers from Commodore Business Machines (CBM), released in 1982 and intended as a follow-on to the Commodore PET series.
The CBM-II has two incarnations, the P series (P = personal, or, home use) and the B series (B = business use). The B series was available with a built-in monochrome monitor (hi-profile) with detached keyboard, and also as a single unit with built-in keyboard but no monitor (lo-profile).

The CBM-II line sold poorly and ended up being extremely expensive to manufacture, as well as difficult to develop software for. Commodore did not release any sales figures or an official discontinuation date, however the B128/600 is the most common model in the lineup. Production ended at some point during 1984 and Commodore liquidated their remaining inventory in 1985.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Seria Commodore CBM-II to krótko żyjąca seria 8-bitowych komputerów osobistych firmy Commodore Business Machines (CBM), wydana w 1982 roku i będąca następcą serii Commodore PET.
CBM-II ma dwa wcielenia, seria P (P = osobisty, lub, domowy) i seria B (B = biznesowy). Seria B była dostępna z wbudowanym monitorem monochromatycznym (hi-profile) z odłączaną klawiaturą, a także jako pojedyncze urządzenie z wbudowaną klawiaturą, ale bez monitora (lo-profile).

Linia CBM-II sprzedawała się słabo i okazała się niezwykle droga w produkcji, a także trudna w tworzeniu oprogramowania. Commodore nie podało żadnych danych dotyczących sprzedaży ani oficjalnej daty zakończenia produkcji, jednak B128/600 to najczęściej spotykany model w linii. Produkcja zakończyła się w pewnym momencie w 1984 roku, a Commodore upłynniło swoje pozostałe zapasy w 1985 roku.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Серия Commodore CBM-II - это недолговечная серия 8-битных персональных компьютеров компании Commodore Business Machines (CBM), выпущенная в 1982 году и задуманная как продолжение серии Commodore PET.
У CBM-II было два воплощения: серия P (P = персональное, или домашнее использование) и серия B (B = деловое использование). Серия B выпускалась со встроенным монохромным монитором (hi-profile) с отделенной клавиатурой, а также в виде отдельного устройства со встроенной клавиатурой, но без монитора (lo-profile).

Линейка CBM-II продавалась плохо и оказалась чрезвычайно дорогой в производстве, а также сложной для разработки программного обеспечения. Компания Commodore не опубликовала никаких данных о продажах или официальной даты прекращения производства, однако модель B128/600 стала самой распространенной в линейке. Производство закончилось в какой-то момент в 1984 году, а в 1985 году Commodore ликвидировал оставшиеся запасы.</text>
			<text lang="es">La serie Commodore CBM-II es una gama efímera de ordenadores personales de 8 bits de Commodore Business Machines (CBM), lanzada en 1982 como continuación de la serie Commodore PET.
La CBM-II tiene dos versiones, la serie P (P = uso personal o doméstico) y la serie B (B = uso comercial). La serie B estaba disponible con un monitor monocromo integrado (perfil alto) con teclado independiente, y también como unidad única con teclado integrado pero sin monitor (perfil bajo).

La línea CBM-II se vendió mal y resultó ser extremadamente cara de fabricar, además de difícil de desarrollar software para ella. Commodore no publicó cifras de ventas ni una fecha oficial de interrupción de la producción, pero el B128/600 es el modelo más común de la gama. La producción finalizó en algún momento de 1984 y Commodore liquidó el inventario restante en 1985.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Commodore CBM-II-Serie ist eine kurzlebige Reihe von 8-Bit-Personalcomputern von Commodore Business Machines (CBM), die 1982 auf den Markt kam und als Nachfolger der Commodore PET-Serie gedacht war.
Der CBM-II wurde in zwei Varianten hergestellt, der P-Serie (P = Personal oder Home Use) und der B-Serie (B = Business Use). Die B-Serie war mit einem eingebauten Monochrom-Monitor (Hi-Profile) mit abgesetzter Tastatur und auch als Einzelgerät mit eingebauter Tastatur, aber ohne Monitor (Lo-Profile) erhältlich.

Die CBM-II-Reihe verkaufte sich schlecht und erwies sich als extrem teuer in der Herstellung sowie als schwierig in der Softwareentwicklung. Commodore gab keine Verkaufszahlen oder ein offizielles Auslaufdatum bekannt, aber der B128/600 ist das meistverkaufte Modell der Reihe. Die Produktion wurde irgendwann im Laufe des Jahres 1984 eingestellt, und Commodore liquidierte 1985 seine restlichen Bestände.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La série Commodore CBM-II est une gamme éphémère d'ordinateurs personnels 8 bits de Commodore Business Machines (CBM), sortie en 1982 et destinée à succéder à la série Commodore PET.
Le CBM-II a connu deux incarnations, la série P (P = personnel, ou usage domestique) et la série B (B = usage professionnel). La série B était disponible avec un moniteur monochrome intégré (profil haut) et un clavier détaché, ainsi que sous la forme d'une unité unique avec clavier intégré mais sans moniteur (profil bas).

La gamme CBM-II s'est mal vendue et s'est révélée extrêmement coûteuse à fabriquer et difficile à développer en termes de logiciels. Commodore n'a pas publié de chiffres de vente ni de date officielle d'arrêt de la production, mais le B128/600 est le modèle le plus courant de la gamme. La production s'est arrêtée dans le courant de l'année 1984 et Commodore a liquidé ses stocks restants en 1985.</text>
			<text lang="it">La serie Commodore CBM-II è una serie di personal computer a 8 bit di Commodore Business Machines (CBM), rilasciata nel 1982 e destinata a seguire la serie Commodore PET.
Il CBM-II ebbe due incarnazioni, la serie P (P = personal, o uso domestico) e la serie B (B = uso aziendale). La serie B era disponibile con un monitor monocromatico incorporato (hi-profile) con tastiera staccata, e anche come unità singola con tastiera incorporata ma senza monitor (lo-profile).

La linea CBM-II ebbe scarse vendite e finì per essere estremamente costosa da produrre, oltre che difficile da sviluppare software. Commodore non ha rilasciato dati di vendita o una data ufficiale di cessazione della produzione, tuttavia il B128/600 è il modello più comune della linea. La produzione terminò a un certo punto nel 1984 e Commodore liquidò le rimanenti scorte nel 1985.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Commodore CBM-II foi uma série de computadores pessoais de 8 bits de curta duração da Commodore Business Machines (CBM), lançada em 1982 e sucessor da série Commodore PET.

O CBM-II tinha duas versões, a série P (P = pessoal, ou, doméstico) e a série B (B = comercial). A série B estava disponível com um monitor monocromático integrado (perfil alto) com teclado destacável, e também como um único dispositivo com teclado integrado, mas sem monitor (perfil baixo).

A linha CBM-II teve vendas fracas e se mostrou extremamente cara de produzir, além de ser difícil de programar. A Commodore não divulgou dados sobre as vendas ou a data oficial de término da produção, mas o B128/600 é o modelo mais comum da linha. A produção terminou em algum momento de 1984, e a Commodore liquidou seus estoques restantes em 1985.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
