<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.519 0.378</pos>
			<maxSize>0.3</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.239 0.378" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1997</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>C-Dogs SDL</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>C-Dogs, the sequel to Cyberdogs, is a shoot'em up video game where players work cooperatively during missions, and against each other in "dogfight" deathmatch mode.
C-Dogs made changes and improvements on the original Cyberdogs game mechanics. The single-player/cooperative gameplay is separated into campaigns, each comprising many missions. Usually, each level involves the player(s) killing enemies (while avoiding harming civilians and teammates) using a variety of pre-selected weapons; collecting keys to unlock special rooms; and picking up required items to fulfill the mission objectives.

The "dog fight" gameplay is the typical deathmatch: players attempt to kill each other for points, in order to gain victory. Only two players can play against each other, by sitting at the same computer and using the keyboard, joysticks or gamepads.</text>
			<text lang="pl">C-Dogs, sequel Cyberdogs, to gra wideo typu shoot'em up, w której gracze współpracują podczas misji, a także przeciwko sobie w trybie "dogfight" deathmatch.
C-Dogs wprowadził zmiany i ulepszenia w mechanice oryginalnej gry Cyberdogs. Rozgrywka dla jednego gracza/kooperacyjna jest podzielona na kampanie, z których każda składa się z wielu misji. Zazwyczaj każdy poziom wymaga od gracza (lub graczy) zabijania wrogów (przy jednoczesnym unikaniu krzywdy cywilów i kolegów z drużyny) przy użyciu różnych wybranych wcześniej broni; zbierania kluczy, aby odblokować specjalne pomieszczenia; i zbierania wymaganych przedmiotów, aby wypełnić cele misji.

Rozgrywka "walki psów" to typowy deathmatch: gracze próbują zabijać się nawzajem za punkty, aby zdobyć zwycięstwo. Tylko dwóch graczy może grać przeciwko sobie, siedząc przy tym samym komputerze i używając klawiatury, joysticków lub gamepadów.</text>
			<text lang="ru">C-Dogs, продолжение Cyberdogs, представляет собой видеоигру в жанре shoot'em up, в которой игроки работают совместно во время миссий и друг против друга в режиме "собачьего боя" deathmatch.
В C-Dogs были внесены изменения и улучшения в игровую механику оригинальной Cyberdogs. Однопользовательский/кооперативный геймплей разделен на кампании, каждая из которых состоит из множества миссий. Обычно на каждом уровне игроку(ам) предстоит убивать врагов (избегая при этом причинения вреда гражданским лицам и товарищам по команде), используя различные виды оружия, собирать ключи, чтобы открыть специальные комнаты, и собирать предметы, необходимые для выполнения поставленных задач.

Геймплей "собачьего боя" представляет собой типичный deathmatch: игроки пытаются убить друг друга за очки, чтобы одержать победу. Только два игрока могут играть друг против друга, сидя за одним компьютером и используя клавиатуру, джойстики или геймпады.</text>
			<text lang="it">C-Dogs, il sequel di Cyberdogs, è un videogioco sparatutto in cui i giocatori lavorano in cooperazione durante le missioni e l'uno contro l'altro in modalità "dogfight" (combattimento tra cani).
C-Dogs ha apportato modifiche e miglioramenti alla meccanica di gioco originale di Cyberdogs. Il gioco per giocatore singolo/cooperativo è suddiviso in campagne, ognuna delle quali comprende numerose missioni. Di solito, ogni livello prevede che il giocatore uccida i nemici (evitando di danneggiare i civili e i compagni di squadra) utilizzando una varietà di armi preselezionate, raccogliendo chiavi per sbloccare stanze speciali e raccogliendo gli oggetti necessari per raggiungere gli obiettivi della missione.

Il gameplay "dog fight" è il tipico deathmatch: i giocatori cercano di uccidersi a vicenda per ottenere punti, al fine di ottenere la vittoria. Solo due giocatori possono sfidarsi, seduti allo stesso computer e utilizzando la tastiera, i joystick o il gamepad.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
