<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1997</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>C-Dogs SDL</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>C-Dogs, the sequel to Cyberdogs, is a shoot'em up video game where players work cooperatively during missions, and against each other in "dogfight" deathmatch mode.
C-Dogs made changes and improvements on the original Cyberdogs game mechanics. The single-player/cooperative gameplay is separated into campaigns, each comprising many missions. Usually, each level involves the player(s) killing enemies (while avoiding harming civilians and teammates) using a variety of pre-selected weapons; collecting keys to unlock special rooms; and picking up required items to fulfill the mission objectives.

The "dog fight" gameplay is the typical deathmatch: players attempt to kill each other for points, in order to gain victory. Only two players can play against each other, by sitting at the same computer and using the keyboard, joysticks or gamepads.</text>
			<text lang="pl">C-Dogs, sequel Cyberdogs, to gra wideo typu shoot'em up, w której gracze współpracują podczas misji, a także przeciwko sobie w trybie "dogfight" deathmatch.
C-Dogs wprowadził zmiany i ulepszenia w mechanice oryginalnej gry Cyberdogs. Rozgrywka dla jednego gracza/kooperacyjna jest podzielona na kampanie, z których każda składa się z wielu misji. Zazwyczaj każdy poziom wymaga od gracza (lub graczy) zabijania wrogów (przy jednoczesnym unikaniu krzywdy cywilów i kolegów z drużyny) przy użyciu różnych wybranych wcześniej broni; zbierania kluczy, aby odblokować specjalne pomieszczenia; i zbierania wymaganych przedmiotów, aby wypełnić cele misji.

Rozgrywka "walki psów" to typowy deathmatch: gracze próbują zabijać się nawzajem za punkty, aby zdobyć zwycięstwo. Tylko dwóch graczy może grać przeciwko sobie, siedząc przy tym samym komputerze i używając klawiatury, joysticków lub gamepadów.</text>
			<text lang="ru">C-Dogs - продолжение Cyberdogs, представляет собой игру в жанре "Run-and-Gun", поддерживающая до 4 игроков в режимах кооператива и deathmatch. Настройте своего персонажа, выберите один из множества видов оружия и пройдите более 100 кампаний, созданных пользователями. Получайте удовольствие!

В C-Dogs были внесены изменения и улучшения в игровую механику оригинальной Cyberdogs. Однопользовательский/кооперативный геймплей разделен на кампании, каждая из которых состоит из множества миссий. Обычно на каждом уровне игроку(ам) предстоит убивать врагов (избегая при этом причинения вреда гражданским лицам и товарищам по команде), используя различные виды оружия, собирать ключи, чтобы открыть специальные комнаты, и собирать предметы, необходимые для выполнения поставленных задач.

Геймплей "собачьего боя" представляет собой типичный deathmatch: игроки пытаются убить друг друга за очки, чтобы одержать победу. Только два игрока могут играть друг против друга, сидя за одним компьютером и используя клавиатуру, джойстики или геймпады.</text>
			<text lang="es">C-Dogs, la secuela de Cyberdogs, es un videojuego de disparos en el que los jugadores trabajan de forma cooperativa durante las misiones, y unos contra otros en el modo "dogfight" deathmatch.
C-Dogs introdujo cambios y mejoras en la mecánica original de Cyberdogs. El modo de juego individual/cooperativo se divide en campañas, cada una de las cuales comprende muchas misiones. Por lo general, cada nivel implica que el jugador o jugadores maten a los enemigos (evitando dañar a los civiles y compañeros de equipo) utilizando una variedad de armas preseleccionadas, recogiendo llaves para desbloquear habitaciones especiales y recogiendo los objetos necesarios para cumplir los objetivos de la misión.

El modo de juego "pelea de perros" es el típico deathmatch: los jugadores intentan matarse unos a otros a cambio de puntos, para conseguir la victoria. Sólo pueden enfrentarse dos jugadores, sentados frente al mismo ordenador y utilizando el teclado, los joysticks o los gamepads.</text>
			<text lang="de">C-Dogs, die Fortsetzung von Cyberdogs, ist ein Shoot'em-up-Videospiel, bei dem die Spieler während der Missionen kooperativ zusammenarbeiten und im Deathmatch-Modus "Dogfight" gegeneinander antreten.
In C-Dogs wurden Änderungen und Verbesserungen an der ursprünglichen Cyberdogs-Spielmechanik vorgenommen. Das Einzelspieler-/Kooperations-Gameplay ist in Kampagnen unterteilt, die jeweils aus vielen Missionen bestehen. In der Regel geht es in jedem Level darum, Feinde zu töten (ohne dabei Zivilisten und Teamkameraden zu verletzen), indem man eine Reihe von vordefinierten Waffen einsetzt, Schlüssel sammelt, um spezielle Räume zu öffnen, und benötigte Gegenstände einsammelt, um die Missionsziele zu erfüllen.

Das "Dog Fight"-Gameplay ist das typische Deathmatch: Die Spieler versuchen, sich gegenseitig um Punkte zu töten, um den Sieg zu erringen. Nur zwei Spieler können gegeneinander antreten, indem sie am selben Computer sitzen und die Tastatur, Joysticks oder Gamepads benutzen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">C-Dogs, la suite de Cyberdogs, est un jeu vidéo de type shoot'em up dans lequel les joueurs travaillent en coopération pendant les missions, et les uns contre les autres en mode deathmatch "dogfight".
C-Dogs a apporté des modifications et des améliorations aux mécanismes de jeu originaux de Cyberdogs. Le jeu solo/coopératif est divisé en campagnes, chacune comprenant de nombreuses missions. En général, chaque niveau implique que le(s) joueur(s) tue(nt) des ennemis (tout en évitant de blesser les civils et les coéquipiers) à l'aide d'une variété d'armes présélectionnées, qu'il(s) récupère(nt) des clés pour déverrouiller des salles spéciales et qu'il(s) ramasse(nt) des objets nécessaires pour remplir les objectifs de la mission.

Le jeu "dog fight" est un match à mort typique : les joueurs tentent de s'entretuer pour gagner des points, afin de remporter la victoire. Seuls deux joueurs peuvent s'affronter, assis devant le même ordinateur et utilisant le clavier, les joysticks ou les manettes de jeu.</text>
			<text lang="it">C-Dogs, il sequel di Cyberdogs, è un videogioco sparatutto in cui i giocatori lavorano in cooperazione durante le missioni e l'uno contro l'altro in modalità "dogfight" (combattimento tra cani).
C-Dogs ha apportato modifiche e miglioramenti alla meccanica di gioco originale di Cyberdogs. Il gioco per giocatore singolo/cooperativo è suddiviso in campagne, ognuna delle quali comprende numerose missioni. Di solito, ogni livello prevede che il giocatore uccida i nemici (evitando di danneggiare i civili e i compagni di squadra) utilizzando una varietà di armi preselezionate, raccogliendo chiavi per sbloccare stanze speciali e raccogliendo gli oggetti necessari per raggiungere gli obiettivi della missione.

Il gameplay "dog fight" è il tipico deathmatch: i giocatori cercano di uccidersi a vicenda per ottenere punti, al fine di ottenere la vittoria. Solo due giocatori possono sfidarsi, seduti allo stesso computer e utilizzando la tastiera, i joystick o il gamepad.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
