<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.48 0.352</pos>
			<maxSize>0.27</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2 0.352" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.43</origin>
			<pos>0.48 0.352</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2 0.352" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>EACA</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>EG2000 Colour Genie</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The EACA EG2000 Colour Genie was a computer produced by Hong Kong-based manufacturer EACA. It was introduced in Germany in August 1982 by Tromeschläger Computer Service and Schmidtke Electronic.
This computer followed their earlier Video Genie I and II models and was released around the same time as the business-oriented Video Genie. The Colour Genie featured a Zilog Z80 CPU running at 2.2 MHz, 16 KB RAM (expandable to 32 KB), and 16 colors for graphics. It had a 40×24 text display and 160×96 graphics resolution. The sound hardware included a General Instruments AY-3-8910 chip with 3 sound channels and 1 noise channel.

The Colour Genie was not compatible with Tandy's newer TRS-80 Color Computer due to architectural differences. Approximately 190 games were published for this system in English and German.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'EACA EG2000 Colour Genie era un computer prodotto dal produttore EACA di Hong Kong. Fu introdotto in Germania nell'agosto 1982 da Tromeschläger Computer Service e Schmidtke Electronic.
Questo computer seguiva i precedenti modelli Video Genie I e II e fu commercializzato all'incirca nello stesso periodo del Video Genie orientato al business. Il Colour Genie era dotato di una CPU Zilog Z80 a 2,2 MHz, 16 KB di RAM (espandibile a 32 KB) e 16 colori per la grafica. Aveva un display di testo 40×24 e una risoluzione grafica di 160×96. L'hardware audio comprendeva un chip General Instruments AY-3-8910 con 3 canali audio e 1 canale di rumore.

Il Colour Genie non era compatibile con il più recente TRS-80 Color Computer di Tandy a causa delle differenze architettoniche. Per questo sistema furono pubblicati circa 190 giochi in inglese e tedesco.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'EACA EG2000 Colour Genie était un ordinateur produit par le fabricant EACA basé à Hong Kong. Il a été introduit en Allemagne en août 1982 par Tromeschläger Computer Service et Schmidtke Electronic.
Cet ordinateur faisait suite aux modèles Video Genie I et II et a été commercialisé à peu près en même temps que le Video Genie destiné aux entreprises. Le Colour Genie était équipé d'un processeur Zilog Z80 cadencé à 2,2 MHz, d'une mémoire vive de 16 Ko (extensible à 32 Ko) et de 16 couleurs pour les graphiques. Il disposait d'un écran texte de 40×24 et d'une résolution graphique de 160×96. Le matériel audio comprenait une puce General Instruments AY-3-8910 avec 3 canaux sonores et 1 canal de bruit.

Le Colour Genie n'était pas compatible avec le TRS-80 Color Computer de Tandy, plus récent, en raison de différences architecturales. Environ 190 jeux ont été publiés pour ce système en anglais et en allemand.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der EACA EG2000 Colour Genie war ein Computer des in Hongkong ansässigen Herstellers EACA. Er wurde in Deutschland im August 1982 von Tromeschläger Computer Service und Schmidtke Electronic eingeführt.
Dieser Computer folgte auf die früheren Modelle Video Genie I und II und wurde etwa zur gleichen Zeit wie der business-orientierte Video Genie herausgebracht. Der Colour Genie verfügte über eine Zilog Z80-CPU mit 2,2 MHz, 16 KB RAM (erweiterbar auf 32 KB) und 16 Farben für Grafiken. Er hatte eine Textanzeige von 40×24 und eine Grafikauflösung von 160×96. Die Sound-Hardware umfasste einen General Instruments AY-3-8910 Chip mit 3 Soundkanälen und 1 Rauschkanal.

Der Colour Genie war aufgrund architektonischer Unterschiede nicht mit dem neueren TRS-80 Color Computer von Tandy kompatibel. Ungefähr 190 Spiele wurden für dieses System in Englisch und Deutsch veröffentlicht.</text>
			<text lang="es">El EACA EG2000 Colour Genie era un ordenador producido por el fabricante EACA, con sede en Hong Kong. Fue introducido en Alemania en agosto de 1982 por Tromeschläger Computer Service y Schmidtke Electronic.
Este ordenador siguió a sus modelos anteriores Video Genie I y II y salió al mercado más o menos al mismo tiempo que el Video Genie orientado a los negocios. El Colour Genie disponía de una CPU Zilog Z80 a 2,2 MHz, 16 KB de RAM (ampliable a 32 KB) y 16 colores para los gráficos. Tenía una pantalla de texto de 40×24 y una resolución gráfica de 160×96. El hardware de sonido incluía un chip General Instruments AY-3-8910 con 3 canales de sonido y 1 canal de ruido.

El Colour Genie no era compatible con el nuevo TRS-80 Color Computer de Tandy debido a diferencias arquitectónicas. Se publicaron aproximadamente 190 juegos para este sistema en inglés y alemán.</text>
			<text lang="ru">EACA EG2000 Colour Genie - компьютер, выпущенный гонконгским производителем EACA. Он был представлен в Германии в августе 1982 года компаниями Tromeschläger Computer Service и Schmidtke Electronic.
Этот компьютер последовал за более ранними моделями Video Genie I и II и был выпущен примерно в то же время, что и бизнес-ориентированный Video Genie. Colour Genie оснащался процессором Zilog Z80, работающим на частоте 2,2 МГц, 16 КБ оперативной памяти (с возможностью расширения до 32 КБ) и 16 цветами для графики. Он имел текстовый дисплей 40×24 и графическое разрешение 160×96. Звуковая аппаратура включала микросхему General Instruments AY-3-8910 с 3 звуковыми каналами и 1 каналом шума.

Из-за архитектурных различий Colour Genie не был совместим с более новой моделью Tandy TRS-80 Color Computer. Для этой системы было выпущено около 190 игр на английском и немецком языках.</text>
			<text lang="pl">EACA EG2000 Colour Genie był komputerem wyprodukowanym przez firmę EACA z siedzibą w Hongkongu. Został wprowadzony na rynek niemiecki w sierpniu 1982 roku przez Tromeschläger Computer Service i Schmidtke Electronic.
Komputer ten był następcą wcześniejszych modeli Video Genie I i II i został wydany mniej więcej w tym samym czasie, co zorientowany na biznes Video Genie. Colour Genie wyposażony był w procesor Zilog Z80 pracujący z częstotliwością 2,2 MHz, 16 KB pamięci RAM (z możliwością rozszerzenia do 32 KB) i 16 kolorów grafiki. Miał wyświetlacz tekstowy 40×24 i rozdzielczość grafiki 160×96. Sprzęt dźwiękowy zawierał układ General Instruments AY-3-8910 z 3 kanałami dźwiękowymi i 1 kanałem szumu.

Colour Genie nie był kompatybilny z nowszym komputerem TRS-80 Color Computer firmy Tandy ze względu na różnice architektoniczne. Na ten system wydano około 190 gier w języku angielskim i niemieckim.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O EACA EG2000 Colour Genie era um computador produzido pela EACA, com sede em Hong Kong. Foi lançado no mercado alemão em agosto de 1982 pela Tromeschläger Computer Service e Schmidtke Electronic.

Este computador era o sucessor dos modelos anteriores Video Genie I e II e foi lançado aproximadamente na mesma época que o Video Genie, voltado para negócios. O Colour Genie era equipado com um processador Zilog Z80 operando a 2,2 MHz, 16 KB de RAM (com possibilidade de expansão para 32 KB) e 16 cores de gráficos. Tinha um visor de texto 40×24 e resolução gráfica de 160×96. O hardware de som incluía um chip General Instruments AY-3-8910 com 3 canais de som e 1 canal de ruído.

O Colour Genie não era compatível com o computador TRS-80 Color Computer, mais recente, da Tandy, devido a diferenças arquitetônicas. Cerca de 190 jogos foram lançados para este sistema, em inglês e alemão.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
