<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2013</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>CorsixTH</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>A reimplementation of the 1997 Bullfrog business sim Theme Hospital. As well as faithfully recreating the original, CorsixTH adds support for modern operating systems (Windows, macOS, Linux and BSD), high resolutions and much more.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Reimplementacja biznesowego symulatora Theme Hospital firmy Bullfrog z 1997 roku. Oprócz wiernego odtworzenia oryginału, CorsixTH dodaje obsługę nowoczesnych systemów operacyjnych (Windows, macOS, Linux i BSD), wysokie rozdzielczości i wiele więcej.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Реализация бизнес-симулятора Theme Hospital от Bullfrog 1997 года. Помимо точного воссоздания оригинала, CorsixTH добавляет поддержку современных операционных систем (Windows, macOS, Linux и BSD), высоких разрешений и многое другое.</text>
			<text lang="es">Una reimplementación del simulador de negocios Theme Hospital de Bullfrog de 1997. Además de recrear fielmente el original, CorsixTH añade compatibilidad con sistemas operativos modernos (Windows, macOS, Linux y BSD), altas resoluciones y mucho más.</text>
			<text lang="de">Eine Neuimplementierung der Business-Simulation Theme Hospital von Bullfrog aus dem Jahr 1997. Neben der originalgetreuen Nachbildung des Originals bietet CorsixTH Unterstützung für moderne Betriebssysteme (Windows, macOS, Linux und BSD), hohe Auflösungen und vieles mehr.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Une réimplémentation de la simulation d'entreprise Theme Hospital de Bullfrog de 1997. En plus de recréer fidèlement l'original, CorsixTH prend en charge les systèmes d'exploitation modernes (Windows, macOS, Linux et BSD), les hautes résolutions et bien plus encore.</text>
			<text lang="it">Una reimplementazione del simulatore aziendale Theme Hospital di Bullfrog del 1997. Oltre a ricreare fedelmente l'originale, CorsixTH aggiunge il supporto per i sistemi operativi moderni (Windows, macOS, Linux e BSD), le alte risoluzioni e molto altro ancora.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
