<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.52 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.54 0.45</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.234 0.43" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.52 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.54 0.45</pos>
			<maxSize>0.202</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.26 0.45" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2005</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Zico</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>DXX-Rebirth</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>DXX-Rebirth is an open-source source port of the Descent and Descent II game engines, with some key features such as improved OpenGL graphics and effects, advanced multiplayer, stability and enhancements.

DXX-Rebirth preserves the classic Descent gameplay while offering modern features and compatibility.</text>
			<text lang="it">DXX-Rebirth è un porting open-source dei motori di gioco Descent e Descent II, con alcune caratteristiche chiave come grafica ed effetti OpenGL migliorati, multiplayer avanzato, stabilità e miglioramenti.

DXX-Rebirth conserva il classico gameplay di Descent, offrendo al contempo funzionalità e compatibilità moderne.</text>
			<text lang="fr">DXX-Rebirth est un portage open-source des moteurs de jeu Descent et Descent II, avec quelques caractéristiques clés telles que des graphismes et des effets OpenGL améliorés, un multijoueur avancé, de la stabilité et des améliorations.

DXX-Rebirth préserve le gameplay classique de Descent tout en offrant des fonctionnalités et une compatibilité modernes.</text>
			<text lang="de">DXX-Rebirth ist eine quelloffene Portierung der Descent- und Descent II-Spiele-Engines mit einigen wichtigen Funktionen wie verbesserten OpenGL-Grafiken und -Effekten, erweitertem Multiplayer-Modus, Stabilität und Erweiterungen.

DXX-Rebirth bewahrt das klassische Descent-Gameplay und bietet gleichzeitig moderne Funktionen und Kompatibilität.</text>
			<text lang="es">DXX-Rebirth es un port de código abierto de los motores de juego Descent y Descent II, con algunas características clave como gráficos y efectos OpenGL mejorados, multijugador avanzado, estabilidad y mejoras.

DXX-Rebirth conserva la jugabilidad clásica de Descent a la vez que ofrece características modernas y compatibilidad.</text>
			<text lang="ru">DXX-Rebirth - это порт с открытым исходным кодом игровых движков Descent и Descent II с некоторыми ключевыми особенностями, такими как обновлённый рендер 3D графики OpenGL, фильтрация текстур, полноэкранное сглаживание, эффекты прозрачности спрайтов, а так же расширенный мультиплеер, стабильность и другие улучшения.

DXX-Rebirth сохраняет классический геймплей Descent, предлагая при этом современные возможности и улучшенную совместимость.</text>
			<text lang="pl">DXX-Rebirth jest otwartoźródłowym portem silników gier Descent i Descent II, z kilkoma kluczowymi funkcjami, takimi jak ulepszona grafika i efekty OpenGL, zaawansowany tryb wieloosobowy, stabilność i ulepszenia.
				
DXX-Rebirth zachowuje klasyczną rozgrywkę Descent, oferując jednocześnie nowoczesne funkcje i kompatybilność.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>