<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.31</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.44</origin>
			<pos>0.498 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.26</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.218 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.31</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.44</origin>
			<pos>0.498 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.218 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2015</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>ECWolf</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>ECWolf is an advanced source port for Wolfenstein 3D, Spear of Destiny, and Super 3D Noah's Ark based off of the Wolf4SDL code base. ECWolf pulls a substantial amount of code from ZDoom and aims to provide a wide array of mod editing capabilities without the need to modify the source code.

Expanding upon Wolf4SDL, ECWolf opens up yet even more possibilities for the world of Wolfenstein modding. Starting in 2015, numerous sets have been released exclusively for the ECWolf port, most notably projects by AstroCreep and Executor.</text>
			<text lang="pl">ECWolf jest zaawansowanym portem źródłowym dla Wolfenstein 3D, Spear of Destiny i Super 3D Noah's Ark opartym na bazie kodu Wolf4SDL. ECWolf czerpie znaczną część kodu z ZDooma i ma na celu zapewnienie szerokiego wachlarza możliwości edycji modów bez konieczności modyfikowania kodu źródłowego.

Rozszerzając Wolf4SDL, ECWolf otwiera jeszcze więcej możliwości dla świata modowania Wolfensteina. Począwszy od 2015 roku, liczne zestawy zostały wydane wyłącznie dla portu ECWolf, w szczególności projekty AstroCreep i Executor.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Порт Wolfenstein-3D под современные ОС

ECWolf предоставляет много полезных функций, таких как улучшенное управление (и возможность его настройки), поддержка больших разрешений и снятие ограничений с количества слотов для сохранений. Сама же игра начинает выглядеть крайне респектабельно: сглаженные углы и грамотно растянутые текстуры без какой-либо фильтрации.</text>
			<text lang="es">ECWolf es un port de código avanzado para Wolfenstein 3D, Spear of Destiny y Super 3D Noah's Ark basado en el código Wolf4SDL. ECWolf extrae una cantidad sustancial de código de ZDoom y tiene como objetivo proporcionar una amplia gama de capacidades de edición de mods sin necesidad de modificar el código fuente.

Ampliando Wolf4SDL, ECWolf abre aún más posibilidades para el mundo del modding de Wolfenstein. A partir de 2015, se han lanzado numerosos sets en exclusiva para el port ECWolf, entre los que destacan los proyectos de AstroCreep y Executor.</text>
			<text lang="de">ECWolf ist eine erweiterte Quellcode-Portierung für Wolfenstein 3D, Spear of Destiny und Super 3D Noah's Ark, die auf der Wolf4SDL-Codebasis basiert. ECWolf zieht eine beträchtliche Menge an Code aus ZDoom und zielt darauf ab, eine breite Palette von Mod-Bearbeitungsmöglichkeiten zu bieten, ohne die Notwendigkeit, den Quellcode zu ändern.

Durch die Erweiterung von Wolf4SDL eröffnet ECWolf noch mehr Möglichkeiten für die Welt des Wolfenstein-Modding. Seit 2015 wurden zahlreiche Sets exklusiv für die ECWolf-Portierung veröffentlicht, vor allem die Projekte von AstroCreep und Executor.</text>
			<text lang="fr">ECWolf est un portage avancé de Wolfenstein 3D, Spear of Destiny et Super 3D Noah's Ark basé sur le code Wolf4SDL. ECWolf reprend une grande partie du code de ZDoom et vise à fournir un large éventail de capacités d'édition de mods sans avoir à modifier le code source.

En s'appuyant sur Wolf4SDL, ECWolf ouvre encore plus de possibilités pour le monde du modding Wolfenstein. Depuis 2015, de nombreux sets ont été publiés exclusivement pour le portage ECWolf, notamment les projets d'AstroCreep et d'Executor.</text>
			<text lang="it">ECWolf è un port sorgente avanzato per Wolfenstein 3D, Spear of Destiny e Super 3D Noah's Ark basato sulla base di codice Wolf4SDL. ECWolf estrae una quantità sostanziale di codice da ZDoom e mira a fornire un'ampia gamma di capacità di modifica delle mod senza la necessità di modificare il codice sorgente.

Espandendo Wolf4SDL, ECWolf apre ancora più possibilità al mondo del modding di Wolfenstein. A partire dal 2015, sono stati rilasciati numerosi set esclusivamente per il port ECWolf, in particolare i progetti di AstroCreep ed Executor.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
