<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-left" extra="true">
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.3 0.2</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.4 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.1 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.285 0.36</pos>
			<minSize>0.1 0.3</minSize>
			<rotation>26</rotation>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>27</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.005 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-right" extra="true">
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.6 0.2</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.9 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.71 0.36</pos>
			<minSize>0.1 0.3</minSize>
			<rotation>-26</rotation>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>27</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.43 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video-arcade" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.435</pos>
			<size>0.38 0.2</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.38 0.15</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.29 0.2</size>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.435" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videoboxarcade" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.436</pos>
			<maxSize>0.36</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.436" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2008</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Examu</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>eX-Board</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The eX-Board, introduced in 2008, is a proprietary arcade system board created by Examu. It served as the foundation for their video games.

The hardware specifications of eX-Board include a fanless Via C7 NanoBGA2 CPU (based on the X86 architecture), a Via CN700 and VT8237R Plus chipset, 1 GB DDR2 SDRAM (with VRAM sharing), and integrated S3 UniChrome Pro AGP graphics with MPEG-2 decoding acceleration. Initially, Examu developed games specifically for eX-Board, but later shifted their focus to Taito’s NESiCAxLive arcade delivery system.
Support for eX-Board ceased in December 2013.</text>
			<text lang="it">La eX-Board, introdotta nel 2008, è una scheda di sistema arcade proprietaria creata da Examu. È servita come base per i loro videogiochi.

Le specifiche hardware della eX-Board includono una CPU Via C7 NanoBGA2 senza ventola (basata sull'architettura X86), un chipset Via CN700 e VT8237R Plus, 1 GB di DDR2 SDRAM (con condivisione della VRAM) e grafica integrata S3 UniChrome Pro AGP con accelerazione della decodifica MPEG-2. Inizialmente, Examu sviluppò giochi specifici per eX-Board, ma in seguito spostò la propria attenzione sul sistema di distribuzione arcade NESiCAxLive di Taito.
Il supporto per eX-Board è cessato nel dicembre 2013.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'eX-Board, introduite en 2008, est une carte d'arcade propriétaire créée par Examu. Elle a servi de base à leurs jeux vidéo.

Les spécifications matérielles de l'eX-Board comprennent un processeur Via C7 NanoBGA2 sans ventilateur (basé sur l'architecture X86), un chipset Via CN700 et VT8237R Plus, 1 Go de SDRAM DDR2 (avec partage de VRAM), et une carte graphique AGP S3 UniChrome Pro intégrée avec accélération du décodage MPEG-2. Au départ, Examu a développé des jeux spécifiquement pour l'eX-Board, mais s'est ensuite concentré sur le système d'arcade NESiCAxLive de Taito.
Le support de l'eX-Board a cessé en décembre 2013.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das 2008 eingeführte eX-Board ist ein proprietäres Arcade-System-Board, das von Examu entwickelt wurde. Es diente als Grundlage für ihre Videospiele.

Zu den Hardwarespezifikationen des eX-Boards gehören eine lüfterlose Via C7 NanoBGA2-CPU (basierend auf der X86-Architektur), ein Via CN700- und VT8237R Plus-Chipsatz, 1 GB DDR2-SDRAM (mit VRAM-Sharing) und integrierte S3 UniChrome Pro AGP-Grafik mit MPEG-2-Dekodierungsbeschleunigung. Anfangs entwickelte Examu Spiele speziell für das eX-Board, später verlagerte sich der Schwerpunkt auf das NESiCAxLive Arcade-System von Taito.
Die Unterstützung für eX-Board wurde im Dezember 2013 eingestellt.</text>
			<text lang="es">La eX-Board, presentada en 2008, es una placa de sistema arcade patentada creada por Examu. Sirvió de base para sus videojuegos.

Las especificaciones de hardware de la eX-Board incluyen una CPU Via C7 NanoBGA2 sin ventilador (basada en la arquitectura X86), un chipset Via CN700 y VT8237R Plus, 1 GB de SDRAM DDR2 (con uso compartido de VRAM) y gráficos integrados S3 UniChrome Pro AGP con aceleración de descodificación MPEG-2. En un principio, Examu desarrolló juegos específicamente para la eX-Board, pero más tarde se centró en el sistema arcade NESiCAxLive de Taito.
El soporte para eX-Board cesó en diciembre de 2013.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Плата eX-Board, представленная в 2008 году, - это фирменная плата для аркадных систем, созданная компанией Examu. Она послужила основой для их видеоигр.

Аппаратные характеристики eX-Board включают в себя безвентиляторный процессор Via C7 NanoBGA2 (на базе архитектуры X86), чипсет Via CN700 и VT8237R Plus, 1 Гб DDR2 SDRAM (с разделением VRAM) и интегрированную графику S3 UniChrome Pro AGP с ускорением декодирования MPEG-2. Изначально компания Examu разрабатывала игры специально для eX-Board, но позже переключила свое внимание на аркадную систему доставки NESiCAxLive от Taito.
Поддержка eX-Board была прекращена в декабре 2013 года.</text>
			<text lang="pl">eX-Board, wprowadzona na rynek w 2008 roku, jest zastrzeżoną płytą systemu arcade stworzoną przez Examu. Służyła ona jako podstawa ich gier wideo.

Specyfikacja sprzętowa eX-Board obejmuje bezwentylatorowy procesor Via C7 NanoBGA2 (oparty na architekturze X86), chipset Via CN700 i VT8237R Plus, 1 GB pamięci DDR2 SDRAM (ze współdzieloną pamięcią VRAM) oraz zintegrowany układ graficzny S3 UniChrome Pro AGP z akceleracją dekodowania MPEG-2. Początkowo Examu opracowywało gry specjalnie dla eX-Board, ale później skupiło się na systemie zręcznościowym Taito NESiCAxLive.
Wsparcie dla eX-Board zakończyło się w grudniu 2013 roku.</text>
			<text lang="pt">eX-Board, lançada no mercado em 2008, é uma placa de sistema arcade proprietária criada pela Examu. Ela serviu como base para seus jogos de videogame.

A especificação de hardware do eX-Board inclui um processador Via C7 NanoBGA2 sem ventoinha (baseado na arquitetura X86), chipset Via CN700 e VT8237R Plus, 1 GB de memória DDR2 SDRAM (com memória VRAM compartilhada) e um chip gráfico integrado S3 UniChrome Pro AGP com aceleração de decodificação MPEG-2. Inicialmente, a Examu desenvolvia jogos especificamente para o eX-Board, mas depois se concentrou no sistema arcade Taito NESiCAxLive.

O suporte para o eX-Board foi encerrado em dezembro de 2013.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
