<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video-arcade" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.15</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.363</pos>
			<size>0.38 0.15</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.285 0.15</size>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.363" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videoboxarcade" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.15</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.366</pos>
			<maxSize>0.376</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.366" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2000</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Final Burn Neo</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Final Burn Neo (aka FBNeo) is the new official branch of the Final Burn Alpha emulator, which is compatible with hundreds of arcade and console games. The libretro core of FBNeo brings its library of compatible titles to RetroArch, where the core's tight integration with the libretro API allows it to work with RetroArch's advanced time-bending features like rollback-based netplay and runahead latency reduction. It includes input presets for automatic mapping of buttons for different games, including fighting game layouts for both modern and old-school arcade controls (aka fightsticks).</text>
			<text lang="pl">Final Burn Neo (aka FBNeo) to nowa oficjalna odmiana emulatora Final Burn Alpha, który jest kompatybilny z setkami gier arcade i konsolowych. Rdzeń libretro FBNeo przenosi bibliotekę kompatybilnych tytułów do RetroArch, gdzie ścisła integracja z API libretro pozwala na pracę z zaawansowanymi funkcjami RetroArch, takimi jak odtwarzanie sieciowe oparte na cofaniu i redukcja opóźnień. Zawiera presety wejściowe do automatycznego mapowania przycisków dla różnych gier, w tym układy gier walki dla nowoczesnych i oldschoolowych kontrolerów arcade (aka fightsticków).

Uruchamia gry z automatów:

- Capcom CPS-1
- Capcom CPS-2
- Capcom CPS-3
- Cave
- Sprzęt oparty na Galaxian
- Kaneko 16
- Konami
- Neo-Geo
- Pacman oparty na Iron
- PGM
- Sprzęt oparty na Psikyo 68EC020
- Sega System 1, System 16 (i podobne), System 18, X-Board i Y-Board
- Toaplan 1
- Toaplan 2
- Taito F2, X, Z i inne</text>
			<text lang="ru">Эмулятор аркадных игр. Проект с открытым исходным кодом, его программирует группа людей, известная как FBA Team.

Запускает игры с автоматов:

Capcom CPS-1
Capcom CPS-2
Capcom CPS-3
Cave
Железо на базе Galaxian
Kaneko 16
Konami
Neo-Geo
Железо на базе Pacman
PGM
Железо на базе Psikyo 68EC020
Sega System 1, System 16 (и схожие), System 18, X-Board и Y-Board
Toaplan 1
Toaplan 2
Taito F2, X, Z и другие</text>
			<text lang="es">Final Burn Neo (también conocido como FBNeo) es la nueva rama oficial del emulador Final Burn Alpha, compatible con cientos de juegos arcade y de consola. El núcleo libretro de FBNeo lleva su biblioteca de títulos compatibles a RetroArch, donde la estrecha integración del núcleo con la API libretro le permite trabajar con las funciones avanzadas de retroceso de RetroArch, como el juego en red basado en rollback y la reducción de latencia runahead. Incluye preajustes de entrada para el mapeado automático de botones para diferentes juegos, incluyendo diseños de juegos de lucha para controles arcade modernos y de la vieja escuela (también conocidos como fightsticks).</text>
			<text lang="de">Final Burn Neo (alias FBNeo) ist der neue offizielle Zweig des Final Burn Alpha-Emulators, der mit Hunderten von Arcade- und Konsolenspielen kompatibel ist. Der libretro-Kern von FBNeo bringt seine Bibliothek kompatibler Titel nach RetroArch, wo die enge Integration des Kerns in die libretro-API es ermöglicht, mit den fortschrittlichen Zeitverschiebungsfunktionen von RetroArch wie Rollback-basiertem Netplay und Runahead-Latenzreduzierung zu arbeiten. Es enthält Eingabevoreinstellungen für die automatische Zuordnung von Tasten für verschiedene Spiele, einschließlich Kampfspiel-Layouts für moderne und Old-School-Arcade-Steuerungen (aka Fightsticks).</text>
			<text lang="fr">Final Burn Neo (aka FBNeo) est la nouvelle branche officielle de l'émulateur Final Burn Alpha, qui est compatible avec des centaines de jeux d'arcade et de console. Le noyau libretro de FBNeo apporte sa bibliothèque de titres compatibles à RetroArch, où l'intégration étroite du noyau avec l'API libretro lui permet de travailler avec les fonctionnalités avancées de RetroArch comme le rollback-based netplay et la réduction de la latence runahead. Il comprend des préréglages d'entrée pour l'affectation automatique des boutons à différents jeux, y compris des dispositions de jeux de combat pour les commandes d'arcade modernes et anciennes (alias bâtons de combat).</text>
			<text lang="it">Final Burn Neo (alias FBNeo) è il nuovo ramo ufficiale dell'emulatore Final Burn Alpha, compatibile con centinaia di giochi arcade e per console. Il nucleo libretro di FBNeo porta la sua libreria di titoli compatibili a RetroArch, dove la stretta integrazione con le API libretro gli permette di lavorare con le funzioni avanzate di time-bending di RetroArch, come il netplay basato sul rollback e la riduzione della latenza runahead. Include preset di input per la mappatura automatica dei pulsanti per diversi giochi, compresi i layout dei giochi di combattimento per i controlli arcade moderni e della vecchia scuola (alias fightstick).</text>
			<text lang="pt">Final Burn Neo (também conhecido como FBNeo) é uma nova versão oficial do emulador Final Burn Alpha, compatível com centenas de jogos de arcade e console. O núcleo libretro do FBNeo transfere a biblioteca de títulos compatíveis para o RetroArch, onde a integração estreita com a API libretro permite o uso de recursos avançados do RetroArch, como rollback netplay e redução de lag. Ele inclui presets de entrada para mapeamento automático de botões para vários jogos, incluindo layouts de jogos de luta para controladores de arcade modernos e antigos (também conhecidos como fight sticks).

Executa jogos de arcade:

- Capcom CPS-1
- Capcom CPS-2
- Capcom CPS-3
- Cave
- Hardware baseado em Galaxian
- Kaneko 16
- Konami
- Neo-Geo
- Pacman baseado em Iron
- PGM
- Hardware baseado em Psikyo 68EC020
- Sega System 1, System 16 (e similares), System 18, X-Board e Y-Board
- Toaplan 1
- Toaplan 2
- Taito F2, X, Z e outros</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
