<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2019</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Fury</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Ion Fury is a new Build Engine game from the creators of the EDuke32 source port.

3D Realms and Voidpoint are proud to bring back the Build engine, which powered Duke Nukem 3D, Blood, and Shadow Warrior, in all of its hand-crafted pixelated glory. They’ve spent a lot of time tinkering under the hood to take advantage of new technology and techniques. Bigger levels, hundreds of new colors, and morphing maps that transform mid-level are all just a few of the advancements made to the engine.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Ion Fury to gra i nowy Build Engine od twórców źródłowego portu EDuke32.

3D Realms i Voidpoint z dumą przywracają Build Engine, który napędzał Duke Nukem 3D, Blood i Shadow Warrior, w całej jego ręcznie wykonanej pikselowej chwale. Spędzili mnóstwo czasu majstrując pod maską, aby wykorzystać nowe technologie i techniki. Większe poziomy, setki nowych kolorów i mapy morfingu, które przekształcają się w połowie poziomu to tylko niektóre z ulepszeń silnika.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Ion Fury - это новая игра на Build Engine от создателей исходного порта EDuke32.

3D Realms и Voidpoint с гордостью возвращают движок Build, на котором были созданы Duke Nukem 3D, Blood и Shadow Warrior, во всей его пиксельной красе, созданной вручную. Они потратили много времени на доработку движка, чтобы использовать преимущества новых технологий и методов. Большие уровни, сотни новых цветов, трансформация карты в середине уровня - вот лишь некоторые из усовершенствований, внесенных в движок.</text>
			<text lang="es">Ion Fury es un nuevo juego de Build Engine de los creadores del port fuente EDuke32.

3D Realms y Voidpoint se enorgullecen de traer de vuelta el motor Build, que impulsó Duke Nukem 3D, Blood y Shadow Warrior, en toda su gloria pixelada hecha a mano. Han pasado mucho tiempo retocando el motor para aprovechar las nuevas tecnologías y técnicas. Niveles más grandes, cientos de colores nuevos y mapas morphing que se transforman a mitad de nivel son sólo algunos de los avances realizados en el motor.</text>
			<text lang="de">Ion Fury ist ein neues Build-Engine-Spiel von den Machern der EDuke32-Quellcode-Portierung.

3D Realms und Voidpoint sind stolz darauf, die Build-Engine, die Duke Nukem 3D, Blood und Shadow Warrior angetrieben hat, in all ihrer handgefertigten, pixeligen Pracht wieder aufleben zu lassen. Sie haben viel Zeit damit verbracht, unter der Haube zu tüfteln, um die Vorteile neuer Technologien und Techniken zu nutzen. Größere Levels, Hunderte neuer Farben und Morphing-Maps, die sich in der Mitte des Levels verwandeln, sind nur einige der Verbesserungen, die an der Engine vorgenommen wurden.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Ion Fury est un nouveau jeu Build Engine des créateurs du portage source EDuke32.

3D Realms et Voidpoint sont fiers de ramener le moteur Build, qui a fait fonctionner Duke Nukem 3D, Blood et Shadow Warrior, dans toute sa gloire pixellisée et artisanale. Ils ont passé beaucoup de temps à bricoler sous le capot pour tirer parti des nouvelles technologies et techniques. Des niveaux plus grands, des centaines de nouvelles couleurs et des cartes de morphing qui se transforment à mi-parcours ne sont que quelques-unes des améliorations apportées au moteur.</text>
			<text lang="it">Ion Fury è un nuovo gioco di Build Engine dai creatori del port sorgente di EDuke32.

3D Realms e Voidpoint sono orgogliosi di riportare il motore Build, che ha alimentato Duke Nukem 3D, Blood e Shadow Warrior, in tutta la sua gloria pixelata artigianale. Hanno trascorso molto tempo a lavorare sotto il cofano per sfruttare le nuove tecnologie e tecniche. Livelli più grandi, centinaia di nuovi colori e mappe morphing che si trasformano a metà livello sono solo alcuni dei progressi apportati al motore.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
