<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.43</pos>
			<maxSize>0.26</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.43" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1990</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Sega
Game Gear</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Game Gear is an 8-bit fourth generation handheld game console released by Sega on October 6, 1990 in Japan, in April 1991 throughout North America and Europe, and during 1992 in Australia. The Game Gear primarily competed with Nintendo's Game Boy, the Atari Lynx, and NEC's TurboExpress. It shares much of its hardware with the Master System, and can play Master System games by the use of an adapter. Sega positioned the Game Gear, which had a full-color backlit screen with a landscape format, as a technologically superior handheld to the Game Boy.

Though the Game Gear was rushed to market, its unique game library and price point gave it an edge over the Atari Lynx and TurboExpress. However, due to its short battery life, lack of original games, and weak support from Sega, the Game Gear was unable to surpass the Game Boy, selling 10.62 million units by March 1996. The Game Gear was discontinued on April 30, 1997. It was re-released as a budget system by Majesco Entertainment in 2000, under license from Sega.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Game Gear (ゲームギア, Gēmu gia) est une console de jeux vidéo portable en couleurs, sortie en 1990 et produite par Sega afin de concurrencer la Game Boy de Nintendo apparue une année plus tôt.

En 2001, Majesco relance la production en acquérant les droits de fabrication auprès de Sega ; cette version n'est cependant pas compatible avec certains accessoires. En 2006, Mediatronic lance la Pocket Gear, une réédition compacte sans cartouches de la console avec une vingtaine de jeux Game Gear et Master System inclus. At games rachète aussi les droits pour créer une petite console de 30 jeux incluant Sonic Chaos.

Le 3 juin 2020, Sega a annoncé la Game Gear Micro, une mise à jour de la console originale déclinée en quatre versions et coloris, à savoir gris, jaune, bleu et rouge. Chaque coloris de machine dispose de quatre jeux chacun.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Портативная игровая консоль, выпущенная компанией Sega в 1990 году в качестве ответа консоли Game Boy компании Nintendo. Она стала третьей портативной консолью с цветной графикой, после Atari Lynx и TurboExpress.

Работа над консолью началась в 1989 году под рабочим названием Project Mercury, согласно существовавшей в то время в Sega традиции использовать названия планет в качестве рабочих названий проектов.
Консоль впервые поступила в продажу 6 октября 1990 года в Японии. В США, Европе и Бразилии консоль стала доступна в 1991 году, а в Австралии — в 1992 году.
Sega задалась целью любым способом сделать карманную 8-разрядную игровую систему, которая будет значительно превосходить Game Boy. Так как предыдущая приставка Sega — Master System — превосходила по своим техническим характеристикам 8-разрядные приставки от Nintendo, было решено применить в Game Gear аппаратную часть на основе Master System. Сильнейшее сходство с архитектурой Master System позволяет легкий перенос игр Master System на Game Gear. В отличие от системы Game Boy, система Game Gear имела цветной экран, поддерживала вставляемые в слот для картриджей модули расширения (конвертер для подключения картриджей Master System, приёмник и даже TV-тюнер), консоль было удобно держать в руках, в отличие от Gameboy. К консоли отдельно продавалась специальная линза Super Wide Gear, визуально увеличивающая размер экрана до 5 дюймов против обычных 3,2.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>