<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.47</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.48 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.482 0.444</pos>
			<maxSize>0.216</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.202 0.444" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.47</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.48 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.482 0.444</pos>
			<maxSize>0.206</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.202 0.444" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1984</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Epoch</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Game Pocket Computer</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Epoch Game Pocket Computer (Japanese: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) is a second-generation handheld game console released by Epoch Co. in Japan in 1984 for 12,000 Japanese yen. It is also known as Pokekon and was one of the very few truly handheld systems to be released in the early 1980s, preceding the Game Boy by 5 years.

The system was a bust in Japan, and as a result, only 5 games were made for it. A puzzle game and a paint program were built into the system. It was powered by 4 AA batteries, and screen's contrast could be adjusted by the user. Input and output controls included four buttons, an 8-way joypad, a contrast dial, and a sound on-off switch.

The Game Pocket Computer failed in Japan, and was never released internationally. The device is extremely rare, and units on eBay can go for hundreds of US dollars.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Epoch Game Pocket Computer (japoński: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) to przenośna konsola do gier drugiej generacji wydana przez Epoch Co. w Japonii w 1984 roku za 12 000 jenów japońskich. Jest on również znany jako Pokekon i był jednym z niewielu prawdziwie ręcznych systemów, które zostały wydane na początku lat 80-tych, poprzedzając Game Boy o 5 lat.

System okazał się niewypałem w Japonii, w wyniku czego powstało na niego tylko 5 gier. Gra logiczna i program do malowania były wbudowane w system. Zasilany był przez 4 baterie AA, a kontrast ekranu mógł być regulowany przez użytkownika. Kontrolki wejścia i wyjścia zawierały cztery przyciski, 8-kierunkowy joypad, pokrętło kontrastu i przełącznik włączania i wyłączania dźwięku.

Game Pocket Computer nie odniósł sukcesu w Japonii i nigdy nie został wypuszczony na rynek międzynarodowy. Urządzenie jest niezwykle rzadkie, a egzemplarze na eBay'u mogą kosztować setki dolarów amerykańskich.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Вторая в мире портативная игровая консоль со сменными картриджами, выпущенная компанией Epoch эксклюзивно для японского рынка в 1984 году.

Консоль имела прямоугольную форму размером 21,5 x 14,6 сантиметров толщиной 2,9 сантиметров. Монохромный жидкокристаллический экран размером 75 на 64 пикселя позволял создавать на системе полноценные игры на уровне приставок второго поколения, вроде Atari 2600, Intellivision или Emerson Arcadia 2001.

Для управления играми в нижней части корпуса Game Pocket Computer находились D-pad (8 направлений), 6 кнопок, регулятор контрастности изображения и два выключателя — для включения/выключения консоли и включения/выключения звука. Работал Game Pocket Computer от четырёх AA батареек, заряда которых хватало на 70 часов.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Epoch Game Pocket Computer (japonés: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) es una consola portátil de segunda generación lanzada por Epoch Co. en Japón en 1984 por 12.000 yenes japoneses. También se la conoce como Pokekon y fue una de las pocas consolas realmente portátiles que salieron al mercado a principios de la década de 1980, 5 años antes que la Game Boy.

El sistema fue un fracaso en Japón y, como resultado, sólo se crearon 5 juegos para él. El sistema incluía un juego de puzles y un programa de pintura. Funcionaba con 4 pilas AA y el usuario podía ajustar el contraste de la pantalla. Los controles de entrada y salida incluían cuatro botones, un joypad de 8 direcciones, un dial de contraste y un interruptor de encendido y apagado del sonido.

El Game Pocket Computer fracasó en Japón y nunca salió al mercado internacional. El dispositivo es extremadamente raro, y en eBay se pueden encontrar unidades por cientos de dólares.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Epoch Game Pocket Computer (japanisch: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) ist eine Handheld-Spielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die 1984 von Epoch Co. in Japan für 12.000 japanische Yen veröffentlicht wurde. Es ist auch unter dem Namen Pokekon bekannt und war eines der wenigen echten Handheld-Systeme, die Anfang der 1980er Jahre auf den Markt kamen, fünf Jahre vor dem Game Boy.

Das System war in Japan ein Flop, und so wurden nur 5 Spiele für das System entwickelt. Ein Puzzlespiel und ein Malprogramm waren in das System integriert. Es wurde mit 4 AA-Batterien betrieben, und der Kontrast des Bildschirms konnte vom Benutzer eingestellt werden. Zu den Eingabe- und Ausgabesteuerungen gehörten vier Tasten, ein 8-Wege-Joypad, ein Kontrastregler und ein Schalter zum Ausschalten des Tons.

Der Game Pocket Computer scheiterte in Japan und wurde international nie veröffentlicht. Das Gerät ist extrem selten und wird auf eBay für Hunderte von US-Dollar gehandelt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Epoch Game Pocket Computer (japonais : ゲームポケコン, Hepburn : Gēmupokekon) est une console de jeu portable de deuxième génération commercialisée par Epoch Co. au Japon en 1984 au prix de 12 000 yens japonais. Elle est également connue sous le nom de Pokekon et fut l'une des rares consoles véritablement portables à sortir au début des années 1980, précédant le Game Boy de 5 ans.

La console a été un échec au Japon et, par conséquent, seuls 5 jeux ont été produits pour elle. Un jeu de puzzle et un programme de peinture étaient intégrés au système. Il était alimenté par 4 piles AA et le contraste de l'écran pouvait être réglé par l'utilisateur. Les commandes d'entrée et de sortie comprenaient quatre boutons, un joypad à 8 directions, une molette de réglage du contraste et un interrupteur d'activation et de désactivation du son.

Le Game Pocket Computer a échoué au Japon et n'a jamais été commercialisé à l'étranger. L'appareil est extrêmement rare et, sur eBay, les unités peuvent atteindre des centaines de dollars américains.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'Epoch Game Pocket Computer (giapponese: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) è una console di gioco portatile di seconda generazione rilasciata da Epoch Co. in Giappone nel 1984 al prezzo di 12.000 yen. Conosciuta anche con il nome di Pokekon, è stata una delle pochissime console portatili realmente rilasciate all'inizio degli anni '80, precedendo di 5 anni il Game Boy.

Il sistema è stato un fiasco in Giappone e di conseguenza sono stati realizzati solo 5 giochi. Il sistema includeva un puzzle game e un programma di pittura. Era alimentato da 4 batterie AA e il contrasto dello schermo poteva essere regolato dall'utente. I controlli di ingresso e uscita comprendevano quattro pulsanti, un joypad a 8 direzioni, un selettore di contrasto e un interruttore per l'attivazione e la disattivazione del suono.

Il Game Pocket Computer fallì in Giappone e non fu mai distribuito a livello internazionale. Il dispositivo è estremamente raro e le unità su eBay possono arrivare a centinaia di dollari.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
