<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/gb.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/gb.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">1 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.34 0.45</pos>
			<maxSize>0.15</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.06 0.45" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<video name="videobox2" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/gb.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/gb.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<audio>false</audio>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.66 0.54</pos>
			<maxSize>0.15</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<rotation>180</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.38 0.54" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1989</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Nintendo</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Game Boy (2 Players)</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Nintendo Game Link Cable is an accessory for the Game Boy line of handheld video game systems, allowing players to connect Game Boy's of all types for multiplayer play. Depending on the games, the Game Link Cable can be used to connect two games with the same title, such as Tetris, or two compatible games, such as Pokémon Red and Blue. Games can be linked together to compete, cooperate, trade items, unlock hidden features, etc.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Nintendo Game Link Cable jest akcesorium dla linii Game Boy ręcznych systemów gier wideo, umożliwiając graczom połączenie Game Boy'ów wszystkich typów do gry wieloosobowej. W zależności od gier, kabel Game Link może być używany do łączenia dwóch gier o tym samym tytule, takich jak Tetris, lub dwóch kompatybilnych gier, takich jak Pokémon Red i Blue. Gry można łączyć ze sobą w celu rywalizacji, współpracy, handlu przedmiotami, odblokowywania ukrytych funkcji itp.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La (ou le) Game Boy (ゲームボーイ, Gēmu Bōi) est une console portable de jeu vidéo 8-bits de quatrième génération développée et fabriquée par Nintendo. Mise en vente au Japon le 21 avril 1989, puis en Amérique du Nord en octobre 1989, et enfin en Europe le 28 septembre 1990, elle est la première console portable de la gamme des Game Boy. Elle fut conçue par Gunpei Yokoi et Nintendo Research and Development 1 — la même équipe ayant conçu la série des Game and Watch ainsi que de nombreux jeux à succès sur Nintendo Entertainment System.

Malgré la sortie de consoles portables techniquement plus avancées6, la Game Boy connaît un franc succès. Les modèles Game Boy et Game Boy Color totalisent 118,6 millions d'exemplaires vendus à travers le monde. Dès sa sortie aux États-Unis, plus d'un million d'exemplaires sont vendus en quelques semaines. La production de la console portable s'est achevée en 2003.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Линейка портативных игровых устройств, разработанная и производившаяся Nintendo.
Первый Game Boy был выпущен ещё в 1989 году, как продолжение к известным карманным играм Nintendo Game &amp; Watch. Это была первая популярная портативная игровая система, и многие компании пытались повторить успех Game Boy, но никому сделать этого так и не удалось.

Устройство имело монохромный жидкокристаллический экран с размерами 160×144 пикселей, стереозвук на четыре канала и функцию GameLink, позволяющую соединять две консоли вместе и играть вдвоём в поддерживающие данную технологию игры.

Всякий раз, если по каким-либо причинам продажи Game Boy шли на убыль, Nintendo выпускала новые разновидности Game Boy, чтобы снова увеличить продажи. Таким образом, в ноябре 1996 года появился Game Boy Pocket, который был меньше в размерах на 30 %, чем свой предшественник, но с экраном большего размера и всего с двумя батареями AAA. Позже был выпущен Game Boy Color c цветным экраном, затем — Game Boy Advance.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il cavo Game Link di Nintendo è un accessorio per la linea di console portatili per videogiochi Game Boy, che consente ai giocatori di collegare Game Boy di ogni tipo per giocare in multiplayer. A seconda dei giochi, il cavo Game Link può essere utilizzato per collegare due giochi con lo stesso titolo, come Tetris, o due giochi compatibili, come Pokémon Rosso e Blu. I giochi possono essere collegati tra loro per competere, cooperare, scambiare oggetti, sbloccare funzioni nascoste, ecc.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
