<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.32</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>2001</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>Nintendo
GameCube</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Nintendo GameCube is a home video game console released by Nintendo in Japan and North America in 2001 and in PAL territories in 2002. The GameCube is Nintendo's entry in the sixth generation of video game consoles and is the successor to their previous console, the Nintendo 64. The GameCube competed with Sony's PlayStation 2 and Microsoft's Xbox.

The GameCube is the first Nintendo console to use optical discs as its primary storage medium. The discs are in a miniDVD-based format but the system was not designed to play full-sized DVDs or audio CDs unlike its competitors, and mainly focused on gaming instead. The console supports limited online gaming for a small number of games via a GameCube broadband or modem adapter and can connect to a Game Boy Advance with a link cable, which allows players to access exclusive in-game features using the handheld as a second screen and controller like a Wii U.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">La (ou le) Nintendo GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ, Nintendō Gēmukyūbu, Nintendo Gamecube) est une console de jeux vidéo de salon du fabricant japonais Nintendo, sortie en 2001 (2002 en Europe), développée en association avec IBM, NEC et ATI. Elle fut en concurrence avec la PlayStation 2 de Sony, la Xbox de Microsoft et la Dreamcast de Sega, qui forment ensemble la sixième génération de consoles de jeux vidéo.

Malgré ses excellents jeux, la GameCube ne rencontre pas le succès de ses devancières, avec 5 ans sur le marché des consoles de jeux, elle ne totalise que le score de 22 millions d'unités écoulées. Il y a en France 150 jeux sortis la première année de commercialisation (du 3 mai 2002 au 2 mai 2003), 111 la deuxième année, 80 la troisième, 63 la quatrième. L'un des derniers jeux majeurs développés pour cette console fut The Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess, sorti en France le 15 décembre 2006, et disponible également sur le successeur de la GameCube, la Wii.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Четвёртая домашняя игровая консоль от Nintendo, относится к шестому поколению игровых систем. Предшественник Wii и преемник Nintendo 64.

В отличие от конкурентов того поколения (PlayStation 2 и Xbox) GameCube использует диски на основе mini-DVD вместо полноразмерных DVD. Нет поддержки проигрывания DVD-Video и audio CD, а также возможностей других консолей, использующих полноразмерные оптические диски.

Кроме того, GameCube вводила множество возможностей соединения с консолями Nintendo и была четвёртой консолью после Nintendo 64DD, Famicom Modem и Satellaview, поддерживающей официально онлайн-игру, через широкополосный модем Nintendo GameCube. Она также имела возможность соединяться с Game Boy Advance и получать доступ к исключительным особенностям определённых игр или использовать портативную систему как контроллер для Game Boy Player.

GameCube впервые упоминалась в выпуске № 145 журнала Nintendo Power. Консоль была выпущена 14 сентября 2001 в Японии, 18 ноября 2001 в Северной Америке, 3 мая 2002 в Европе и 17 мая 2002 в Австралии. Nintendo GameCube продалась тиражом в 21,74 миллиона приставок по всему миру.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>