<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysart" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/gamegear.png</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/4K/gamegear.png</path>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.422</pos>
			<maxSize>0.225</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.422" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/gamegear.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/gamegear.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.424</pos>
			<maxSize>0.213</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.424" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
			<video name="videoglich" extra="true">
            <path>./../../_inc/anim/video/glich.mp4</path>
            <delay>0</delay>
            <effect>none</effect>
 			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.422</pos>
			<maxSize>0.215</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<color>FFFFFF50</color>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.422" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1990</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sega</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Game Gear</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant" extra="true">
			<text>ROM Hacks</text>
			<text lang="pl">Hacki rom</text>
			<text lang="ru">Хаки</text>
			<text lang="es">ROM Hacks</text>
			<text lang="de">ROM-Hacks</text>
			<text lang="fr">ROM Hacks</text>
			<text lang="it">ROM Hacks</text>
			<text lang="pt">Hacks de ROM</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Game Gear is an 8-bit fourth generation handheld game console released by Sega on October 6, 1990 in Japan, in April 1991 throughout North America and Europe, and during 1992 in Australia. The Game Gear primarily competed with Nintendo's Game Boy, the Atari Lynx, and NEC's TurboExpress. It shares much of its hardware with the Master System, and can play Master System games by the use of an adapter. Sega positioned the Game Gear, which had a full-color backlit screen with a landscape format, as a technologically superior handheld to the Game Boy.

Though the Game Gear was rushed to market, its unique game library and price point gave it an edge over the Atari Lynx and TurboExpress. However, due to its short battery life, lack of original games, and weak support from Sega, the Game Gear was unable to surpass the Game Boy, selling 10.62 million units by March 1996. The Game Gear was discontinued on April 30, 1997. It was re-released as a budget system by Majesco Entertainment in 2000, under license from Sega.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Sega Game Gear – przenośna konsola firmy Sega, która miała być konkurencją dla konsoli Game Boy. Pod względem technicznym była zdecydowanie lepsza od swojego konkurenta, posiadała m.in. kolorowy wyświetlacz (oryginalny GameBoy był czarno-biały). Podstawową wadą był bardzo duży pobór prądu z baterii, które wystarczały zaledwie na 3 do 5 godzin gry.

Konsola od początku jej sprzedaży w 1990 do końca w 1997 roku została sprzedana w 11 milionach egzemplarzy – do czasu wydania PlayStation Portable Game Gear był najlepiej sprzedającą się konsolą przenośnią niewyprodukowaną przez Nintendo. W 2000 Sega sprzedała licencje na produkcję Game Gear firmie Majesco i mimo iż konsola faktycznie miała szanse przeżyć drugą młodość, to brak jakichkolwiek zmian w jej konstrukcji spowodował, że w 2002 roku Majesco zaprzestało jej produkcji.

Dane techniczne:
- Procesor: Z80 @ 3,58 MHz
- Pamięć RAM: 24kB RAM
- Grafika: 160x144 pikseli, 32 kolory z palety 4096
- Dźwięk: 4 kanały
- Zasilanie: 6 baterii AA, zasilacz lub zewnętrzny akumulator</text>
			<text lang="ru">Портативная игровая консоль, выпущенная компанией Sega в 1990 году в качестве ответа консоли Game Boy компании Nintendo. Она стала третьей портативной консолью с цветной графикой, после Atari Lynx и TurboExpress.

Работа над консолью началась в 1989 году под рабочим названием Project Mercury, согласно существовавшей в то время в Sega традиции использовать названия планет в качестве рабочих названий проектов.
Консоль впервые поступила в продажу 6 октября 1990 года в Японии. В США, Европе и Бразилии консоль стала доступна в 1991 году, а в Австралии — в 1992 году.
Sega задалась целью любым способом сделать карманную 8-разрядную игровую систему, которая будет значительно превосходить Game Boy. Так как предыдущая приставка Sega — Master System — превосходила по своим техническим характеристикам 8-разрядные приставки от Nintendo, было решено применить в Game Gear аппаратную часть на основе Master System. Сильнейшее сходство с архитектурой Master System позволяет легкий перенос игр Master System на Game Gear. В отличие от системы Game Boy, система Game Gear имела цветной экран, поддерживала вставляемые в слот для картриджей модули расширения (конвертер для подключения картриджей Master System, приёмник и даже TV-тюнер), консоль было удобно держать в руках, в отличие от Gameboy. К консоли отдельно продавалась специальная линза Super Wide Gear, визуально увеличивающая размер экрана до 5 дюймов против обычных 3,2.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Game Gear es una videoconsola portátil de 8 bits de cuarta generación lanzada por Sega el 6 de octubre de 1990 en Japón, en abril de 1991 en Norteamérica y Europa, y durante 1992 en Australia. La Game Gear compitió principalmente con la Game Boy de Nintendo, la Atari Lynx y la TurboExpress de NEC. Comparte gran parte de su hardware con la Master System, y puede reproducir juegos de ésta mediante el uso de un adaptador. Sega posicionó la Game Gear, que tenía una pantalla retroiluminada a todo color con formato apaisado, como una consola portátil tecnológicamente superior a la Game Boy.

Aunque la Game Gear salió al mercado con prisas, su biblioteca de juegos única y su precio la situaron por delante de la Atari Lynx y la TurboExpress. Sin embargo, debido a la corta duración de su batería, la falta de juegos originales y el escaso apoyo de Sega, la Game Gear no pudo superar a la Game Boy, vendiendo 10,62 millones de unidades en marzo de 1996. La Game Gear dejó de venderse el 30 de abril de 1997. En 2000, Majesco Entertainment volvió a comercializarla bajo licencia de Sega.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Game Gear ist eine 8-Bit-Handheld-Spielkonsole der vierten Generation, die von Sega am 6. Oktober 1990 in Japan, im April 1991 in Nordamerika und Europa und 1992 in Australien veröffentlicht wurde. Der Game Gear konkurrierte in erster Linie mit dem Game Boy von Nintendo, dem Atari Lynx und dem TurboExpress von NEC. Er teilt einen Großteil seiner Hardware mit dem Master System und kann mit Hilfe eines Adapters Master System-Spiele spielen. Sega positionierte den Game Gear, der über einen hintergrundbeleuchteten Vollfarbbildschirm im Querformat verfügte, als ein dem Game Boy technologisch überlegenes Handheld.

Obwohl der Game Gear in aller Eile auf den Markt gebracht wurde, verschaffte ihm seine einzigartige Spielebibliothek und sein Preis einen Vorteil gegenüber dem Atari Lynx und dem TurboExpress. Aufgrund der kurzen Akkulaufzeit, des Mangels an Originalspielen und des schwachen Supports von Sega konnte der Game Gear den Game Boy jedoch nicht übertreffen. Bis März 1996 wurden 10,62 Millionen Einheiten verkauft. Der Game Gear wurde am 30. April 1997 aus dem Programm genommen. Im Jahr 2000 wurde er von Majesco Entertainment unter Lizenz von Sega als Budget-System wiederveröffentlicht.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Game Gear est une console de jeu portable 8 bits de quatrième génération commercialisée par Sega le 6 octobre 1990 au Japon, en avril 1991 en Amérique du Nord et en Europe, et en 1992 en Australie. La Game Gear était principalement en concurrence avec la Game Boy de Nintendo, l'Atari Lynx et la TurboExpress de NEC. Elle partage une grande partie de son matériel avec la Master System et peut jouer aux jeux de la Master System à l'aide d'un adaptateur. Sega a positionné la Game Gear, dotée d'un écran rétroéclairé en couleur et d'un format paysage, comme une console portable technologiquement supérieure à la Game Boy.

Bien que la Game Gear ait été mise sur le marché en toute hâte, sa bibliothèque de jeux unique et son prix lui ont donné un avantage sur l'Atari Lynx et le TurboExpress. Cependant, en raison de la faible autonomie de sa batterie, du manque de jeux originaux et du faible soutien de Sega, la Game Gear n'a pas réussi à surpasser la Game Boy, se vendant à 10,62 millions d'unités en mars 1996. La Game Gear a été abandonnée le 30 avril 1997. Elle a été rééditée en 2000 par Majesco Entertainment, sous licence de Sega, sous la forme d'une console économique.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Game Gear è una console portatile a 8 bit di quarta generazione, rilasciata da Sega il 6 ottobre 1990 in Giappone, nell'aprile 1991 in Nord America e in Europa e nel 1992 in Australia. Il Game Gear competeva principalmente con il Game Boy di Nintendo, l'Atari Lynx e il TurboExpress di NEC. Condivide gran parte dell'hardware con il Master System e può far girare con i giochi del Master System utilizzando un adattatore. Sega ha posizionato il Game Gear, che aveva uno schermo retroilluminato a colori e un formato orizzontale, come una console portatile tecnologicamente superiore al Game Boy.

Sebbene il Game Gear sia stato lanciato sul mercato molto velocemente, la sua libreria di giochi unica e il suo prezzo gli permisero di avere un vantaggio rispetto all'Atari Lynx e al TurboExpress. Tuttavia, a causa della breve durata della batteria, della mancanza di giochi originali e del debole supporto di Sega, il Game Gear non riuscì a superare il Game Boy, vendendo 10,62 milioni di unità nel marzo 1996. Il Game Gear fu dismesso il 30 aprile 1997. È stato ripresentato come sistema economico da Majesco Entertainment nel 2000, su licenza di Sega.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Sega Game Gear – console portátil da Sega, que pretendia competir com o Game Boy. Tecnicamente, era superior ao seu rival, possuindo, entre outras características, uma tela colorida (o Game Boy original era monocromático). Sua principal desvantagem era o alto consumo de energia da bateria, que durava apenas de 3 a 5 horas de jogo.

A console foi lançada em 1990 e descontinuada em 1997, vendendo 11 milhões de unidades – até o lançamento do PlayStation Portable, o Game Gear era o console portátil mais vendido que não era produzido pela Nintendo. Em 2000, a Sega licenciou a produção do Game Gear para a Majesco e, embora a console realmente tivesse chances de reviver, a falta de qualquer mudança em seu design fez com que a Majesco interrompesse sua produção em 2002.

Especificações técnicas:
- Processador: Z80 @ 3,58 MHz
- Memória RAM: 24kB RAM
- Gráficos: 160x144 pixels, 32 cores de uma paleta de 4096
- Som: 4 canais
- Alimentação: 6 baterias AA, fonte de alimentação ou bateria externa</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
