<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.495</pos>
			<maxSize>0.342</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.495" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.493</pos>
			<maxSize>0.33</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.493" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2001</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>GamePark</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>GP32</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The GP32 (GamePark 32) is a handheld game console developed by the South Korean company Game Park. It was released on November 23, 2001, in South Korea and distributed in some parts of Europe.
The overall design is not unlike the original version of the Game Boy Advance. The GP32 is based on a 133 MHz ARM 9 CPU and 8 MB of SDRAM. Unlike other handheld gaming systems, which tend to be proprietary cartridge-based, the GP32 uses SmartMedia cards (SMC) for storing programs and data, making it accessible for amateur developers as no further development hardware is required.

The console has a eight-way microswitch based mini-joystick controller, two main buttons ('A' and 'B'), two shoulder buttons on each side of the SMC slot ('L' and 'R') and two other menu buttons on each side of the screen ('SELECT' and 'START'), made from a softer, translucent rubber. The console also has a USB 1.1 port for connection with a host computer, a serial expansion port, a 3.3 V power adapter input, a headphone connector and a rear compartment that holds two AA-sized batteries.</text>
			<text lang="pl">GP32 (GamePark 32) to przenośna konsola do gier opracowana przez południowokoreańską firmę Game Park. Została wydana 23 listopada 2001 roku w Korei Południowej i dystrybuowana w niektórych częściach Europy.
Ogólny wygląd nie różni się od oryginalnej wersji Game Boy Advance. GP32 bazuje na procesorze ARM 9 133 MHz i 8 MB pamięci SDRAM. W odróżnieniu od innych przenośnych systemów do gier, które zazwyczaj są oparte na kasetach, konsola GP32 wykorzystuje karty SmartMedia (SMC) do przechowywania programów i danych, dzięki czemu jest dostępna dla amatorskich programistów, ponieważ nie wymaga dodatkowego sprzętu.

Konsola jest wyposażona w ośmiokierunkowy kontroler mini-joystick oparty na mikroprzełącznikach, dwa przyciski główne ("A" i "B"), dwa przyciski naramienne po obu stronach gniazda SMC ("L" i "R") oraz dwa inne przyciski menu po obu stronach ekranu ("SELECT" i "START"), wykonane z miękkiej, półprzezroczystej gumy. Konsola ma także port USB 1.1 do połączenia z komputerem głównym, port szeregowy, wejście zasilacza 3,3 V, złącze słuchawkowe oraz tylną komorę, w której mieszczą się dwie baterie AA.</text>
			<text lang="ru">GP32 основана на микропроцессоре архитектуры ARM с частотой 133 МГц и использует 8 мегабайт оперативной памяти. В отличие от других портативных консолей, среди которых имеется тенденция использования проприетарных сменных картриджей и носителей, в данной консоли для хранения программ и данных используются стандартные карты памяти SmartMedia, что упрощает разработку программистам-любителям.

Консоль имеет 4-х позиционный миниджойстик, 2 главные кнопки ('A' и 'B'), две торцевые на каждой стороне от слота для карт ('L' и 'R') и две кнопки меню справа и слева от экрана ('SELECT' и 'START'). Для связи с компьютером используется порт USB v1.1, также имеется последовательный порт для расширения, разъем питания на 3.3 вольта, выход на наушники. Питается консоль от 2 батарей AA.</text>
			<text lang="es">La GP32 (GamePark 32) es una videoconsola portátil desarrollada por la empresa surcoreana Game Park. Salió a la venta el 23 de noviembre de 2001 en Corea del Sur y se distribuyó en algunas partes de Europa.
El diseño general no difiere mucho de la versión original de la Game Boy Advance. La GP32 se basa en una CPU ARM 9 de 133 MHz y 8 MB de SDRAM. A diferencia de otros sistemas de juego portátiles, que suelen basarse en cartuchos propietarios, la GP32 utiliza tarjetas SmartMedia (SMC) para almacenar programas y datos, lo que la hace accesible para desarrolladores aficionados al no necesitar más hardware de desarrollo.

La consola cuenta con un mando minijoystick basado en un microinterruptor de ocho direcciones, dos botones principales ('A' y 'B'), dos botones de hombro a cada lado de la ranura SMC ('L' y 'R') y otros dos botones de menú a cada lado de la pantalla ('SELECT' y 'START'), fabricados con una goma más suave y translúcida. La consola también dispone de un puerto USB 1.1 para la conexión con un ordenador central, un puerto de expansión serie, una entrada para adaptador de corriente de 3,3 V, un conector para auriculares y un compartimento trasero para dos pilas de tamaño AA.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das GP32 (GamePark 32) ist eine von der südkoreanischen Firma Game Park entwickelte Handheld-Spielkonsole. Sie wurde am 23. November 2001 in Südkorea veröffentlicht und in einigen Teilen Europas vertrieben.
Das Design ist der ursprünglichen Version des Game Boy Advance nicht unähnlich. Der GP32 basiert auf einer 133 MHz ARM 9 CPU und 8 MB SDRAM. Im Gegensatz zu anderen Handheld-Spielsystemen, die in der Regel auf proprietären Kassetten basieren, verwendet der GP32 SmartMedia-Karten (SMC) zum Speichern von Programmen und Daten, was ihn auch für Amateurentwickler zugänglich macht, da keine weitere Entwicklungshardware erforderlich ist.

Die Konsole verfügt über einen 8-Wege-Mikroschalter-basierten Mini-Joystick-Controller, zwei Haupttasten ('A' und 'B'), zwei Schultertasten auf jeder Seite des SMC-Steckplatzes ('L' und 'R') und zwei weitere Menütasten auf jeder Seite des Bildschirms ('SELECT' und 'START'), die aus einem weicheren, durchsichtigen Gummi bestehen. Die Konsole verfügt außerdem über einen USB 1.1-Anschluss für die Verbindung mit einem Host-Computer, einen seriellen Erweiterungsanschluss, einen 3,3-V-Netzteileingang, einen Kopfhöreranschluss und ein rückwärtiges Fach für zwei Batterien der Größe AA.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La GP32 (GamePark 32) est une console de jeu portable développée par la société sud-coréenne Game Park. Elle est sortie le 23 novembre 2001 en Corée du Sud et a été distribuée dans certaines parties de l'Europe.
Son design général n'est pas sans rappeler la version originale du Game Boy Advance. Le GP32 est basé sur un processeur ARM 9 à 133 MHz et 8 Mo de SDRAM. Contrairement à d'autres systèmes de jeu portables, qui ont tendance à être basés sur des cartouches propriétaires, le GP32 utilise des cartes SmartMedia (SMC) pour stocker les programmes et les données, ce qui le rend accessible aux développeurs amateurs car aucun autre matériel de développement n'est nécessaire.

La console est équipée d'un mini-joystick à huit positions, de deux boutons principaux ('A' et 'B'), de deux boutons d'épaule de chaque côté de l'emplacement SMC ('L' et 'R') et de deux autres boutons de menu de chaque côté de l'écran ('SELECT' et 'START'), fabriqués dans un caoutchouc translucide plus souple. La console dispose également d'un port USB 1.1 pour la connexion avec un ordinateur hôte, d'un port d'extension série, d'une entrée pour adaptateur d'alimentation de 3,3 V, d'un connecteur pour casque d'écoute et d'un compartiment arrière pouvant contenir deux piles de taille AA.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il GP32 (GamePark 32) è una console portatile sviluppata dall'azienda sudcoreana Game Park. È stata rilasciata il 23 novembre 2001 in Corea del Sud e distribuita in alcune parti d'Europa.
Il design generale non è dissimile dalla versione originale del Game Boy Advance. Il GP32 è basato su una CPU ARM 9 da 133 MHz e 8 MB di SDRAM. A differenza di altri sistemi di gioco portatili, che tendono a essere basati su cartucce proprietarie, il GP32 utilizza schede SmartMedia (SMC) per la memorizzazione di programmi e dati, rendendolo accessibile agli sviluppatori amatoriali, in quanto non richiede ulteriore hardware di sviluppo.

La console è dotata di un controller mini-joystick a otto vie basato su microinterruttori, due pulsanti principali ("A" e "B"), due pulsanti a spalla su ciascun lato dello slot SMC ("L" e "R") e altri due pulsanti di menu su ciascun lato dello schermo ("SELECT" e "START"), realizzati in una gomma morbida e traslucida. La console dispone anche di una porta USB 1.1 per il collegamento con un computer host, di una porta di espansione seriale, di un ingresso per l'alimentatore da 3,3 V, di un connettore per le cuffie e di uno scomparto posteriore per due batterie AA.</text>
			<text lang="pt">GP32 (GamePark 32) é um console portátil de videogame desenvolvido pela empresa sul-coreana Game Park. Foi lançado em 23 de novembro de 2001 na Coreia do Sul e distribuído em algumas partes da Europa.

O design geral não difere da versão original do Game Boy Advance. O GP32 é baseado em um processador ARM 9 de 133 MHz e 8 MB de memória SDRAM. Ao contrário de outros sistemas portáteis de jogos, que normalmente são baseados em cartuchos, o console GP32 usa cartões SmartMedia (SMC) para armazenar programas e dados, tornando-o acessível a desenvolvedores amadores, pois não exige hardware adicional.

O console é equipado com um mini joystick de oito direções baseado em microinterruptores, dois botões principais ("A" e "B"), dois botões de ombro de cada lado do slot SMC ("L" e "R") e dois outros botões de menu de cada lado da tela ("SELECT" e "START"), feitos de borracha macia e translúcida. O console também possui uma porta USB 1.1 para conexão a um computador principal, uma porta serial, uma entrada de energia de 3,3 V, uma tomada de fone de ouvido e um compartimento traseiro que acomoda duas pilhas AA.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
