<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2011</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Hydra Castle Labyrinth</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Hydra Castle Labyrinth, originally Meikyuujou Hydra, is a freeware Indie platformer developed by E. Hashimoto, a.k.a. Buster, and released on his website. The original game was entirely in Japanese, but saw a translation patch months after its original creation.

The game hearkens back to early "Metroidvania" games like Knightmare II: The Maze of Galious and Legacy of the Wizard: the player explores an immense maze-like dungeon, collecting tools and keys that allow them to proceed deeper. Certain areas are cordoned off from the main dungeon area, and each presents a more linear zone with a boss at the end. The player can find new equipment to make themselves stronger as well.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Hydra Castle Labyrinth, oryginalnie Meikyuujou Hydra, to darmowa platformówka Indie opracowana przez E. Hashimoto, a.k.a. Buster, i wydana na jego stronie internetowej. Oryginalna gra była w całości w języku japońskim, ale doczekała się łatki tłumaczącej kilka miesięcy po jej oryginalnym stworzeniu.

Gra nawiązuje do wczesnych "Metroidvania" gier, takich jak Knightmare II: The Maze of Galious i Legacy of the Wizard: gracz bada ogromny labirynt-jak loch, zbierając narzędzia i klucze, które pozwalają im przejść głębiej. Niektóre obszary są odgrodzone od głównego obszaru lochu, a każdy z nich przedstawia bardziej liniową strefę z bossem na końcu.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Hydra Castle Labyrinth, первоначально Meikyuujou Hydra, - это бесплатный инди-платформер, разработанный Э. Хашимото, он же Buster, и выпущенный на его сайте. Оригинальная игра была полностью на японском языке, но через несколько месяцев после ее создания был выпущен патч с переводом.

Игра напоминает ранние "Metroidvania" игры, такие как Knightmare II: The Maze of Galious и Legacy of the Wizard: игрок исследует огромное подземелье, похожее на лабиринт, собирая инструменты и ключи, которые позволяют ему пройти глубже. Некоторые области отделены от основной части подземелья, и каждая представляет собой более линейную зону с боссом в конце. Игрок может найти новое снаряжение, чтобы сделать себя сильнее.</text>
			<text lang="es">Hydra Castle Labyrinth, originalmente Meikyuujou Hydra, es un juego gratuito de plataformas Indie desarrollado por E. Hashimoto, alias Buster, y publicado en su página web. El juego original estaba íntegramente en japonés, pero recibió un parche de traducción meses después de su creación.

El juego recuerda a los primeros "metroidvania", como Knightmare II: The Maze of Galious y Legacy of the Wizard: el jugador explora una inmensa mazmorra laberíntica, recogiendo herramientas y llaves que le permiten adentrarse en ella. Ciertas áreas están separadas de la mazmorra principal, y cada una presenta una zona más lineal con un jefe al final. El jugador también puede encontrar nuevo equipo para hacerse más fuerte.</text>
			<text lang="de">Hydra Castle Labyrinth, ursprünglich Meikyuujou Hydra, ist ein Freeware-Indie-Platformer, der von E. Hashimoto, alias Buster, entwickelt und auf seiner Website veröffentlicht wurde. Das ursprüngliche Spiel war komplett auf Japanisch, wurde aber Monate nach seiner Entstehung mit einem Übersetzungspatch versehen.

Das Spiel erinnert an frühe "Metroidvania"-Spiele wie Knightmare II: The Maze of Galious und Legacy of the Wizard: Der Spieler erkundet ein riesiges, labyrinthartiges Verlies und sammelt Werkzeuge und Schlüssel, die es ihm ermöglichen, tiefer vorzudringen. Bestimmte Bereiche sind vom Hauptbereich des Verlieses abgegrenzt und stellen jeweils eine linearere Zone mit einem Endgegner am Ende dar. Der Spieler kann auch neue Ausrüstung finden, um sich zu stärken.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Hydra Castle Labyrinth, à l'origine Meikyuujou Hydra, est un jeu de plateforme indépendant gratuit développé par E. Hashimoto, alias Buster, et publié sur son site web. Le jeu original était entièrement en japonais, mais a bénéficié d'un patch de traduction quelques mois après sa création.

Le jeu rappelle les premiers jeux de type "Metroidvania" tels que Knightmare II : The Maze of Galious et Legacy of the Wizard : le joueur explore un immense donjon en forme de labyrinthe, collectant des outils et des clés qui lui permettent d'aller plus loin. Certaines zones sont isolées de la zone principale du donjon, et chacune présente une zone plus linéaire avec un boss à la fin. Le joueur peut également trouver de nouveaux équipements pour se renforcer.</text>
			<text lang="it">Hydra Castle Labyrinth, originariamente Meikyuujou Hydra, è un platform Indie freeware sviluppato da E. Hashimoto, alias Buster, e pubblicato sul suo sito web. Il gioco originale era interamente in giapponese, ma ha ricevuto una patch di traduzione mesi dopo la sua creazione.

Il gioco ricorda i primi "Metroidvania" come Knightmare II: The Maze of Galious e Legacy of the Wizard: il giocatore esplora un immenso dungeon simile a un labirinto, raccogliendo strumenti e chiavi che gli permettono di procedere in profondità. Alcune aree sono isolate dalla zona principale del dungeon e ognuna presenta una zona più lineare con un boss alla fine. Il giocatore può anche trovare nuovi equipaggiamenti per diventare più forte.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
