<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.48 0.395</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2 0.395" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1979</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>Mattel
Intellivision</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Intellivision is a home video game console released by Mattel Electronics in 1979. The name Intellivision is a portmanteau of "intelligent television". Development of the console began in 1977, the same year as the introduction of its main competitor, the Atari 2600. From 1980 to 1983 over 3 million Intellivision units were sold. In 1984 Mattel sold their video game assets to a former Mattel Electronics executive and investors who formed an entity that became INTV Corporation. Games development, which had started in 1978, continued until 1990 when the Intellivision was discontinued.

In 2009, video game website IGN named the Intellivision the No. 14 greatest video game console of all time. It remained Mattel's only video game console until the release of the HyperScan in 2006.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Intellivision est une console de jeux vidéo produite par Mattel et sortie en 1979. Le développement de la console a commencé en 1978, moins d'une année après l'introduction de sa principale concurrente, l'Atari 2600.

En 1982 sortit l'Intellivoice Synthesis Voice Module. Le périphérique se branchait sur le lecteur cartouche de la console (l'add-on le substituait avec son propre lecteur). Le module pouvait améliorer le son, ce qui délivrait la capacité de synthétiser des voix audibles dans les jeux compatibles (même si la technologie est sommaire, ce qui fait que les voix soient robotiques). Les ventes furent décevantes, le périphérique est abandonné l'année suivante, même si des versions internationales devaient suivre. La faute au prix du module, 100 $ sans jeux inclus, mais également au prix des jeux, 45 $ qui chutaient lentement par rapport aux jeux classiques ainsi qu'à la ludothèque faible composée de seulement 5 jeux : B-17 Bomber, Bomb Squad, Space Spartans, Tron Solar Sailer et Intellivision World Series Baseball.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка, выпущенная на рынок компанией Mattel в 1979 году. Разработка консоли началась в 1978 году, менее чем через год после выхода её основного конкурента — Atari 2600. Название «Intellivision» составлено из слов «intelligent television» — «интеллектуальное телевидение».

Создание Intellivision началось, как и в случае с многими другими игровыми приставками 80-х годов, под влиянием высоких продаж Atari VCS. Сбросить короля с трона компания Mattel намеревалась при помощи достаточно продвинутой по тем временам графики, неплохих игр (по большей части спортивных) и главной «опции» — дополнительной клавиатуры, превращавшей детскую игрушку в полновесный домашний компьютер.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>