<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.48 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.48 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.20 0.4" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.48 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.48 0.395</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2 0.395" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1979</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Mattel</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Intellivision</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Intellivision is a home video game console released by Mattel Electronics in 1979. The name Intellivision is a portmanteau of "intelligent television". Development of the console began in 1977, the same year as the introduction of its main competitor, the Atari 2600. From 1980 to 1983 over 3 million Intellivision units were sold. In 1984 Mattel sold their video game assets to a former Mattel Electronics executive and investors who formed an entity that became INTV Corporation. Games development, which had started in 1978, continued until 1990 when the Intellivision was discontinued.

In 2009, video game website IGN named the Intellivision the No. 14 greatest video game console of all time. It remained Mattel's only video game console until the release of the HyperScan in 2006.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Intellivision – konsola gier wideo drugiej generacji wydana przez Mattel Electronics w 1979 roku. Nazwa Intellivision pochodzi od skrzyżowania słów "intelligent television". Druga najlepiej sprzedająca się konsola drugiej generacji (po Atari 2600), sprzedano ją w około 3 milionach egzemplarzy, wydano na nią 125 gier.

Dane techniczne:
- 16-bitowy procesor General Instrument CP1600 894.886 kHz, 1 mHz w wersji PAL/SECAM
- RAM: 1465 bitów
- ROM: 7168 bitów
- Chip graficzny: General Instrument AY-3-8900/AY-3-8900-1
- Rozdzielczość 159x96 pikseli
- 16-kolorowa paleta
- Maksymalna liczba spritów - 8
- Chip audio: General Instrument AY-3-8914
- Trzy kanały dźwięku w tym generator szumu(noise)</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка, выпущенная на рынок компанией Mattel в 1979 году. Разработка консоли началась в 1978 году, менее чем через год после выхода её основного конкурента — Atari 2600. Название «Intellivision» составлено из слов «intelligent television» — «интеллектуальное телевидение».

Создание Intellivision началось, как и в случае с многими другими игровыми приставками 80-х годов, под влиянием высоких продаж Atari VCS. Сбросить короля с трона компания Mattel намеревалась при помощи достаточно продвинутой по тем временам графики, неплохих игр (по большей части спортивных) и главной «опции» — дополнительной клавиатуры, превращавшей детскую игрушку в полновесный домашний компьютер.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Intellivision es una videoconsola doméstica lanzada por Mattel Electronics en 1979. El nombre Intellivision es un portmanteau de "televisión inteligente". El desarrollo de la consola comenzó en 1977, el mismo año en que se presentó su principal competidora, la Atari 2600. Entre 1980 y 1983 se vendieron más de 3 millones de unidades de Intellivision. En 1984, Mattel vendió sus activos de videojuegos a un antiguo ejecutivo de Mattel Electronics y a inversores que formaron una entidad que se convirtió en INTV Corporation. El desarrollo de juegos, que había comenzado en 1978, continuó hasta 1990, año en que se dejó de fabricar la Intellivision.

En 2009, el sitio web de videojuegos IGN nombró a la Intellivision la videoconsola número 14 de todos los tiempos. Siguió siendo la única videoconsola de Mattel hasta el lanzamiento de la HyperScan en 2006.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Intellivision ist eine Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch, die 1979 von Mattel Electronics auf den Markt gebracht wurde. Der Name Intellivision ist ein Portmanteau von "intelligent television". Die Entwicklung der Konsole begann 1977, im selben Jahr wie die Einführung ihres Hauptkonkurrenten, des Atari 2600. Von 1980 bis 1983 wurden über 3 Millionen Intellivision-Geräte verkauft. 1984 verkaufte Mattel seine Videospiel-Aktiva an eine ehemalige Führungskraft von Mattel Electronics und Investoren, die ein Unternehmen gründeten, das zur INTV Corporation wurde. Die Entwicklung von Spielen, die 1978 begonnen hatte, wurde bis 1990 fortgesetzt, als das Intellivision eingestellt wurde.

Im Jahr 2009 kürte die Videospiel-Website IGN das Intellivision zur Nr. 14 der besten Videospielkonsolen aller Zeiten. Sie blieb die einzige Videospielkonsole von Mattel bis zur Veröffentlichung des HyperScan im Jahr 2006.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Intellivision est une console de jeux vidéo de salon commercialisée par Mattel Electronics en 1979. Le nom Intellivision est un portmanteau de "intelligent television" (télévision intelligente). Le développement de la console a commencé en 1977, la même année que l'introduction de son principal concurrent, l'Atari 2600. De 1980 à 1983, plus de 3 millions d'Intellivision ont été vendues. En 1984, Mattel a vendu ses actifs dans le domaine des jeux vidéo à un ancien cadre de Mattel Electronics et à des investisseurs qui ont formé une entité qui est devenue INTV Corporation. Le développement des jeux, qui avait commencé en 1978, s'est poursuivi jusqu'en 1990, date à laquelle l'Intellivision a été abandonnée.

En 2009, le site web de jeux vidéo IGN a désigné l'Intellivision comme la 14e plus grande console de jeux vidéo de tous les temps. Elle est restée la seule console de jeux vidéo de Mattel jusqu'à la sortie de l'HyperScan en 2006.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'Intellivision è una console per videogiochi domestica rilasciata da Mattel Electronics nel 1979. Il nome Intellivision è una crasi di "intelligent television". Lo sviluppo della console iniziò nel 1977, lo stesso anno dell'introduzione del suo principale concorrente, l'Atari 2600. Dal 1980 al 1983 sono state vendute oltre 3 milioni di unità Intellivision. Nel 1984 Mattel vendette i propri asset videoludici a un ex dirigente di Mattel Electronics e a degli investitori che formarono un'entità che divenne INTV Corporation. Lo sviluppo dei giochi, iniziato nel 1978, continuò fino al 1990, quando l'Intellivision fu dismesso.

Nel 2009, il sito web di videogiochi IGN ha nominato l'Intellivision la più grande console per videogiochi di tutti i tempi. Rimase l'unica console per videogiochi di Mattel fino all'uscita dell'HyperScan nel 2006.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
