<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.497 0.42</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.217 0.42" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.42</pos>
			<maxSize>0.2</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.42" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2006</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Java 2 Micro Edition</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Java Platform, Micro Edition or Java ME is a computing platform for development and deployment of portable code for embedded and mobile devices (micro-controllers, sensors, gateways, mobile phones, personal digital assistants, TV set-top boxes, printers). Java ME was formerly known as Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition or J2ME. As of December 22, 2006, the Java ME source code is licensed under the GNU General Public License, and is released under the project name phoneME.

There are more than 2.1 billion Java ME enabled mobile phones and PDAs. It was popular in sub-$200 devices such as Nokia's Series 40. It was also used on the Bada operating system and on Symbian OS along with native software. Users of Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo and Android can download Java ME for their respective environments ("proof-of-concept" for Android).</text>
			<text lang="pl">Java Platform, Micro Edition lub Java ME to platforma obliczeniowa do tworzenia i wdrażania przenośnego kodu dla urządzeń wbudowanych i mobilnych (mikrokontrolerów, czujników, bramek, telefonów komórkowych, osobistych asystentów cyfrowych, dekoderów telewizyjnych, drukarek). Java ME była wcześniej znana jako Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition lub J2ME. Od 22 grudnia 2006 roku kod źródłowy Java ME jest licencjonowany na zasadach GNU General Public License i jest udostępniany pod nazwą projektu phoneME.

Istnieje ponad 2,1 miliarda telefonów komórkowych i urządzeń PDA obsługujących technologię Java ME. Była ona popularna w urządzeniach za mniej niż 200 dolarów, takich jak Nokia Series 40. Była również używana w systemie operacyjnym Bada oraz w Symbian OS wraz z natywnym oprogramowaniem. Użytkownicy systemów Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo i Android mogą pobrać Javę ME dla swoich środowisk ("proof-of-concept" dla Androida).</text>
			<text lang="ru">Java Platform, Micro Edition (Java ME, ранее — Java 2 Micro Edition, J2ME)

Java ME разработана под руководством Sun Microsystems и является заменой похожей технологии — PersonalJava. Изначально спецификация разрабатывалась в рамках JCP (Java Community Process) как JSR 68. Позже её варианты развились в отдельные JSR. Sun предоставляет образец реализации спецификации, но до недавнего времени не предоставляла бесплатной реализации среды выполнения Java ME для мобильных устройств. 22 декабря 2006 исходный код Java ME был выпущен под лицензией GNU General Public License, проект получил название phoneME.

Отличительными особенностями устройств с ограниченными ресурсами являются ограниченная вычислительная мощность, ограниченный объём памяти, малый размер дисплея, питание от портативной батареи, а также низкоскоростные и недостаточно надёжные коммуникационные возможности. Типичный мобильный телефон середины двухтысячных содержит внутри 32-разрядный RISC-процессор с тактовой частотой 150—250 МГц, имеет объём оперативной памяти около 1—2 Мб, цветной дисплей с разрешением 240x320 пикселей и имеет возможность соединения с Интернетом посредством GPRS или EDGE со скоростью до 474 кбит/с или 3G.</text>
			<text lang="es">Java Platform, Micro Edition o Java ME es una plataforma informática para el desarrollo y despliegue de código portátil para dispositivos embebidos y móviles (microcontroladores, sensores, pasarelas, teléfonos móviles, asistentes digitales personales, descodificadores de TV, impresoras). Java ME se conocía antes como Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition o J2ME. Desde el 22 de diciembre de 2006, el código fuente de Java ME está sujeto a la Licencia Pública General de GNU y se publica con el nombre de proyecto phoneME.

Hay más de 2.100 millones de teléfonos móviles y PDA con Java ME. Fue muy popular en dispositivos de menos de 200 dólares, como los Series 40 de Nokia. También se utilizó en el sistema operativo Bada y en Symbian OS junto con software nativo. Los usuarios de Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo y Android pueden descargar Java ME para sus respectivos entornos ("prueba de concepto" para Android).</text>
			<text lang="de">Java Platform, Micro Edition oder Java ME ist eine Computerplattform für die Entwicklung und den Einsatz von tragbarem Code für eingebettete und mobile Geräte (Mikrocontroller, Sensoren, Gateways, Mobiltelefone, persönliche digitale Assistenten, TV-Set-Top-Boxen, Drucker). Java ME war früher als Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition oder J2ME bekannt. Seit dem 22. Dezember 2006 steht der Quellcode von Java ME unter der GNU General Public License und wird unter dem Projektnamen phoneME veröffentlicht.

Es gibt mehr als 2,1 Milliarden Java ME-fähige Handys und PDAs. Es war in Geräten unter 200 Dollar wie Nokias Series 40 sehr beliebt. Es wurde auch auf dem Bada-Betriebssystem und auf Symbian OS zusammen mit nativer Software verwendet. Benutzer von Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo und Android können Java ME für ihre jeweiligen Umgebungen herunterladen ("proof-of-concept" für Android).</text>
			<text lang="fr">Java Platform, Micro Edition ou Java ME est une plateforme informatique pour le développement et le déploiement de codes portables pour les appareils embarqués et mobiles (microcontrôleurs, capteurs, passerelles, téléphones mobiles, assistants numériques personnels, décodeurs TV, imprimantes). Java ME était auparavant connu sous le nom de Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition ou J2ME. Depuis le 22 décembre 2006, le code source de Java ME est sous licence GNU General Public License et est publié sous le nom de projet phoneME.

Il y a plus de 2,1 milliards de téléphones mobiles et d'assistants personnels équipés de Java ME. Il était populaire dans les appareils à moins de 200 dollars tels que la série 40 de Nokia. Il a également été utilisé sur le système d'exploitation Bada et sur Symbian OS avec des logiciels natifs. Les utilisateurs de Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo et Android peuvent télécharger Java ME pour leurs environnements respectifs ("proof-of-concept" pour Android).</text>
			<text lang="it">Java Platform, Micro Edition o Java ME è una piattaforma informatica per lo sviluppo e la distribuzione di codice portatile per dispositivi embedded e mobili (microcontrollori, sensori, gateway, telefoni cellulari, assistenti digitali personali, decoder TV, stampanti). Java ME era precedentemente noto come Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition o J2ME. Dal 22 dicembre 2006, il codice sorgente di Java ME è rilasciato sotto licenza GNU General Public License, con il nome di progetto phoneME.

Esistono più di 2,1 miliardi di telefoni cellulari e PDA abilitati a Java ME. Era molto diffuso nei dispositivi da meno di 200 dollari, come la Serie 40 di Nokia. È stato utilizzato anche sul sistema operativo Bada e su Symbian OS insieme al software nativo. Gli utenti di Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo e Android possono scaricare Java ME per i rispettivi ambienti ("proof-of-concept" per Android).</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
