<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.42</pos>
			<maxSize>0.2</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.42" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>2006</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Java 2 Micro Edition</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>Java Platform, Micro Edition or Java ME is a computing platform for development and deployment of portable code for embedded and mobile devices (micro-controllers, sensors, gateways, mobile phones, personal digital assistants, TV set-top boxes, printers). Java ME was formerly known as Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition or J2ME. As of December 22, 2006, the Java ME source code is licensed under the GNU General Public License, and is released under the project name phoneME.

There are more than 2.1 billion Java ME enabled mobile phones and PDAs. It was popular in sub-$200 devices such as Nokia's Series 40. It was also used on the Bada operating system and on Symbian OS along with native software. Users of Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo and Android can download Java ME for their respective environments ("proof-of-concept" for Android).</text>
			<text lang="pl">Java Platform, Micro Edition lub Java ME to platforma obliczeniowa do tworzenia i wdrażania przenośnego kodu dla urządzeń wbudowanych i mobilnych (mikrokontrolerów, czujników, bramek, telefonów komórkowych, osobistych asystentów cyfrowych, dekoderów telewizyjnych, drukarek). Java ME była wcześniej znana jako Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition lub J2ME. Od 22 grudnia 2006 roku kod źródłowy Java ME jest licencjonowany na zasadach GNU General Public License i jest udostępniany pod nazwą projektu phoneME.

Istnieje ponad 2,1 miliarda telefonów komórkowych i urządzeń PDA obsługujących technologię Java ME. Była ona popularna w urządzeniach za mniej niż 200 dolarów, takich jak Nokia Series 40. Była również używana w systemie operacyjnym Bada oraz w Symbian OS wraz z natywnym oprogramowaniem. Użytkownicy systemów Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo i Android mogą pobrać Javę ME dla swoich środowisk ("proof-of-concept" dla Androida).</text>
			<text lang="ru">Java Platform, Micro Edition (Java ME, ранее — Java 2 Micro Edition, J2ME)

Java ME разработана под руководством Sun Microsystems и является заменой похожей технологии — PersonalJava. Изначально спецификация разрабатывалась в рамках JCP (Java Community Process) как JSR 68. Позже её варианты развились в отдельные JSR. Sun предоставляет образец реализации спецификации, но до недавнего времени не предоставляла бесплатной реализации среды выполнения Java ME для мобильных устройств. 22 декабря 2006 исходный код Java ME был выпущен под лицензией GNU General Public License, проект получил название phoneME.

Отличительными особенностями устройств с ограниченными ресурсами являются ограниченная вычислительная мощность, ограниченный объём памяти, малый размер дисплея, питание от портативной батареи, а также низкоскоростные и недостаточно надёжные коммуникационные возможности. Типичный мобильный телефон середины двухтысячных содержит внутри 32-разрядный RISC-процессор с тактовой частотой 150—250 МГц, имеет объём оперативной памяти около 1—2 Мб, цветной дисплей с разрешением 240x320 пикселей и имеет возможность соединения с Интернетом посредством GPRS или EDGE со скоростью до 474 кбит/с или 3G.</text>
			<text lang="it">Java Platform, Micro Edition o Java ME è una piattaforma informatica per lo sviluppo e la distribuzione di codice portatile per dispositivi embedded e mobili (microcontrollori, sensori, gateway, telefoni cellulari, assistenti digitali personali, decoder TV, stampanti). Java ME era precedentemente noto come Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition o J2ME. Dal 22 dicembre 2006, il codice sorgente di Java ME è rilasciato sotto licenza GNU General Public License, con il nome di progetto phoneME.

Esistono più di 2,1 miliardi di telefoni cellulari e PDA abilitati a Java ME. Era molto diffuso nei dispositivi da meno di 200 dollari, come la Serie 40 di Nokia. È stato utilizzato anche sul sistema operativo Bada e su Symbian OS insieme al software nativo. Gli utenti di Windows CE, Windows Mobile, Maemo, MeeGo e Android possono scaricare Java ME per i rispettivi ambienti ("proof-of-concept" per Android).</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
