<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.15</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.15</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.15</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.14</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1987</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Konami</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>LCD Games</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>In the late 1980s, Nintendo’s Game &amp; Watch handheld devices had already established themselves as popular portable gaming gadgets.
Konami, known for its arcade hits and console games, recognized the potential of the handheld market. To challenge Nintendo’s dominance, Konami decided to create its own line of handheld LCD games.

They wanted to reach a broader audience beyond arcades and consoles. Their LCD games featured licensed characters, sports themes, and unique scenarios. Titles like “Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles” and “Top Gun” showcased their commitment to quality.

While they didn’t surpass Nintendo’s Game &amp; Watch in sales, Konami’s handheld LCD games left a lasting impact. They added diversity and excitement to the portable gaming landscape, contributing to the overall growth of handheld gaming.</text>
			<text lang="it">Alla fine degli anni '80, i dispositivi portatili Game &amp; Watch di Nintendo si erano già affermati come popolari gadget di gioco portatili.
Konami, nota per i suoi successi arcade e per i giochi per console, riconobbe il potenziale del mercato delle console portatili. Per sfidare il dominio di Nintendo, Konami decise di creare una propria linea di giochi LCD portatili.

Voleva raggiungere un pubblico più ampio al di là delle sale giochi e delle console. I loro giochi LCD presentavano personaggi su licenza, temi sportivi e scenari unici. Titoli come "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" e "Top Gun" dimostrano il loro impegno per la qualità.

Pur non avendo superato il Game &amp; Watch di Nintendo in termini di vendite, i giochi LCD portatili di Konami hanno lasciato un impatto duraturo. Hanno aggiunto diversità ed eccitazione al panorama dei giochi portatili, contribuendo alla crescita complessiva dei giochi portatili.</text>
			<text lang="fr">À la fin des années 1980, les appareils portables Game &amp; Watch de Nintendo s'étaient déjà imposés comme des gadgets de jeu portables très populaires.
Konami, connu pour ses jeux d'arcade et ses jeux de console, a reconnu le potentiel du marché des appareils portables. Pour contester la domination de Nintendo, Konami a décidé de créer sa propre ligne de jeux LCD portables.

La société souhaitait toucher un public plus large que celui des salles d'arcade et des consoles. Leurs jeux LCD présentaient des personnages sous licence, des thèmes sportifs et des scénarios uniques. Des titres comme "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" et "Top Gun" témoignent de leur engagement en faveur de la qualité.

Bien qu'ils n'aient pas dépassé le Game &amp; Watch de Nintendo en termes de ventes, les jeux LCD portables de Konami ont laissé un impact durable. Ils ont ajouté de la diversité et de l'enthousiasme au paysage des jeux portables, contribuant ainsi à la croissance globale de ce type de jeux.</text>
			<text lang="de">In den späten 1980er Jahren hatten sich Nintendos Game &amp; Watch-Handhelds bereits als beliebte tragbare Spielgeräte etabliert.
Konami, bekannt für seine Arcade-Hits und Konsolenspiele, erkannte das Potenzial des Handheld-Marktes. Um Nintendos Dominanz herauszufordern, beschloss Konami, eine eigene Reihe von LCD-Handheld-Spielen zu entwickeln.

Das Unternehmen wollte ein breiteres Publikum als das der Spielhallen und Konsolen erreichen. Ihre LCD-Spiele enthielten lizenzierte Charaktere, Sportthemen und einzigartige Szenarien. Titel wie "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" und "Top Gun" zeugten von dem hohen Qualitätsanspruch des Unternehmens.

Obwohl sie die Verkaufszahlen von Nintendos Game &amp; Watch nicht übertrafen, hinterließen die LCD-Handheld-Spiele von Konami einen bleibenden Eindruck. Sie brachten Abwechslung und Spannung in die tragbare Spielelandschaft und trugen zum allgemeinen Wachstum der Handheld-Spiele bei.</text>
			<text lang="es">A finales de la década de 1980, los dispositivos portátiles Game &amp; Watch de Nintendo ya se habían consolidado como populares aparatos de juego portátiles.
Konami, conocida por sus éxitos arcade y sus juegos de consola, reconoció el potencial del mercado de las portátiles. Para desafiar el dominio de Nintendo, Konami decidió crear su propia línea de juegos LCD portátiles.

Querían llegar a un público más amplio, más allá de los salones recreativos y las consolas. Sus juegos LCD incluían personajes con licencia, temas deportivos y escenarios únicos. Títulos como "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" y "Top Gun" demostraron su compromiso con la calidad.

Aunque no superaron en ventas a Game &amp; Watch de Nintendo, los juegos LCD portátiles de Konami dejaron un impacto duradero. Aportaron diversidad y emoción al panorama de los juegos portátiles, contribuyendo al crecimiento general de este tipo de juegos.</text>
			<text lang="ru">В конце 1980-х гг. портативные устройства Game &amp; Watch компании Nintendo уже успели завоевать популярность в качестве портативных игровых гаджетов.
Компания Konami, известная своими аркадными хитами и консольными играми, осознала потенциал рынка портативных устройств. Чтобы бросить вызов доминированию Nintendo, Konami решила создать собственную линейку портативных ЖК-игр.

Компания стремилась охватить более широкую аудиторию, чем аркады и консоли. В их ЖК-играх использовались лицензионные персонажи, спортивные темы и уникальные сценарии. Такие игры, как "Черепашки-ниндзя" и "Top Gun", демонстрируют стремление к качеству.

Несмотря на то, что по объему продаж они не превзошли Game &amp; Watch от Nintendo, портативные ЖК-игры Konami оставили неизгладимый след. Они внесли разнообразие и оживление в игровой ландшафт портативных устройств, способствуя общему росту портативных игр.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Pod koniec lat 80-tych, urządzenia przenośne Game &amp; Watch firmy Nintendo stały się już popularnymi przenośnymi gadżetami do gier.
Firma Konami, znana ze swoich hitów arcade i gier konsolowych, dostrzegła potencjał rynku handheldów. Aby rzucić wyzwanie dominacji Nintendo, firma Konami zdecydowała się stworzyć własną linię przenośnych gier LCD.

Firma chciała dotrzeć do szerszego grona odbiorców poza salonami gier i konsolami. Ich gry LCD zawierały licencjonowane postacie, motywy sportowe i unikalne scenariusze. Tytuły takie jak "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" i "Top Gun" pokazały ich zaangażowanie w jakość.

Choć nie prześcignęły Game &amp; Watch Nintendo pod względem sprzedaży, przenośne gry LCD Konami pozostawiły trwały ślad. Dodały różnorodności i ekscytacji do krajobrazu gier przenośnych, przyczyniając się do ogólnego rozwoju gier przenośnych.</text>
			<text lang="pt">No final da década de 1980, os dispositivos portáteis Game &amp; Watch da Nintendo já se tornaram populares gadgets portáteis para jogos. A Konami, conhecida por seus sucessos em fliperamas e jogos de console, percebeu o potencial do mercado de handhelds. Para desafiar a dominância da Nintendo, a Konami decidiu criar sua própria linha de jogos LCD portáteis.

A empresa queria atingir um público mais amplo além dos fliperamas e consoles. Seus jogos LCD apresentavam personagens licenciados, temas esportivos e roteiros exclusivos. Títulos como "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" e "Top Gun" mostraram seu compromisso com a qualidade.

Embora não tenham superado o Game &amp; Watch da Nintendo em vendas, os jogos LCD portáteis da Konami deixaram uma marca duradoura. Adicionaram diversidade e excitação ao cenário de jogos portáteis, contribuindo para o desenvolvimento geral dos jogos portáteis.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
