<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.43 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.4645 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.1845 0.41" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.43 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.4645 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.1845 0.41" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1983</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>VTech</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Laser 310</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>VTech Laser 310 (also known as VZ-310). It is an all-in-one computer with a Z80, 3.54 MHz microprocessor. VTech (short for Video Technology Ltd.) was a Hong Kong electronics company that also sold the Laser in other countries through various retail chains. The Laser 310 was sold by Dick Smith Electronics , for example, so instead of VTech the Laser 310 was then called the Dick Smith Laser VZ-310 or VZ-310 for short (sold from 1983 to 1989). The Laser 310 is comparable to the previous model Laser200 (VZ-200), except for a modified keyboard and a rather unusual memory size of 18 KiB (2 KiB of which is video RAM) and is fully compatible with it. The machine ran basic games on the cartridge, such as Hoppy (Frogger's version), Cosmic Rescue (Scramble), VZ Invaders (Space Invaders), Dawn Patrol (Chopper) and Moon Patrol.

Technical specifications:
- Processor: Z80A processor, 3.54 MHz
- RAM: 16KiB
- RAM: 2KiB
- Motorola 6807 video processor
- Text resolution: 32 x 16 characters (8 colors)
- Graphics resolution: 128 x 64 pixels (4 colors)</text>
			<text lang="pl">VTech Laser 310 (znany również jako VZ-310). Jest to komputer typu all-in-one z mikroprocesorem Z80, 3,54 MHz. VTech (skrót od Video Technology Ltd.) to firma elektroniczna z Hongkongu, która za pośrednictwem różnych sieci handlowych sprzedawała Laser również w innych krajach. Laser 310 był sprzedawany na przykład przez Dick Smith Electronics , więc zamiast VTech Laser 310 był wtedy nazywany Dick Smith Laser VZ-310 lub w skrócie VZ-310 (sprzedawany od 1983 do 1989). Laser 310 jest porównywalny z poprzednim modelem Laser200 (VZ-200), z wyjątkiem zmodyfikowanej klawiatury i dość nietypowej wielkości pamięci 18 KiB (2 KiB z czego to pamięć RAM wideo) i jest z nim w pełni kompatybilny. Maszyna uruchamiała podstawowe gry na kasecie, takie jak Hoppy (wersja Froggera), Cosmic Rescue (Scramble), VZ Invaders (Space Invaders), Dawn Patrol (Chopper) i Moon Patrol.</text>
			<text lang="ru">VTech Laser 310 (также известный как VZ-310). Это компьютер "все-в-одном" с микропроцессором Z80, 3,54 МГц. VTech (сокращение от Video Technology Ltd.) - гонконгская компания по производству электроники, которая также продавала Laser в других странах через различные розничные сети. Например, Laser 310 продавался компанией Dick Smith Electronics, поэтому вместо VTech Laser 310 назывался Dick Smith Laser VZ-310 или сокращенно VZ-310 (продавался с 1983 по 1989 год). Laser 310 сопоставим с предыдущей моделью Laser200 (VZ-200), за исключением измененной клавиатуры и довольно необычного объема памяти в 18 КиБ (2 КиБ из которых - видео ОЗУ), и полностью совместим с ней. Машина запускала основные игры на картридже, такие как Hoppy (версия Frogger), Cosmic Rescue (Scramble), VZ Invaders (Space Invaders), Dawn Patrol (Chopper) и Moon Patrol.</text>
			<text lang="es">VTech Laser 310 (también conocido como VZ-310). Se trata de un ordenador todo en uno con un microprocesador Z80 de 3,54 MHz. VTech (abreviatura de Video Technology Ltd.) era una empresa de electrónica de Hong Kong que también vendía el Laser en otros países a través de varias cadenas minoristas. El Laser 310 fue vendido por Dick Smith Electronics , por ejemplo, por lo que en lugar de VTech el Laser 310 se llamó entonces Dick Smith Laser VZ-310 o VZ-310 para abreviar (vendido de 1983 a 1989). El Laser 310 es comparable al modelo anterior Laser200 (VZ-200), excepto por un teclado modificado y un tamaño de memoria bastante inusual de 18 KiB (2 KiB de los cuales son RAM de vídeo) y es totalmente compatible con él. La máquina ejecutaba juegos básicos en el cartucho, como Hoppy (versión de Frogger), Cosmic Rescue (Scramble), VZ Invaders (Space Invaders), Dawn Patrol (Chopper) y Moon Patrol.

Especificaciones técnicas:
- Procesador: Procesador Z80A, 3,54 MHz
- RAM: 16KiB
- RAM: 2KiB
- Procesador de vídeo Motorola 6807
- Resolución de texto: 32 x 16 caracteres (8 colores)
- Resolución gráfica: 128 x 64 píxeles (4 colores)</text>
			<text lang="de">VTech Laser 310 (auch bekannt als VZ-310). Er ist ein All-in-One-Computer mit einem Z80-Mikroprozessor mit 3,54 MHz. VTech (kurz für Video Technology Ltd.) war ein Elektronikunternehmen aus Hongkong, das den Laser auch in anderen Ländern über verschiedene Einzelhandelsketten vertrieb. Der Laser 310 wurde z. B. von Dick Smith Electronics verkauft, so dass der Laser 310 statt VTech dann Dick Smith Laser VZ-310 oder kurz VZ-310 genannt wurde (verkauft von 1983 bis 1989). Der Laser 310 ist mit dem Vorgängermodell Laser200 (VZ-200) vergleichbar, abgesehen von einer geänderten Tastatur und einer eher ungewöhnlichen Speichergröße von 18 KiB (davon 2 KiB Video-RAM), und ist voll kompatibel mit diesem. Auf dem Gerät liefen einfache Spiele auf der Kassette, wie Hoppy (Frogger-Version), Cosmic Rescue (Scramble), VZ Invaders (Space Invaders), Dawn Patrol (Chopper) und Moon Patrol.

Technische Daten:
- Prozessor: Z80A-Prozessor, 3,54 MHz
- Arbeitsspeicher: 16KiB
- Arbeitsspeicher: 2KiB
- Motorola 6807 Videoprozessor
- Textauflösung: 32 x 16 Zeichen (8 Farben)
- Grafikauflösung: 128 x 64 Pixel (4 Farben)</text>
			<text lang="fr">VTech Laser 310 (également connu sous le nom de VZ-310). Il s'agit d'un ordinateur tout-en-un doté d'un microprocesseur Z80 de 3,54 MHz. VTech (abréviation de Video Technology Ltd.) était une société d'électronique de Hong Kong qui a également vendu le Laser dans d'autres pays par l'intermédiaire de diverses chaînes de magasins. Le Laser 310 a été vendu par Dick Smith Electronics , par exemple, de sorte qu'au lieu de VTech, le Laser 310 a été appelé Dick Smith Laser VZ-310 ou VZ-310 en abrégé (vendu de 1983 à 1989). Le Laser 310 est comparable au modèle précédent Laser200 (VZ-200), à l'exception d'un clavier modifié et d'une taille de mémoire plutôt inhabituelle de 18 KiB (dont 2 KiB de RAM vidéo) et est entièrement compatible avec lui. La machine exécutait des jeux de base sur la cartouche, tels que Hoppy (version de Frogger), Cosmic Rescue (Scramble), VZ Invaders (Space Invaders), Dawn Patrol (Chopper) et Moon Patrol.

Caractéristiques techniques :
- Processeur : Processeur Z80A, 3,54 MHz
- RAM : 16KiB
- RAM : 2KiB
- Processeur vidéo Motorola 6807
- Résolution du texte : 32 x 16 caractères (8 couleurs)
- Résolution graphique : 128 x 64 pixels (4 couleurs)</text>
			<text lang="it">VTech Laser 310 (noto anche come VZ-310). È un computer all-in-one con microprocessore Z80 a 3,54 MHz. VTech (acronimo di Video Technology Ltd.) era un'azienda elettronica di Hong Kong che vendeva il Laser anche in altri Paesi attraverso varie catene di vendita al dettaglio. Il Laser 310 era venduto, ad esempio, da Dick Smith Electronics, quindi invece di VTech il Laser 310 era chiamato Dick Smith Laser VZ-310 o VZ-310 (venduto dal 1983 al 1989). Il Laser 310 è paragonabile al modello precedente Laser200 (VZ-200), ad eccezione di una tastiera modificata e di una memoria piuttosto insolita di 18 KiB (di cui 2 KiB di RAM video) ed è pienamente compatibile con esso. La macchina funzionava con giochi di base su cartuccia, come Hoppy (versione di Frogger), Cosmic Rescue (Scramble), VZ Invaders (Space Invaders), Dawn Patrol (Chopper) e Moon Patrol.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
