<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videocrton" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_ON.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<loops>0</loops>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.38</pos>
			<maxSize>0.242</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
		</video>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.38</pos>
			<maxSize>0.242</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.38" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1995</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Casio</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Loopy</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Casio Loopy (Japanese: ルーピー, Hepburn: Rūpī), subtitled My Seal Computer SV-100, is a 32-bit home video game console. Released exclusively in Japan in October 1995, it was unique in that the marketing for it was completely targeted to female gamers.

The Loopy includes a built-in thermal color printer that can be used to create stickers from game screenshots. An optional accessory, called Magical Shop (マジカルショップ, Majikaru Shoppu), is a video capture device to obtain images from VCRs and DVD players. Users may add text to these images and make stickers. Including Magical Shop's own built-in software, the Loopy library contains 10 games. The Loopy features one controller port for use with a standard game controller or with a mouse which was sold separately. Developer Kenji Terada worked on Loopy Town no Oheya ga Hoshii!.

Casio ceased production of the console in December 1998, with software development ending in November 1996.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Casio Loopy (jap. ルーピー Rūpī) – 32-bitowa konsola gier wideo stworzona przez firmę Casio i wydana wyłącznie w Japonii w 19 października 1995 roku. Konsola była stworzona z myślą o kobietach. Konsola była wyposażona w drukarkę, która pozwalała na tworzenie naklejek z zrzutów ekranów z gier. Dodatkowe akcesorium o nazwie „Magical Shop” pozwalało konsoli na podłączenie do takich urządzeń jak magnetowid czy odtwarzacz DVD, a następnie wydrukowanie obrazu na przykład z filmu. Na konsolę wydano jedenaście gier.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Descriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="de">Descriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">(другое название — My Seal Computer SV-100) — 32-битная игровая приставка, выпущенная компанией Casio эксклюзивно для японского рынка в октябре 1995. Успеха консоль не имела, продажи и выпуск игр прекратились уже в 1996 году. Относится к пятому поколению игровых систем.

Casio и раньше пыталась выйти на рынок игровых систем, выпустив в октябре 1983 года игровую приставку Casio PV-1000. Успеха приставка не имела, к ней было выпущено всего 15 игр, и продавалась она только в Японии. Кроме того, в 1980-х годах Casio занималась разработкой и выпуском видеоигр для персональных компьютеров MSX. В период с 1984 по 1987 год компанией было выпущено более двадцати компьютерных игр для японского рынка, в том числе: Circus Charlie (только версия для японского рынка), Ice World, Exoide-Z Area 5 и ролевая игра Kenja no ishi. На этот раз компания решила пойти несколько другим путём и выпустила первую в мире игровую приставку, полностью ориентированную на девочек дошкольного и младшего школьного возраста.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>