<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.46 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.475 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.242</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.195 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.46 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.475 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.195 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1985</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sega</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Mark III</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Sega Mark III, released in October 1985 in Japan, was a pivotal gaming console in Sega's history. It served as an upgrade from its predecessors, the SG-1000 and Mark II. The Mark III featured composite video output, accommodated both Mega Cartridges and Sega Cards, and inspired the creation of the Sega Master System.

Despite being overshadowed, it remains an important milestone in gaming technology and Sega's legacy.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Sega Mark III, uscito nell'ottobre del 1985 in Giappone, è stata una console di gioco fondamentale nella storia di Sega. Si trattava di un aggiornamento rispetto ai suoi predecessori, l'SG-1000 e il Mark II. Il Mark III era dotato di uscita video composita, ospitava cartucce Mega e Sega Card e ha ispirato la creazione del Sega Master System.

Nonostante sia stato messo in ombra, rimane un'importante pietra miliare della tecnologia di gioco e dell'eredità di Sega.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Sega Mark III, sortie en octobre 1985 au Japon, est une console de jeu charnière dans l'histoire de Sega. Elle constitue une amélioration par rapport à ses prédécesseurs, la SG-1000 et la Mark II. La Mark III disposait d'une sortie vidéo composite, pouvait accueillir des Mega Cartridges et des Sega Cards, et a inspiré la création du Sega Master System.

Bien qu'il ait été éclipsé, il reste un jalon important dans la technologie des jeux et dans l'héritage de Sega.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Sega Mark III, der im Oktober 1985 in Japan auf den Markt kam, war eine der wichtigsten Spielkonsolen in der Geschichte von Sega. Sie diente als Upgrade ihrer Vorgänger, der SG-1000 und der Mark II. Der Mark III verfügte über einen Composite-Video-Ausgang, konnte sowohl Mega Cartridges als auch Sega Cards aufnehmen und inspirierte die Entwicklung des Sega Master System.

Obwohl es im Schatten steht, bleibt es ein wichtiger Meilenstein in der Spieltechnologie und dem Vermächtnis von Sega.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Sega Mark III, lanzada en octubre de 1985 en Japón, fue una consola de videojuegos fundamental en la historia de Sega. Supuso una mejora con respecto a sus predecesoras, la SG-1000 y la Mark II. La Mark III ofrecía salida de vídeo compuesto, admitía tanto Mega Cartridges como Sega Cards e inspiró la creación de la Sega Master System.

A pesar de haber sido eclipsada, sigue siendo un hito importante en la tecnología de los videojuegos y en el legado de Sega.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Sega Mark III, выпущенная в октябре 1985 года в Японии, стала поворотной игровой консолью в истории Sega. Она была усовершенствована по сравнению со своими предшественниками - SG-1000 и Mark II. Mark III оснащена композитным видеовыходом, поддерживает Mega Cartridges и Sega Cards и вдохновила на создание Sega Master System.

Несмотря на то, что Mark III был отодвинут на второй план, он остается важной вехой в развитии игровых технологий и наследия Sega.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Sega Mark III, wydana w październiku 1985 roku w Japonii, była kluczową konsolą do gier w historii firmy Sega. Służyła jako ulepszenie swoich poprzedników, SG-1000 i Mark II. Mark III posiadał kompozytowe wyjście wideo, obsługiwał zarówno Mega Cartridge, jak i Sega Cards i zainspirował stworzenie Sega Master System.

Pomimo tego, że został przyćmiony, pozostaje ważnym kamieniem milowym w technologii gier i dziedzictwie firmy Sega.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Sega Mark III, lançada em outubro de 1985 no Japão, foi um console de videogame crucial na história da Sega. Serviu como aprimoramento de seus predecessores, SG-1000 e Mark II. O Mark III tinha saída de vídeo composto, suportava tanto Mega Cartridge quanto Sega Cards e inspirou a criação do Sega Master System. 

Apesar de ter sido ofuscado, permanece um marco importante na tecnologia de jogos e no legado da Sega.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>