<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.46 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.475 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.242</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.195 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.46 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.475 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.195 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1987</text>
		</text>
	<!-- Regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="us">
			<text>1986</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>1985</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sega</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Master System</text>
		</text>
	<!-- Regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="us"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>Mark III</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Sega Master System is a third-generation 8-bit home video game console manufactured by Sega. It was originally a remodeled export version of the Sega Mark III, the third iteration of the SG-1000 series of consoles, which was released in Japan in 1985 and featured enhanced graphical capabilities over its predecessors. The Master System launched in North America in 1986, followed by Europe in 1987, and Brazil in 1989. A Japanese version of the Master System was also launched in 1987, which features a few enhancements over the export models (and by proxy the original Mark III): a built-in FM audio chip, a rapid-fire switch, and a dedicated port for the 3D glasses. The Master System II, a cheaper model, was released in 1990 in North America and Europe.

The original Master System models use both cartridges and a credit card-sized format known as Sega Cards. Accessories for the consoles include a light gun and 3D glasses that work with a range of specially designed games. The later Master System II redesign removed the card slot, turning it into a strictly cartridge-only system and is incompatible with the 3D glasses.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Sega Master System (jap.: マスターシステム) – 8-bitowa konsola na kartridże produkowana przez japońską firmę Sega.

Sega Master System została wprowadzona na rynek jako przerobiona wersja Sega SG-1000 Mark III, która z kolei była następcą SG-1000 Mark I i SG-1000 Mark II. W Japonii Mark III oficjalnie weszła na rynek 20 października 1985, maskotką systemu był Alex Kidd. W Stanach Zjednoczonych pojawiła się w czerwcu 1986, rok po wejściu na rynek konsoli Nintendo Entertainment System. Przez kolejny rok była wprowadzona do krajów europejskich.
Pomimo że SMS była konsolą bardziej zaawansowaną technicznie niż NES, nie udało jej się zdobyć takiej samej popularności. Spowodowane to było przede wszystkim późniejszym debiutem SMS, większą liczbą gier dostępnych na NES i restrykcjami nałożonymi przez Segę na producentów gier na SMS. W ciągu czterech pierwszych miesięcy sprzedano zaledwie 125 000 konsoli Segi. Dla porównania: w tym samym czasie sprzedano ponad 2 000 000 egzemplarzy Nintendo.

Dane techniczne:
- Procesor: 8-bitowy Zilog Z80, 3 546 893 Hz PAL/SECAM, 3 579 545 Hz NTSC
- Grafika: Video Display Processor bazowany na układzie Texas Instruments TMS9918:32 kolory z palety 64
- Rozdzielczość – 256x192 i 256x224, w wersji PAL/SECAM także 256x240
- Dźwięk: Texas Instruments SN76489 Czterokonałowy, monofoniczny generator dźwięku z zakresem 4 oktaw
- Jeden generator białego szumu
- ROM: 64 kbit (8 kB) do 2048 kbit (256 kB) w zależności od gry
- RAM: 64 kbit (8 kB)
- Wideo RAM: 128 kbit (16 kB)</text>
			<text lang="ru">8-битная игровая приставка третьего поколения, разработанная и выпущенная компанией Sega. Изначально приставка была выпущена в Японии в 1985 году под названием Sega Mark III. После модернизации перед изданием в Северной Америке, приставка была переименована в Master System и выпущена в 1986 году в США, в 1987 году в Европе, и в 1989 году в Бразилии. Master System была повторно перевыпущена в Японии в 1987 году, отличаясь от экспортных моделей наличием дополнительных возможностей. Mark III, как и оригинальные модели Master System, могли работать и с обычными картриджами — которые официально назывались Mega Cartridges — и с Sega Cards, размером с банковскую карточку, которые продавались по меньшей цене чем картриджи. Master System II и более поздние модели не имели слота для карточек.

Master System, являющаяся наследницей SG-1000, была создана как прямой конкурент приставке Nintendo Entertainment System. В отличие от её соперницы Master System использовала более современную аппаратную начинку, но несмотря на это ей не удалось побороть Nintendo по продажам в Японии и Северной Америке. При этом, приставка достигла значительно больших успехов в продажах в Европе и Бразилии. По сравнению с NES в игровой библиотеке Master System было гораздо меньше игр из-за лицензионной политики Nintendo, которая требовала от издателей эксклюзивности игр для NES.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Sega Master System es una videoconsola doméstica de 8 bits de tercera generación fabricada por Sega. Originalmente, era una versión de exportación remodelada de la Sega Mark III, la tercera iteración de la serie SG-1000 de consolas, que se lanzó en Japón en 1985 y presentaba capacidades gráficas mejoradas con respecto a sus predecesoras. La Master System se lanzó en Norteamérica en 1986, seguida de Europa en 1987 y Brasil en 1989. En 1987 también se lanzó una versión japonesa de la Master System, que incorporaba algunas mejoras con respecto a los modelos de exportación (y, por poder, a la Mark III original): un chip de audio FM integrado, un interruptor de disparo rápido y un puerto dedicado para las gafas 3D. La Master System II, un modelo más barato, salió a la venta en 1990 en Norteamérica y Europa.

Los modelos originales de Master System utilizan tanto cartuchos como un formato del tamaño de una tarjeta de crédito conocido como Sega Cards. Entre los accesorios de las consolas se incluyen una pistola de luz y gafas 3D que funcionan con una serie de juegos especialmente diseñados. El posterior rediseño de Master System II eliminó la ranura para tarjetas, convirtiéndola en un sistema estrictamente de cartuchos, y es incompatible con las gafas 3D.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Sega Master System ist eine 8-Bit-Heimvideospielkonsole der dritten Generation, die von Sega hergestellt wurde. Ursprünglich war es eine umgestaltete Exportversion des Sega Mark III, der dritten Generation der SG-1000-Konsolenreihe, die 1985 in Japan auf den Markt kam und im Vergleich zu ihren Vorgängern über verbesserte grafische Möglichkeiten verfügte. Das Master System kam 1986 in Nordamerika auf den Markt, gefolgt von Europa im Jahr 1987 und Brasilien im Jahr 1989. Eine japanische Version des Master System wurde ebenfalls 1987 auf den Markt gebracht, die gegenüber den Exportmodellen (und damit auch gegenüber dem ursprünglichen Mark III) einige Verbesserungen aufwies: einen eingebauten FM-Audio-Chip, einen Schnellfeuerschalter und einen eigenen Anschluss für die 3D-Brille. Das Master System II, ein günstigeres Modell, wurde 1990 in Nordamerika und Europa veröffentlicht.

Die ursprünglichen Master System-Modelle verwenden sowohl Cartridges als auch ein kreditkartengroßes Format, die so genannten Sega Cards. Das Zubehör für die Konsolen umfasst eine Lichtpistole und eine 3D-Brille, die mit einer Reihe von speziell entwickelten Spielen funktioniert. Bei der späteren Überarbeitung des Master System II wurde der Kartensteckplatz entfernt, wodurch es zu einem reinen Kassettensystem wurde, das nicht mit der 3D-Brille kompatibel ist.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Sega Master System est une console de jeux vidéo de salon 8 bits de troisième génération fabriquée par Sega. Il s'agissait à l'origine d'une version export remodelée de la Sega Mark III, la troisième itération de la série de consoles SG-1000, sortie au Japon en 1985 et dotée de capacités graphiques améliorées par rapport à ses prédécesseurs. Le Master System a été lancé en Amérique du Nord en 1986, puis en Europe en 1987 et au Brésil en 1989. Une version japonaise du Master System a également été lancée en 1987, avec quelques améliorations par rapport aux modèles d'exportation (et par procuration au Mark III original) : une puce audio FM intégrée, un commutateur de tir rapide et un port dédié pour les lunettes 3D. Le Master System II, un modèle moins cher, est sorti en 1990 en Amérique du Nord et en Europe.

Les modèles originaux du Master System utilisent à la fois des cartouches et un format de carte de crédit connu sous le nom de Sega Cards. Les accessoires pour les consoles comprennent un pistolet à lumière et des lunettes 3D qui fonctionnent avec une gamme de jeux spécialement conçus. La version ultérieure du Master System II a supprimé l'emplacement pour carte, ce qui en a fait un système exclusivement à cartouches, incompatible avec les lunettes 3D.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Sega Master System è una console per videogiochi domestici a 8 bit di terza generazione prodotta da Sega. Originariamente era una versione da esportazione rimaneggiata del Sega Mark III, la terza iterazione della serie di console SG-1000, uscita in Giappone nel 1985 e dotata di capacità grafiche migliorate rispetto ai suoi predecessori. Il Master System fu lanciato in Nord America nel 1986, seguito dall'Europa nel 1987 e dal Brasile nel 1989. Nel 1987 fu lanciata anche una versione giapponese del Master System, che presentava alcuni miglioramenti rispetto ai modelli per l'esportazione (e per procura al Mark III originale): un chip audio FM integrato, un interruttore a fuoco rapido e una porta dedicata per gli occhiali 3D. Il Master System II, un modello più economico, fu lanciato nel 1990 in Nord America e in Europa.

I modelli originali di Master System utilizzano sia cartucce che un formato di carta di credito noto come Sega Card. Gli accessori per le console includono una light gun e occhiali 3D che funzionano con una serie di giochi appositamente progettati. La successiva riprogettazione del Master System II ha eliminato lo slot per le schede, trasformandolo in un sistema esclusivamente a cartucce ed è incompatibile con gli occhiali 3D.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Sega Master System (jap.: マスターシステム) – console de 8 bits com cartuchos produzida pela empresa japonesa Sega.

Sega Master System foi lançada como uma versão modificada da Sega SG-1000 Mark III, que por sua vez era sucessor da SG-1000 Mark I e SG-1000 Mark II. No Japão, a Mark III foi lançada oficialmente em 20 de outubro de 1985, tendo Alex Kidd como mascote do sistema. Nos Estados Unidos, a console chegou em junho de 1986, um ano após o lançamento do Nintendo Entertainment System. No ano seguinte, foi lançada nos países europeus.

Apesar de a SMS ser tecnicamente mais avançada que o NES, ela não conseguiu alcançar a mesma popularidade. Isso se deveu principalmente ao lançamento posterior da SMS, ao maior número de jogos disponíveis para NES e às restrições impostas pela Sega aos desenvolvedores de jogos para SMS. Nos primeiros quatro meses, foram vendidas apenas 125.000 consolas Sega. Em comparação, nesse mesmo período, foram vendidos mais de 2.000.000 de unidades do Nintendo.

Especificações técnicas:
- Processador: Zilog Z80 de 8 bits, 3 546 893 Hz PAL/SECAM, 3 579 545 Hz NTSC
- Gráficos: Processador de Vídeo baseado no chip Texas Instruments TMS9918: 32 cores de uma paleta de 64 cores
- Resolução - 256x192 e 256x224, na versão PAL/SECAM também 256x240
- Som: Texas Instruments SN76489, gerador de som monofônico de quatro canais com alcance de 4 oitavas
- Um gerador de ruído branco
- ROM: 64 kbit (8 kB) a 2048 kbit (256 kB) dependendo do jogo
- RAM: 64 kbit (8 kB)
- RAM de Vídeo: 128 kbit (16 kB)</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
