<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.255</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.41" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.235</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.41" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Applied Technology</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>MicroBee</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>MicroBee (or Micro Bee) was a series of networkable home computers by Applied Technology, which became publicly listed company MicroBee Systems Limited soon after its release.
				
The MicroBee's most distinctive features are its user configurable video display (capable of mimicking the displays of other computers and devices including the TRS-80, Sorcerer and SOL20 with later colour and graphic models 40 and 80 column terminals, Super-80, ZX Spectrum, early arcade machines, Amstrad CPC 464) and its battery backed non-volatile RAM and small size allowing it to be powered off, transported, and powered back on and resume activities on the currently loaded program or document.

It was originally packaged as a two board unit with the lower "baseboard" containing all components except the system memory which was mounted on the upper "core board".</text>
			<text lang="it">MicroBee (o Micro Bee) era una serie di home computer collegabili in rete di Applied Technology, che subito dopo la sua uscita è diventata la società MicroBee Systems Limited, quotata in borsa.
				
Le caratteristiche principali del MicroBee sono il suo display video configurabile dall'utente (in grado di imitare i display di altri computer e dispositivi, tra cui TRS-80, Sorcerer e SOL20 con i successivi modelli a colori e grafici, terminali a 40 e 80 colonne, Super-80, ZX Spectrum, le prime macchine arcade, Amstrad CPC 464) e la sua RAM non volatile alimentata a batteria e le sue dimensioni ridotte che consentono di spegnerlo, trasportarlo e riaccenderlo per riprendere le attività sul programma o sul documento attualmente caricato.

Originariamente era confezionato come un'unità a due schede, con la "baseboard" inferiore contenente tutti i componenti tranne la memoria di sistema, montata sulla "core board" superiore.</text>
			<text lang="fr">MicroBee (ou Micro Bee) est une série d'ordinateurs domestiques en réseau d'Applied Technology, qui est devenue la société cotée en bourse MicroBee Systems Limited peu de temps après sa sortie.
				
Les caractéristiques les plus distinctives du MicroBee sont son écran vidéo configurable par l'utilisateur (capable d'imiter les écrans d'autres ordinateurs et appareils, notamment le TRS-80, le Sorcerer et le SOL20 avec les modèles couleur et graphiques ultérieurs, les terminaux à 40 et 80 colonnes, le Super-80, le ZX Spectrum, les premières machines d'arcade, l'Amstrad CPC 464), sa mémoire vive non volatile alimentée par une batterie et sa petite taille, qui lui permet d'être éteint, transporté et rallumé et de reprendre les activités sur le programme ou le document en cours de chargement.

À l'origine, il se présentait sous la forme d'une unité à deux cartes, la "carte de base" inférieure contenant tous les composants à l'exception de la mémoire du système, qui était montée sur la "carte principale" supérieure.</text>
			<text lang="de">MicroBee (oder Micro Bee) war eine Serie von vernetzbaren Heimcomputern von Applied Technology, die bald nach ihrer Veröffentlichung in das börsennotierte Unternehmen MicroBee Systems Limited umgewandelt wurde.
				
Die markantesten Merkmale des MicroBee sind sein benutzerkonfigurierbares Videodisplay (das in der Lage ist, die Displays anderer Computer und Geräte zu imitieren, darunter TRS-80, Sorcerer und SOL20 mit späteren Farb- und Grafikmodellen, 40- und 80-Spalten-Terminals, Super-80, ZX Spectrum, frühe Arcade-Automaten, Amstrad CPC 464) sowie sein batteriegestützter nichtflüchtiger Arbeitsspeicher und seine geringe Größe, die es ermöglicht, das Gerät auszuschalten, zu transportieren und wieder einzuschalten und die Aktivitäten mit dem aktuell geladenen Programm oder Dokument fortzusetzen.

Ursprünglich bestand er aus zwei Platinen, wobei die untere "Basisplatine" alle Komponenten außer dem Systemspeicher enthielt, der auf der oberen "Kernplatine" montiert war.</text>
			<text lang="es">MicroBee (o Micro Bee) fue una serie de ordenadores domésticos conectables en red de Applied Technology, que se convirtió en la empresa cotizada MicroBee Systems Limited poco después de su lanzamiento.
				
Las características más distintivas del MicroBee son su pantalla de vídeo configurable por el usuario (capaz de imitar las pantallas de otros ordenadores y dispositivos como el TRS-80, Sorcerer y SOL20 con modelos posteriores en color y gráficos, terminales de 40 y 80 columnas, Super-80, ZX Spectrum, las primeras máquinas recreativas, Amstrad CPC 464) y su memoria RAM no volátil respaldada por batería y su pequeño tamaño que permite apagarlo, transportarlo y volver a encenderlo y reanudar las actividades en el programa o documento cargado en ese momento.

Originalmente se empaquetó como una unidad de dos placas con la "placa base" inferior que contenía todos los componentes excepto la memoria del sistema que estaba montada en la "placa central" superior.</text>
			<text lang="ru">MicroBee (или Micro Bee) - серия сетевых домашних компьютеров компании Applied Technology, которая вскоре после выпуска стала публично зарегистрированной компанией MicroBee Systems Limited.
				
Наиболее характерными особенностями MicroBee являются настраиваемый пользователем видеодисплей (способный имитировать дисплеи других компьютеров и устройств, включая TRS-80, Sorcerer и SOL20 с более поздними цветными и графическими моделями 40 и 80 колоночных терминалов, Super-80, ZX Spectrum, ранние аркадные автоматы, Amstrad CPC 464), энергонезависимая оперативная память на батарейках и небольшие размеры, позволяющие выключать, перевозить, включать и возобновлять работу с текущей загруженной программой или документом.

Изначально он был выполнен в виде двухплатного блока, нижняя "базовая плата" которого содержала все компоненты, кроме системной памяти, установленной на верхней "основной плате".</text>
			<text lang="pl">MicroBee (lub Micro Bee) to seria sieciowych komputerów domowych firmy Applied Technology, która wkrótce po premierze stała się notowaną na giełdzie spółką MicroBee Systems Limited.
				
Najbardziej charakterystyczne cechy MicroBee to konfigurowalny przez użytkownika wyświetlacz wideo (zdolny do naśladowania wyświetlaczy innych komputerów i urządzeń, w tym TRS-80, Sorcerer i SOL20 z późniejszymi kolorowymi i graficznymi modelami terminali 40 i 80-kolumnowych, Super-80, ZX Spectrum, wczesne automaty zręcznościowe, Amstrad CPC 464) oraz jego nieulotna pamięć RAM podtrzymywana bateryjnie i niewielkie rozmiary pozwalające na wyłączenie, transport i ponowne włączenie oraz wznowienie działań na aktualnie załadowanym programie lub dokumencie.

Pierwotnie był pakowany jako dwupłytowa jednostka z dolną "płytą bazową" zawierającą wszystkie komponenty z wyjątkiem pamięci systemowej, która była zamontowana na górnej "płycie głównej".</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
