<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-left" extra="true">
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.3 0.33</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.44 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.105 0.51</origin>
			<pos>0.287 0.36</pos>
			<minSize>0.1 0.3</minSize>
			<rotation>26</rotation>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>27</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.007 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-right" extra="true">
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.7 0.33</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.57 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.915 0.51</origin>
			<pos>0.713 0.36</pos>
			<minSize>0.1 0.3</minSize>
			<rotation>-26</rotation>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>27</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.433 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video-arcade" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>20</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.5 0.47</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.385</pos>
			<size>0.38 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.38 0.17</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.39 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.28 0.22</size>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.385" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videoboxarcade" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.27</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.41</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.38</pos>
			<maxSize>0.365</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.38" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1993</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sega</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Model 2</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Sega Model 2 is an arcade system board originally debuted by Sega in 1993 as a successor to the Sega Model 1 board. It is an extension of the Model 1 hardware, most notably introducing the concept of texture-mapped polygons, allowing for more realistic 3D graphics for its time.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Sega Model 2 to płyta systemu arcade pierwotnie zadebiutowała w 1993 roku przez firmę Sega jako następca płyty Sega Model 1. Stanowi ona rozwinięcie sprzętu z Modelu 1, wprowadzając przede wszystkim koncepcję mapowanych teksturowo wielokątów, co pozwoliło na uzyskanie bardziej realistycznej grafiki 3D w tamtych czasach.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Аркадная система, выпущенная в 1993 году и являющаяся преемником Sega Model 1. Sega Model 2 стала первой системой, на которой вышли игры-сериалы такие как Daytona USA, Dead Or Alive, Sega Rally, House of the Dead и Virtua Cop. Имела процессор Intel i960-KB на 25 MHz и 9776KB оперативной памяти.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Sega Model 2 es una placa de sistema arcade originalmente debutada por Sega en 1993 como sucesora de la Sega Model 1. Se trata de una ampliación del hardware del Model 1, en la que destaca la introducción del concepto de polígonos mapeados con texturas, que permite gráficos 3D más realistas para su época.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Sega Model 2 ist eine Spielhallen-Systemplatine, die 1993 von Sega als Nachfolger des Sega Model 1 vorgestellt wurde. Es ist eine Erweiterung der Modell 1-Hardware, vor allem die Einführung des Konzepts der Textur-gemappten Polygone, die eine realistischere 3D-Grafik für seine Zeit ermöglicht.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Sega Model 2 est une carte de système d'arcade lancée par Sega en 1993 pour succéder à la carte Sega Model 1. Il s'agit d'une extension du matériel de la Model 1, qui introduit notamment le concept de polygones texturés, ce qui permet des graphismes 3D plus réalistes pour l'époque.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Sega Model 2 è una scheda di sistema arcade originariamente presentata da Sega nel 1993 come successore della scheda Sega Model 1. Si tratta di un'estensione dell'hardware del Model 1, che introduce in particolare il concetto di poligoni mappati con texture, consentendo una grafica 3D più realistica per l'epoca.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Sega Model 2 é uma placa de sistema arcade lançada originalmente em 1993 pela Sega como sucessor da placa Sega Model 1. É uma evolução do hardware do Model 1, introduzindo principalmente o conceito de polígonos mapeados por textura, o que permitiu gráficos 3D mais realistas para a época.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
