<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.405</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.47</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.392</pos>
			<maxSize>0.382</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.497</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.417</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.392" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise169.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.405</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.47</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.392</pos>
			<maxSize>0.372</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.495</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.415</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.392" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2013</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Moonlight</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Moonlight allows you to play your PC games on almost any device, whether you're in another room or miles away from your gaming rig.
Moonlight (formerly Limelight) is an open source implementation of NVIDIA's GameStream protocol. We implemented the protocol used by the NVIDIA Shield and wrote a set of 3rd party clients.

You can stream your collection of PC games from your GameStream-compatible PC to any supported device and play them remotely. Moonlight is perfect for gaming on the go without sacrificing the graphics and game selection available on PC.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Moonlight umożliwia Ci granie w Twoje gry PC na niemal każdym urządzeniu, niezależnie od tego, czy jesteś w innym pokoju, czy też oddalony o wiele kilometrów od swojej konsoli do gier.
Moonlight (dawniej Limelight) jest otwartoźródłową implementacją protokołu GameStream firmy NVIDIA. Zaimplementowaliśmy protokół używany przez NVIDIA Shield i napisaliśmy zestaw klientów innych firm.

Możesz przesyłać swoją kolekcję gier PC ze swojego komputera kompatybilnego z GameStream do dowolnego obsługiwanego urządzenia i grać w nie zdalnie. Moonlight jest idealny do grania w podróży, bez poświęcania grafiki i wyboru gier dostępnych na PC.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Стриминг игр с ПК. 
Для использования Moonlight подходит любой ПК (не мобильный) с видеокартой Nvidia GeForce GTX 600-й серии и лучше. Ограничение по типу видеокарты связано с тем, что Moonlight базируется на сервисе Nvidia Shield GameStream. На ПК вам не нужно какое-либо стороннее ПО, только GeForce Experience, которое поставляется вместе с драйверами Nvidia.</text>
			<text lang="es">Moonlight te permite jugar a tus juegos de PC en casi cualquier dispositivo, estés en otra habitación o a kilómetros de distancia de tu equipo de juego.
Moonlight (antes Limelight) es una implementación de código abierto del protocolo GameStream de NVIDIA. Implementamos el protocolo utilizado por la NVIDIA Shield y escribimos un conjunto de clientes de terceros.

Puedes transmitir tu colección de juegos de PC desde tu PC compatible con GameStream a cualquier dispositivo compatible y jugar a distancia. Moonlight es perfecto para jugar fuera de casa sin renunciar a los gráficos y la selección de juegos disponibles en el PC.</text>
			<text lang="de">Mit Moonlight können Sie Ihre PC-Spiele auf fast jedem Gerät spielen, egal ob Sie sich in einem anderen Raum oder meilenweit von Ihrer Spielkonsole entfernt befinden.
Moonlight (früher Limelight) ist eine Open-Source-Implementierung von NVIDIAs GameStream-Protokoll. Wir haben das von NVIDIA Shield verwendete Protokoll implementiert und eine Reihe von Drittanbieter-Clients geschrieben.

Sie können Ihre Sammlung von PC-Spielen von Ihrem GameStream-kompatiblen PC auf jedes unterstützte Gerät streamen und sie aus der Ferne spielen. Moonlight eignet sich perfekt für das Spielen unterwegs, ohne auf die Grafik und die Spieleauswahl des PCs verzichten zu müssen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Moonlight vous permet de jouer à vos jeux PC sur presque tous les appareils, que vous soyez dans une autre pièce ou à des kilomètres de votre plate-forme de jeu.
Moonlight (anciennement Limelight) est une implémentation open source du protocole GameStream de NVIDIA. Nous avons implémenté le protocole utilisé par le NVIDIA Shield et écrit un ensemble de clients tiers.

Vous pouvez diffuser votre collection de jeux PC depuis votre PC compatible GameStream vers n'importe quel appareil compatible et y jouer à distance. Moonlight est parfait pour jouer en déplacement sans sacrifier les graphismes et la sélection de jeux disponibles sur PC.</text>
			<text lang="it">Moonlight permette di giocare ai giochi per PC su quasi tutti i dispositivi, sia che ci si trovi in un'altra stanza o a chilometri di distanza dal proprio impianto di gioco.
Moonlight (ex Limelight) è un'implementazione open source del protocollo GameStream di NVIDIA. Abbiamo implementato il protocollo utilizzato da NVIDIA Shield e scritto una serie di client di terze parti.

È possibile eseguire lo streaming della propria collezione di giochi per PC dal proprio PC compatibile con GameStream a qualsiasi dispositivo supportato e giocarci in remoto. Moonlight è perfetto per giocare in movimento senza sacrificare la grafica e la selezione di giochi disponibili su PC.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
