<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/msx2+.png</path>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.21 0.4" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1988</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>MSX 2+</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>MSX is a standardized home computer architecture, announced by Microsoft and ASCII Corporation on June 16, 1983. It was initially conceived by Microsoft as a product for the Eastern sector, and jointly marketed by Kazuhiko Nishi, then vice-president at Microsoft and director at ASCII Corporation. Microsoft and Nishi conceived the project as an attempt to create unified standards among various home computing system manufacturers of the period, in the same fashion as the VHS standard for home video tape machines.

MSX systems were popular in Japan and several other countries. Sony was the primary manufacturer of MSX systems at the time of release, and throughout most of the products lifespan, producing more units than any other manufacturer. Eventually 5 million MSX-based units were sold in Japan alone. Despite Microsoft's involvement, few MSX-based machines were released in the United States.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le MSX était un standard de micro-ordinateurs à vocation domestique (grand public) d’origine japonaise, qui date des années 1980. Contrairement à la plupart des ordinateurs de l’époque, les MSX ont été produits par divers fabricants. Ils étaient compatibles entre eux, aussi bien pour le matériel que pour les logiciels. Plusieurs versions du standard se sont succédé.

Il y eut quatre générations de MSX : les MSX (ou MSX1), les MSX2, les MSX2+ et les MSX turbo R. Ils furent très populaires au Japon et en Europe, surtout à l’époque du MSX1. Le MSX2+ fut commercialisé en Europe grâce à quelques rares importateurs en France, en Espagne et aux Pays-Bas. Le MSX turbo R fut encore plus rare en Europe, car produit uniquement par la firme Panasonic et réservé exclusivement au marché japonais. Cependant, il existe une extension pour MSX1 permettant de l'utiliser comme un MSX2, le NEOS MA-20(v)</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Machines with Software eXchangeability — название стандарта для бытовых компьютеров 1980-х годов. Он являлся попыткой создания единых стандартов для разработчиков аппаратного обеспечения, инициированной японским отделением компании Microsoft и Кадзухико Ниси, возглавлявшим его на тот момент. Также в разработке стандарта участвовала ныне хорошо известная японская компания — ASCII Corporation, основанная Ниси совместно с Кадзуя Ватанабэ специально для этой цели. Компьютеры стандарта MSX получили большую популярность в Японии и ряде других стран, однако, несмотря на поддержку Microsoft, почти не получили известности в США и Европе. Всего в мире было продано более 7,5 миллиона экземпляров MSX-совместимых компьютеров, из них 5 млн — в Японии.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>