<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.32</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.358</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.358" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.32</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.358</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.358" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1985</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>MSX 2</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>MSX is a standardized home computer architecture, announced by Microsoft and ASCII Corporation on June 16, 1983. It was initially conceived by Microsoft as a product for the Eastern sector, and jointly marketed by Kazuhiko Nishi, then vice-president at Microsoft and director at ASCII Corporation. Microsoft and Nishi conceived the project as an attempt to create unified standards among various home computing system manufacturers of the period, in the same fashion as the VHS standard for home video tape machines.

MSX systems were popular in Japan and several other countries. Sony was the primary manufacturer of MSX systems at the time of release, and throughout most of the products lifespan, producing more units than any other manufacturer. Eventually 5 million MSX-based units were sold in Japan alone. Despite Microsoft's involvement, few MSX-based machines were released in the United States.</text>
			<text lang="pl">MSX 2 to standard komputerów 8-bitowych wprowadzony w 1985 roku, rozwinięcie standardu MSX (nazywanego potem MSX 1). W stosunku do poprzedniego, miał rozszerzone możliwości graficzne i system operacyjny MSX DOS 2.0.

Standard MSX 2 nie zdobył dużej popularności, a nawet takiej, jak MSX 1. Po jego wprowadzeniu Microsoft opuścił projekt MSX, lecz firma ASCII Corporation kontynuowała prace i w 1988 został zaprezentowany kolejny ulepszony standard MSX 2+, dostępny jedynie w Japonii. W 1991 Panasonic zaprezentował komputer ulepszonego standardu MSX Turbo R, lecz już w 1992 zaprzestał ich produkcji. Komputery MSX zostały wyparte z rynku wraz ze zmierzchem komputerów 8-bitowych.

Dane techniczne:
- mikroprocesor - Zilog Z80A lub kompatybilny, zegar - 3.58 MHz
- koprocesor graficzny - Yamaha V9938 (MSX-VIDEO)
- pamięć RAM - co najmniej 64 kB
- pamięć obrazu VRAM - co najmniej 64 kB
- pamięć ROM - 48 kB
- wbudowany język programowania - MSX BASIC V2.0
- tryby tekstowe (liczba znaków x linii): 40 x 24; 32 x 24
- tryby graficzne (liczba pikseli): 64 x 48; 256 x 192; 256 x 212; 512 x 212
- liczba kolorów - 512
- dźwięk General Instrument AY-3-8910 - 3 kanały, 8 oktaw
- urządzenia wejścia/wyjścia (I/O): - port dla joysticka (1 lub 2), gniazda na cartridge, wejście magnetofonu kasetowego, wyjście video RGB, - interfejs równoległy Centronics

Firmy produkujące komputery MSX 2:
Philips, Sony, Sanyo, Mitsubishi, JVC, National, Panasonic, Canon</text>
			<text lang="ru">Machines with Software eXchangeability — название стандарта для бытовых компьютеров 1980-х годов. Он являлся попыткой создания единых стандартов для разработчиков аппаратного обеспечения, инициированной японским отделением компании Microsoft и Кадзухико Ниси, возглавлявшим его на тот момент. Также в разработке стандарта участвовала ныне хорошо известная японская компания — ASCII Corporation, основанная Ниси совместно с Кадзуя Ватанабэ специально для этой цели. Компьютеры стандарта MSX получили большую популярность в Японии и ряде других стран, однако, несмотря на поддержку Microsoft, почти не получили известности в США и Европе. Всего в мире было продано более 7,5 миллиона экземпляров MSX-совместимых компьютеров, из них 5 млн — в Японии.</text>
			<text lang="es">MSX es una arquitectura estandarizada de ordenadores domésticos, anunciada por Microsoft y ASCII Corporation el 16 de junio de 1983. Fue concebido inicialmente por Microsoft como un producto para el sector oriental, y comercializado conjuntamente por Kazuhiko Nishi, entonces vicepresidente de Microsoft y director de ASCII Corporation. Microsoft y Nishi concibieron el proyecto como un intento de crear estándares unificados entre los distintos fabricantes de sistemas informáticos domésticos de la época, al igual que el estándar VHS para las máquinas de cintas de vídeo domésticas.

Los sistemas MSX fueron populares en Japón y otros países. Sony fue el principal fabricante de sistemas MSX en el momento de su lanzamiento y durante la mayor parte de la vida útil del producto, produciendo más unidades que ningún otro fabricante. Sólo en Japón se llegaron a vender 5 millones de unidades basadas en MSX. A pesar de la implicación de Microsoft, en Estados Unidos se lanzaron pocas máquinas basadas en MSX.</text>
			<text lang="de">MSX ist eine standardisierte Heimcomputerarchitektur, die von Microsoft und der ASCII Corporation am 16. Juni 1983 angekündigt wurde. Ursprünglich wurde es von Microsoft als Produkt für den Ostsektor konzipiert und von Kazuhiko Nishi, damals Vizepräsident bei Microsoft und Direktor bei der ASCII Corporation, gemeinsam vermarktet. Microsoft und Nishi betrachteten das Projekt als einen Versuch, einheitliche Standards für die verschiedenen Hersteller von Heimcomputersystemen jener Zeit zu schaffen, ähnlich wie der VHS-Standard für Heimvideogeräte.

MSX-Systeme waren in Japan und einigen anderen Ländern sehr beliebt. Sony war der wichtigste Hersteller von MSX-Systemen zum Zeitpunkt der Markteinführung und während des größten Teils der Lebensdauer des Produkts, da er mehr Geräte als jeder andere Hersteller produzierte. Schließlich wurden allein in Japan 5 Millionen MSX-basierte Geräte verkauft. Trotz der Beteiligung von Microsoft wurden nur wenige MSX-basierte Geräte in den Vereinigten Staaten veröffentlicht.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le MSX est une architecture d'ordinateur domestique standardisée, annoncée par Microsoft et ASCII Corporation le 16 juin 1983. Il a été initialement conçu par Microsoft comme un produit destiné au secteur oriental, et commercialisé conjointement par Kazuhiko Nishi, alors vice-président de Microsoft et directeur d'ASCII Corporation. Microsoft et Nishi ont conçu le projet comme une tentative de créer des normes unifiées entre les différents fabricants de systèmes informatiques domestiques de l'époque, à l'instar de la norme VHS pour les magnétoscopes domestiques.

Les systèmes MSX étaient populaires au Japon et dans plusieurs autres pays. Sony a été le principal fabricant de systèmes MSX au moment de leur sortie et pendant la majeure partie de leur durée de vie, produisant plus d'unités que n'importe quel autre fabricant. Au final, 5 millions d'unités MSX ont été vendues rien qu'au Japon. Malgré l'implication de Microsoft, peu de machines basées sur le MSX ont été commercialisées aux États-Unis.</text>
			<text lang="it">MSX è un'architettura standardizzata per home computer, annunciata da Microsoft e ASCII Corporation il 16 giugno 1983. Fu inizialmente concepito da Microsoft come prodotto per il settore orientale e commercializzato congiuntamente da Kazuhiko Nishi, allora vicepresidente di Microsoft e direttore di ASCII Corporation. Microsoft e Nishi concepirono il progetto come un tentativo di creare standard unificati tra i vari produttori di sistemi informatici domestici dell'epoca, alla stregua dello standard VHS per le macchine videofonografiche domestiche.

I sistemi MSX erano popolari in Giappone e in diversi altri paesi. Sony fu il principale produttore di sistemi MSX al momento del lancio e per la maggior parte della durata del prodotto, producendo più unità di qualsiasi altro produttore. Solo in Giappone furono venduti 5 milioni di unità basate su MSX. Nonostante il coinvolgimento di Microsoft, negli Stati Uniti furono rilasciate poche macchine basate su MSX.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O MSX 2 foi um padrão de computador de 8 bits lançado em 1985, uma evolução do padrão MSX (chamado posteriormente de MSX 1). Em relação ao seu antecessor, possuía recursos gráficos aprimorados e o sistema operacional MSX DOS 2.0.

O padrão MSX 2 não alcançou grande popularidade, nem mesmo a mesma do MSX 1. Após seu lançamento, a Microsoft abandonou o projeto MSX, mas a ASCII Corporation continuou trabalhando e, em 1988, apresentou o padrão MSX 2+, aprimorado, disponível apenas no Japão. Em 1991, a Panasonic lançou o computador com o padrão aprimorado MSX Turbo R, mas em 1992, interrompeu sua produção. Os computadores MSX foram retirados do mercado com o declínio dos computadores de 8 bits.

Especificações:
- Microprocessador - Zilog Z80A ou compatível, clock - 3.58 MHz
- Coprocessador gráfico - Yamaha V9938 (MSX-VIDEO)
- Memória RAM - no mínimo 64 kB
- Memória de vídeo VRAM - no mínimo 64 kB
- Memória ROM - 48 kB
- Linguagem de programação integrada - MSX BASIC V2.0
- Modos de texto (número de caracteres x linhas): 40 x 24; 32 x 24
- Modos gráficos (número de pixels): 64 x 48; 256 x 192; 256 x 212; 512 x 212
- Número de cores - 512
- Som - General Instrument AY-3-8910 - 3 canais, 8 oitavas
- Dispositivos de entrada/saída (I/O): - porta para joystick (1 ou 2), slots para cartuchos, entrada para fita cassete, saída de vídeo RGB, - interface paralela Centronics

Empresas que produziram computadores MSX 2:
Philips, Sony, Sanyo, Mitsubishi, JVC, National, Panasonic, Canon</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
