<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.44</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.354</pos>
			<maxSize>0.245</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.354" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.44</origin>
			<pos>0.496 0.354</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.216 0.354" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1985</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sharp</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>MZ-2500</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Sharp MZ-2500, released in 1985, is an 8-bit personal computer that stood out for its advanced features and innovative design during its time. Powered by a Z80A processor, it delivered superior performance for both business applications and gaming. Its impressive graphics capabilities, including 640×200 resolution with up to 256 colors, and an excellent FM sound synthesis system, made it a pioneer in multimedia computing.

The MZ-2500 came with a range of software support and expandability options, making it highly versatile and appealing to enthusiasts. Despite being primarily popular in Japan, it earned a reputation as one of Sharp's most iconic systems in the MZ series, embodying a blend of functionality and forward-thinking technology. It played a significant role in shaping the early computing landscape of the mid-1980s.
</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Sharp MZ-2500, lançado em 1985, é um computador pessoal de 8 bits que se destacou pelas suas funcionalidades avançadas e design inovador na sua época. Equipado com um processador Z80A, oferecia um desempenho superior tanto para aplicações empresariais como para jogos. As suas impressionantes capacidades gráficas, incluindo uma resolução de 640×200 com um máximo de 256 cores, e um excelente sistema de síntese de som FM, fizeram dele um pioneiro na computação multimédia.

O MZ-2500 vinha com uma gama de suporte de software e opções de expansão, tornando-o altamente versátil e apelativo para os entusiastas. Apesar de ser principalmente popular no Japão, ganhou reputação como um dos sistemas mais emblemáticos da Sharp na série MZ, incorporando uma mistura de funcionalidade e tecnologia avançada. Desempenhou um papel significativo na formação do panorama informático inicial de meados da década de 1980.</text>
			<text lang="it">Lo Sharp MZ-2500, rilasciato nel 1985, è un personal computer a 8 bit che all'epoca si distingueva per le sue caratteristiche avanzate e il suo design innovativo. Alimentato da un processore Z80A, offriva prestazioni superiori sia per le applicazioni aziendali che per i giochi. Le sue impressionanti capacità grafiche, tra cui una risoluzione di 640×200 con un massimo di 256 colori, e un eccellente sistema di sintesi sonora FM, lo resero un pioniere dell'informatica multimediale.

L'MZ-2500 era dotato di una serie di opzioni di espansione e supporto software che lo rendevano estremamente versatile e interessante per gli appassionati. Nonostante fosse popolare soprattutto in Giappone, si è guadagnato la reputazione di uno dei sistemi più iconici della serie MZ di Sharp, in quanto incarna una miscela di funzionalità e tecnologia all'avanguardia. Ha svolto un ruolo significativo nel plasmare il panorama informatico della metà degli anni Ottanta.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Sharp MZ-2500, sorti en 1985, est un ordinateur personnel 8 bits qui s'est distingué par ses fonctions avancées et son design innovant à l'époque. Doté d'un processeur Z80A, il offrait des performances supérieures pour les applications professionnelles et les jeux. Ses capacités graphiques impressionnantes, dont une résolution de 640×200 avec jusqu'à 256 couleurs, et un excellent système de synthèse sonore FM en ont fait un pionnier de l'informatique multimédia.

Le MZ-2500 était accompagné d'une série de logiciels et d'options d'extension, ce qui le rendait très polyvalent et attrayant pour les passionnés. Bien qu'il ait été principalement populaire au Japon, il a acquis la réputation d'être l'un des systèmes les plus emblématiques de la série MZ de Sharp, incarnant un mélange de fonctionnalité et de technologie d'avant-garde. Il a joué un rôle important dans le paysage informatique du milieu des années 1980.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Sharp MZ-2500, der 1985 auf den Markt kam, ist ein 8-Bit-Personalcomputer, der sich zu seiner Zeit durch seine fortschrittlichen Funktionen und sein innovatives Design auszeichnete. Angetrieben von einem Z80A-Prozessor bot er eine hervorragende Leistung sowohl für Geschäftsanwendungen als auch für Spiele. Seine beeindruckenden Grafikfähigkeiten, einschließlich einer Auflösung von 640×200 mit bis zu 256 Farben, und ein hervorragendes FM-Sound-Synthese-System machten ihn zu einem Pionier im Bereich Multimedia-Computing.

Der MZ-2500 wurde mit einer Reihe von Softwareunterstützung und Erweiterungsoptionen geliefert, was ihn sehr vielseitig und für Enthusiasten interessant machte. Obwohl es vor allem in Japan populär war, erwarb es sich den Ruf als eines der kultigsten Systeme der MZ-Serie von Sharp, das eine Mischung aus Funktionalität und zukunftsweisender Technologie verkörpert. Er spielte eine wichtige Rolle bei der Gestaltung der frühen Computerlandschaft Mitte der 1980er Jahre.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Sharp MZ-2500, lanzado en 1985, es un ordenador personal de 8 bits que destacó en su época por sus avanzadas prestaciones y su innovador diseño. Equipado con un procesador Z80A, ofrecía un rendimiento superior tanto para aplicaciones empresariales como para juegos. Sus impresionantes capacidades gráficas, que incluían una resolución de 640×200 con hasta 256 colores, y un excelente sistema de síntesis de sonido FM, lo convirtieron en un pionero de la informática multimedia.

El MZ-2500 contaba con una amplia gama de opciones de ampliación y compatibilidad de software, lo que lo hacía muy versátil y atractivo para los entusiastas. A pesar de ser popular sobre todo en Japón, se ganó la reputación de ser uno de los sistemas más emblemáticos de la serie MZ de Sharp, ya que encarnaba una mezcla de funcionalidad y tecnología vanguardista. Desempeñó un papel importante en la configuración del panorama informático de mediados de la década de 1980.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Sharp MZ-2500, выпущенный в 1985 году, - это 8-битный персональный компьютер, который в свое время отличался расширенными возможностями и инновационным дизайном. Работающий на процессоре Z80A, он обеспечивал превосходную производительность как для бизнес-приложений, так и для игр. Впечатляющие графические возможности, включая разрешение 640×200 и до 256 цветов, и отличная система синтеза FM-звука сделали его пионером в области мультимедийных компьютеров.

MZ-2500 поставлялся с широким спектром программной поддержки и возможностей расширения, что делало его очень универсальным и привлекательным для энтузиастов. Несмотря на то, что эта модель была популярна в основном в Японии, она заслужила репутацию одной из самых знаковых систем Sharp в серии MZ, воплотившей в себе сочетание функциональности и передовых технологий. Она сыграла значительную роль в формировании раннего компьютерного ландшафта середины 1980-х годов.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Sharp MZ-2500, wydany w 1985 roku, to 8-bitowy komputer osobisty, który w swoim czasie wyróżniał się zaawansowanymi funkcjami i innowacyjną konstrukcją. Zasilany procesorem Z80A, zapewniał doskonałą wydajność zarówno w aplikacjach biznesowych, jak i grach. Jego imponujące możliwości graficzne, w tym rozdzielczość 640×200 z maksymalnie 256 kolorami i doskonały system syntezy dźwięku FM, uczyniły go pionierem w dziedzinie komputerów multimedialnych.

MZ-2500 był wyposażony w szereg opcji obsługi oprogramowania i możliwości rozbudowy, dzięki czemu był bardzo wszechstronny i atrakcyjny dla entuzjastów. Mimo że był popularny głównie w Japonii, zyskał reputację jednego z najbardziej kultowych systemów Sharp z serii MZ, ucieleśniając połączenie funkcjonalności i przyszłościowej technologii. Odegrał on znaczącą rolę w kształtowaniu wczesnego krajobrazu komputerowego połowy lat 80-tych.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
