<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.32</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1996</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Nintendo</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>64</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Nintendo 64 (officially abbreviated as N64, hardware model number pre-term: NUS, stylized as NINTENDO64) is a home video game console developed and marketed by Nintendo. Named for its 64-bit central processing unit, it was released in June 1996 in Japan, September 1996 in North America, and March 1997 in Europe and Australia. It was the last major home console to use the ROM cartridge as its primary storage format until the Switch in 2017. The Nintendo 64 was discontinued in 2002 following the launch of its successor, the GameCube.

Codenamed "Project Reality", the Nintendo 64 design was mostly complete by mid-1995, but its launch was delayed until 1996, when Time named it Machine of the Year. It was launched with three games: Super Mario 64, Pilotwings 64 and Saikyō Habu Shōgi (exclusive to Japan). As part of the fifth generation of video game consoles, it competed primarily with the Sony PlayStation and Sega Saturn. The suggested retail price at its United States launch was US$199.99 (equivalent to $326.02 in 2019), and as of December 2009, 32.93 million units had been sold worldwide. In 2015, IGN named it the ninth-greatest video game console of all time.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Nintendo 64, N64 – domowa konsola gier komputerowych stworzona przez firmę Nintendo. Premiera konsoli w Japonii miała miejsce 23 czerwca 1996 roku, w Ameryce Północnej – 29 września 1996, a w Europie – 1 marca 1997 roku. Oficjalnie prace nad konsolą rozpoczęły się 23 sierpnia 1993. W tym dniu bowiem poinformowano o podpisaniu umowy między firmami Nintendo i Silicon Graphics, w której była mowa o projekcie „Reality”, mającym na celu stworzenie nowej konsoli do gier. Początkowo konsola miała nosić nazwę Ultra Nintendo, skróconą później do Ultra 64.

Konsola obsługuje grafikę trójwymiarową. Zostało na nią wydane 396 gier. Sprzedano ponad 32 mln. egzemplarzy tej konsoli. Pad do N64 posiada gałkę analogową.

Dane techniczne:
- Procesor: 64 bit MIPS VR4300 (kompatybilny z R4300i) (RISC) 93,75 MHz, 24 kB L1 Cache
- Koprocesor: 64 bit MIPS RISC RCP (Reality Immersion Co-Processor) i DP (Pixel Drawing Processor) 62,5 MHz
- Grafika: 256x224, max. 640x480, 16,8 mln. kolorów z czego w jednej chwili może być wyświetlanych 32 000.
- Pamięć: 4 MB Rambus DRAM, istnieje możliwość rozbudowania do 8 MB za pomocą Expansion Pak
- Dźwięk: stereo 16 bit, kompresja ADPCM
- Nośnik danych: kartridż o pojemności od 32 do 512 Mbit (od 4 do 64 MB).
- Wejścia: 4 porty padów 3 pinowe
- Wyjścia:
    Composite Video
    S-Video
    RGB (tylko w systemie NTSC)
    Analogowy dźwięk stereo
    RF poprzez zewnętrzny modulator[2]
- Wymiary: 260 × 170 mm x 73 mm
- Waga: 1,1 kg</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Nintendo 64 (ニンテンドウ64, Nintendō Rokujūyon), également connue sous les noms de code Project Reality et Ultra 64 lors de sa phase de développement, est une console de jeux vidéo de salon, sortie en 1996 (1997 en Europe), du constructeur japonais Nintendo en collaboration avec Silicon Graphics. Elle fut la dernière des consoles de salon de cinquième génération à être sortie.

La Nintendo 64 a plusieurs particularités : c'est une console « 64-bits » contrairement à ses principales concurrentes dites « 32-bits » (A part l'Atari Jaguar sortie 3 ans auparavant) ; l'entreprise a préféré le support cartouche, plus rentable pour Nintendo mais plus contraignant pour le développement et plus cher que le support CD proposé par ses concurrents ; elle innove en instaurant un stick analogique sur sa manette qui se révélera indispensable pour les jeux en 3D temps réel ; elle est aussi la première console à disposer de quatre ports manettes pour les jeux multijoueurs (ne nécessitant pas d'adaptateur).</text>
			<text lang="ru">64-разрядная игровая приставка. Разрабатывалась японской компанией Nintendo совместно с Silicon Graphics. Была выпущена в 1996 году (23 июня в Японии и 29 сентября в США) и стала ответом на приставки конкурентов Sony PlayStation и Sega Saturn. Тактовая частота центрального процессора — 93,75 МГц, графического — 62,5 МГц. Оснащалась оперативной памятью объёмом 4,5 МБ. Максимальное разрешение равнялось 640×480 при 24-битной глубине цвета. Благодаря участию Silicon Graphics, в этой приставке появилась масса новшеств, связанных с трёхмерной графикой: сглаживание текстур, MIP-mapping и др. В качестве игрового носителя был выбран картридж объёмом до 64 МБ.

Вместе с консолью Nintendo выпустила первый 3D-платформер Super Mario 64, который демонстрировал её новшества во всей красе. Это и дало начальный толчок. Однако первое время игр для Nintendo 64 было крайне мало: не всем давались особенности программирования для неё, кроме того, многих отпугивал устаревший формат носителя (оба основных конкурента тогда уже перешли на компакт-диски, которые имели большую ёмкость и были удобнее и дешевле). Сама же Nintendo не была готова к полному обеспечению своей консоли игровыми проектами. Но к 1998 году ситуация исправилась, и N64 заняла второе место на рынке игровых приставок после PlayStation (проект Saturn тогда уже можно было считать провалившимся).</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Nintendo 64 (ufficialmente abbreviato in N64, numero di modello hardware pre-term: NUS, stilizzato come NINTENDO64) è una console per videogiochi domestica sviluppata e commercializzata da Nintendo. Chiamata così per la sua unità di elaborazione centrale a 64 bit, è stata rilasciata nel giugno 1996 in Giappone, nel settembre 1996 in Nord America e nel marzo 1997 in Europa e Australia. È stata l'ultima grande console domestica a utilizzare la cartuccia ROM come formato di memorizzazione principale fino allo Switch nel 2017. Il Nintendo 64 è stato dismesso nel 2002 dopo il lancio del suo successore, il GameCube.

Con il nome in codice "Project Reality", il progetto del Nintendo 64 era stato in gran parte completato a metà del 1995, ma il suo lancio fu ritardato fino al 1996, quando il Time lo nominò macchina dell'anno. Il lancio avvenne con tre giochi: Super Mario 64, Pilotwings 64 e Saikyō Habu Shōgi (esclusiva per il Giappone). Facendo parte della quinta generazione di console per videogiochi, è entrato in competizione principalmente con la Sony PlayStation e il Sega Saturn. Il prezzo di vendita consigliato al lancio negli Stati Uniti era di 199,99 dollari (equivalenti a 326,02 dollari nel 2019) e, a dicembre 2009, erano state vendute 32,93 milioni di unità in tutto il mondo. Nel 2015, IGN l'ha definita la nona console per videogiochi più grande di tutti i tempi.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
