<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.32</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.30</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1995</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Nintendo</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>64DD</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The 64DD is a magnetic floppy disk drive peripheral for the Nintendo 64 game console developed by Nintendo. It was announced in 1995, prior to the Nintendo 64's 1996 launch, and after numerous delays was released in Japan on December 13, 1999. The "64" references both the Nintendo 64 console and the 64MB storage capacity of the disks, and "DD" is short for "disk drive" or "dynamic drive".

Plugging into the extension port on the underside of the console, the 64DD allows the Nintendo 64 to use proprietary 64MB magnetic disks for expanded and rewritable data storage, a real-time clock for persistent game world design, and a standard font and audio library for further storage efficiency. Its games and hardware accessories let the user create movies, characters, and animations to use within various other games and shared online.
The system could connect to the Internet through a dedicated online service, Randnet, for e-commerce, online gaming, and media sharing.
Describing it as "the first writable bulk data storage device for a modern video game console", Nintendo designed the 64DD as an enabling technology platform for the development of new genres of games and applications, dozens of which were in development for several years.</text>
			<text lang="pl">64DD, w języku potocznym jako Nintendo 64DD – akcesorium będące stacją dyskietek do konsoli Nintendo 64, wyprodukowanej przez Nintendo.

64DD po raz pierwszy zostało zaprezentowane szerszej publiczności w 1995 roku, na rok przed oficjalną premierą Nintendo 64 w roku 1996. Po licznych opóźnieniach zostało oficjalnie wydane jedynie w Japonii 1 grudnia 1999 roku. Nazwa składa się z dwóch członów: „64” – odnoszącym się do nazwy konsoli Nintendo 64, oraz do 64 megabajtów pamięci na dane, które posiadały dyskietki, jak i „DD”, będące skrótem angielskiego „Dynamic drive”, czyli „stacji o dużej prędkości działania”.

64DD miało na celu zwiększyć pojemność wykorzystywanych nośników. Kartridże używane w podstawowej wersji Nintendo 64 pozwalały na przechowanie od 12 do 16 MB danych, co w porównaniu do zyskujących na popularności w tamtym czasie płyt CD, pozwalających zgromadzić 700 MB danych, było wartością niemalże 60-krotnie niższą. Technologia kartridży przez wielu była uznawana za przestarzałą i mało funkcjonalną.

Dyskietki wykorzystywane przez akcesorium 64DD mogły pomieścić do 64 MB danych, co nie dorównywało płytom CD, jednak pozwoliło zwiększyć pierwotną pojemność nośnika danych ponad pięciokrotnie.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Nintendo 64 (ニンテンドウ64, Nintendō Rokujūyon), également connue sous les noms de code Project Reality et Ultra 64 lors de sa phase de développement, est une console de jeux vidéo de salon, sortie en 1996 (1997 en Europe), du constructeur japonais Nintendo en collaboration avec Silicon Graphics. Elle fut la dernière des consoles de salon de cinquième génération à être sortie.

La Nintendo 64 a plusieurs particularités : c'est une console « 64-bits » contrairement à ses principales concurrentes dites « 32-bits » (A part l'Atari Jaguar sortie 3 ans auparavant) ; l'entreprise a préféré le support cartouche, plus rentable pour Nintendo mais plus contraignant pour le développement et plus cher que le support CD proposé par ses concurrents ; elle innove en instaurant un stick analogique sur sa manette qui se révélera indispensable pour les jeux en 3D temps réel ; elle est aussi la première console à disposer de quatre ports manettes pour les jeux multijoueurs (ne nécessitant pas d'adaptateur).</text>
			<text lang="ru">(«DD» — сокращено от «Disk Drive» и, первоначально, «Dynamic Drive») является периферийным устройством для игровой приставки Nintendo 64. Оно подключается через дополнительный порт с нижней стороны Nintendo 64 и позволяло использовать на N64 магнитные диски размером 64 мегабайта для расширенного хранения данных. Хотя о запуске этого устройства впервые было заявлено до запуска N64, работы над 64DD сильно затянулись. Устройство было выпущено в Японии, когда популярность консоли пошла на спад, и в конце признано коммерчески неудачным; оно никогда не запускалось в продажу в США или в Европе.

64 DD был анонсирован в 1995 году на фирменной игровой выставке компании Nintendo под названием Shoshinkai (позднее переименованное в SpaceWorld). Одна из игр, которая должна была использовать все возможности 64 DD была «Creator», музыкальная и анимационая программа, создаваемая Software Creations, теми же людьми которые отвечали за создание звукового инструментария для комплекта разработчиков Nintendo 64. Игра рекламировала способность заменять текстуры в других играх и даже возможность создавать новые уровни и новых же персонажей. На той выставке не демонстрировалась играбельная версия Creator. В 1997 году на выставке E3, главный дизайнер компании Nintendo, Сигэру Миямото, сделал предположения относительно первых игр, которые будут выпущены для 64DD. Ими должны были стать SimCity64, Mario Artist, Pocket Monster и Earthbound64</text>
			<text lang="it">Il 64DD è una periferica per lettore di dischi magnetici per la console Nintendo 64, sviluppata da Nintendo. Fu annunciato nel 1995, prima del lancio del Nintendo 64 nel 1996, e dopo numerosi ritardi è stato rilasciato in Giappone il 13 dicembre 1999. Il termine "64" si riferisce sia alla console Nintendo 64 che alla capacità di memorizzazione dei dischi di 64 MB, mentre "DD" è l'abbreviazione di "disk drive" o "dynamic drive".

Collegato alla porta di estensione sul lato inferiore della console, il 64DD consente al Nintendo 64 di utilizzare dischi magnetici proprietari da 64 MB per la memorizzazione estesa e riscrivibile di dati, un orologio in tempo reale per la progettazione di mondi di gioco persistenti e una libreria di font e audio standard per un'ulteriore efficienza di memorizzazione. I giochi e gli accessori hardware consentono all'utente di creare filmati, personaggi e animazioni da utilizzare in altri giochi e da condividere online.
Il sistema poteva connettersi a Internet attraverso un servizio online dedicato, Randnet, per il commercio elettronico, il gioco online e la condivisione dei media.
Descritto come "il primo dispositivo di archiviazione dati scrivibile per una moderna console per videogiochi", Nintendo progettò il 64DD come piattaforma tecnologica abilitante per lo sviluppo di nuovi generi di giochi e applicazioni, decine dei quali furono in fase di sviluppo per diversi anni.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
