<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video-arcade" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.15</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.37</pos>
			<size>0.38 0.165</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.285 0.165</size>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.37" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videoboxarcade" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.25</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.38</pos>
			<maxSize>0.38</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.38" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1996</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Namco</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>System 12</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Namco System 12 is an arcade motherboard developed by Namco and released in late 1996. It is an upgrade of the previous System 11, based on Sony’s PlayStation, featuring a MIPS R3000A microprocessor that is 50% faster and a new Hitachi H8/3002 sound processor.

This hardware powered iconic titles like Tekken 3, Soulcalibur, and Mr. Driller, renowned for their advanced 3D graphics and smooth gameplay.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Namco System 12 è una scheda madre arcade sviluppata da Namco e rilasciata alla fine del 1996. Si tratta di un aggiornamento della precedente System 11, basata sulla PlayStation di Sony, con un microprocessore MIPS R3000A più veloce del 50% e un nuovo processore audio Hitachi H8/3002.

Questo hardware ha alimentato titoli iconici come Tekken 3, Soulcalibur e Mr. Driller, rinomati per la loro grafica 3D avanzata e la fluidità di gioco.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Namco System 12 est une carte mère d'arcade développée par Namco et sortie fin 1996. Il s'agit d'une mise à jour du précédent System 11, basé sur la PlayStation de Sony, avec un microprocesseur MIPS R3000A 50% plus rapide et un nouveau processeur de son Hitachi H8/3002.

Ce matériel a alimenté des titres emblématiques tels que Tekken 3, Soulcalibur et Mr. Driller, réputés pour leurs graphismes 3D avancés et leur fluidité de jeu.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Namco System 12 ist ein Arcade-Motherboard, das von Namco entwickelt und Ende 1996 veröffentlicht wurde. Es ist ein Upgrade des vorherigen System 11, das auf Sonys PlayStation basierte, mit einem MIPS R3000A Mikroprozessor, der 50 % schneller ist, und einem neuen Hitachi H8/3002 Soundprozessor.

Auf dieser Hardware liefen Kulttitel wie Tekken 3, Soulcalibur und Mr. Driller, die für ihre fortschrittliche 3D-Grafik und ihr flüssiges Gameplay bekannt waren.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Namco System 12 es una placa base arcade desarrollada por Namco y lanzada a finales de 1996. Se trata de una actualización de la anterior System 11, basada en la PlayStation de Sony, que incorpora un microprocesador MIPS R3000A un 50% más rápido y un nuevo procesador de sonido Hitachi H8/3002.

Este hardware impulsó títulos emblemáticos como Tekken 3, Soulcalibur y Mr. Driller, famosos por sus avanzados gráficos en 3D y su fluida jugabilidad.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Namco System 12 - это материнская плата для аркад, разработанная компанией Namco и выпущенная в конце 1996 года. Она является модернизацией предыдущей System 11, основанной на Sony PlayStation, и оснащена микропроцессором MIPS R3000A, который на 50 % быстрее, и новым звуковым процессором Hitachi H8/3002.

На этом оборудовании были созданы такие культовые игры, как Tekken 3, Soulcalibur и Mr. Driller, известные своей передовой 3D-графикой и плавным геймплеем.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Namco System 12 to arcade'owa płyta główna opracowana przez Namco i wydana pod koniec 1996 roku. Jest to ulepszenie poprzedniego Systemu 11, opartego na PlayStation Sony, wyposażone w mikroprocesor MIPS R3000A, który jest o 50% szybszy i nowy procesor dźwięku Hitachi H8/3002.

Sprzęt ten napędzał kultowe tytuły, takie jak Tekken 3, Soulcalibur i Mr. Driller, znane z zaawansowanej grafiki 3D i płynnej rozgrywki.</text>
			<text lang="pt">A Namco System 12 é uma placa-mãe de arcada desenvolvida pela Namco e lançada no final de 1996. É uma atualização da anterior System 11, baseada na PlayStation da Sony, com um microprocessador MIPS R3000A 50% mais rápido e um novo processador de som Hitachi H8/3002.

Este hardware alimentou títulos icónicos como Tekken 3, Soulcalibur e Mr. Driller, conhecidos pelos seus gráficos 3D avançados e jogabilidade suave.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
