<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videocrton" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_ON.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<loops>0</loops>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.355</pos>
			<maxSize>0.246</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
		</video>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/neogeocd.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/neogeocd.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.355</pos>
			<maxSize>0.246</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.355" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1994</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>SNK</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Neo Geo CD</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Neo Geo CD (Japanese: ネオジオCD, Hepburn: Neo Jio Shī Dī) is the second home video game console of SNK Corporation's Neo Geo family, released in September 9, 1994, four years after its cartridge-based equivalent. This is the same platform, converted to the cheaper CD format retailing at $49 to $79 per title, compared to the $300 cartridges. The system was originally priced at US$399, or £399 in the UK. The unit's 1× CD-ROM drive is slow, with very long loading times. The system can also play Audio CDs. All three versions of the system have no region-lock. The Neo Geo CD was launched bundled with a control pad instead of a joystick like the AES version. However, the original AES joystick can be used with all three Neo Geo CD models.

As of March 1997, there had been 570,000 Neo Geo CD units sold worldwide.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Neo Geo – konsola gier wideo stworzona przez firmę SNK w 1990 roku. Była dostępna w dwóch wersjach: AES (Advanced Entertainment System) jako konsola domowa i MVS (Multi Video System) jako automat do gier. Konsola oferowała kolorową grafikę 2D oraz dźwięk wysokiej jakości. Zostały na nią wydane 154 gry. Jako nośnika danych używała kartridży. W następnej generacji konsol, w 1994 roku pojawiło się Neo Geo CD - z specyfikacją techniczną taką jak w zwykłym Neo Geo, wykorzystujące jako nośnik płyty CD.

W 2009 roku Neo Geo zostało umieszczone na 19 miejscu na liście najlepszych konsol w historii, stworzonej przez IGN

Najrzadszą grą na ten system (a także jedną z najrzadszych na świecie) jest Kizuna Encounter w wersji PAL - wyprodukowano tylko 12 kopii z czego 7 jest zaginionych (prawdopodobnie zniszczone)</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Neo-Geo CD (ネオジオCD, Neo Jio Shī Dī) est une console de jeux vidéo lancée le 9 septembre 1994 au Japon par SNK. Elle est basée sur l'architecture de la Neo-Geo AES et Neo-Geo MVS, mais utilise des CD-ROM à la place des cartouches, ceci dans le but de réduire le prix de vente des jeux.

Le lecteur CD-ROM de la Neo-Geo CD est à la fois son meilleur atout (le prix des jeux est largement inférieur à celui de leurs homologues au format cartouche) et son principal défaut. En effet, sa vitesse de transfert de 150 kio/s (simple vitesse) associée à la faible quantité de RAM disponible, imposent d'importants temps de chargement durant le jeu. Si les titres les plus anciens n'en souffrent que modérément, l'augmentation en taille des productions SNK a rapidement contraint le joueur à patienter plusieurs secondes avant et pendant chaque partie.

Par ailleurs, à cause de la D-RAM limitée à 56 Mio, certains des derniers jeux ont été modifiés. Le plus souvent, il s'agit d'étapes d'animation ou d'effets qui ont été réduits comme The Last Blade et The Last Blade 2, seul le jeu Art of Fighting 3: The Path of the Warrior a été nettement modifié avec des sprites plus petits que dans la version MVS/AES.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая система, созданная японской компанией SNK в 1994 году.

Использованием модной технологии SNK надеялась убить сразу двух зайцев: удешевить производство (диски и сейчас, и тогда обходились на порядок дешевле печатных плат), а заодно снять ограничения, которые на игры накладывал малый объем памяти в картриджах. Но в итоге, как гласит поговорка: за двумя зайцами погонишься – ни одного не поймаешь. Цены все равно высокие, а игры сильно тормозились при загрузках (хоть и обладали качеством, более высоким, чем у оригинала Neo Geo AES). А почему, спросите вы? Да вот: компоновалась консоль вместе с CD-Rom на скорости 1Х, что было полным провалом. Оптика просто была не в состоянии справиться с потоком информации (а раз был CD, то информации было предостаточно) на такой низкой скорости. Частые паузы в таких динамичных играх как King of Fighters и Last Blade (да и в других), просто не выносились геймерами. Еще в добавок, консоль могла проигрывать Audio CD, что было очень неплохо в то время.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>