<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video-arcade" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.15</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.363</pos>
			<size>0.38 0.15</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.285 0.15</size>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.363" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videoboxarcade" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.15</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.366</pos>
			<maxSize>0.376</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.366" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1990</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>SNK</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Neo Geo MVS</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Neo Geo MVS, stylised as NEO•GEO MVS, also written as NEOGEO MVS, is a coin-operated arcade machine released in 1990 by Japanese game company SNK Corporation. Its CPU is technically a 16/32-bit 68000-based system with an 8/16-bit Z80 coprocessor, while its GPU chipset has a 24-bit graphics data bus.

The MVS offers owners the ability to put up to six different cartridges into a single cabinet, a unique feature that was also a key economic consideration for operators with limited floorspace, as well as saving money long-term. With its games stored on self-contained cartridges, a game cabinet can be exchanged for a different game title by swapping the game's ROM cartridge and cabinet artwork.
The Neo Geo MVS was a worldwide commercial success upon release in arcades, becoming one of the highest-earning machines at various arcades across markets.

A home console version was also made, called Advanced Entertainment System (AES). Unlike earlier systems, the Neo Geo AES was intended to reproduce the same quality of game as the arcade MVS system.
</text>
			<text lang="pl">Neo Geo MVS, stylizowane jako NEO-GEO MVS, pisane również jako NEOGEO MVS, to maszyna arcade na monety wydana w 1990 roku przez japońską firmę gier SNK Corporation. Jego procesor to technicznie 16/32-bitowy układ oparty na 68000 z 8/16-bitowym koprocesorem Z80, natomiast układ GPU posiada 24-bitową szynę danych graficznych.

MVS oferuje właścicielom możliwość umieszczenia do sześciu różnych kartridży w jednej obudowie, co jest unikalną cechą, która była również kluczowym czynnikiem ekonomicznym dla operatorów z ograniczoną przestrzenią użytkową, jak również długoterminową oszczędnością pieniędzy. Dzięki grom przechowywanym na niezależnych kartridżach, szafkę z grą można wymienić na inny tytuł gry poprzez zamianę kartridża ROM gry i grafiki obudowy.
Neo Geo MVS odniosła światowy sukces komercyjny po wydaniu w salonach, stając się jedną z najlepiej zarabiających maszyn w różnych salonach na całym rynku.

Powstała również wersja na konsolę domową, nazwana Advanced Entertainment System (AES). W odróżnieniu od wcześniejszych systemów, Neo Geo AES miał na celu odtworzenie tej samej jakości gry, co arcade'owy system MVS.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Neo Geo MVS, стилизованная под NEO-GEO MVS, также пишется как NEOGEO MVS, - это монетоприемник для аркадных автоматов, выпущенный в 1990 году японской игровой компанией SNK Corporation. Его центральный процессор технически представляет собой 16/32-битную систему на базе 68000 с 8/16-битным сопроцессором Z80, а чипсет GPU имеет 24-битную шину графических данных.

MVS предлагает владельцам возможность разместить до шести различных картриджей в одном шкафу - уникальная особенность, которая также была ключевым экономическим соображением для операторов с ограниченным пространством, а также экономией денег в долгосрочной перспективе. Благодаря тому, что игры хранятся на автономных картриджах, игровой шкаф может быть заменен на другую игру путем замены картриджа ROM и художественного оформления корпуса.
Neo Geo MVS имела всемирный коммерческий успех после выпуска в игровых автоматах, став одним из самых высокодоходных автоматов в различных игровых залах на всех рынках.

Была также выпущена версия для домашней консоли, названная Advanced Entertainment System (AES). В отличие от предыдущих систем, Neo Geo AES должна была воспроизводить то же качество игр, что и аркадная система MVS.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Neo Geo MVS, estilizada como NEO-GEO MVS, también escrita como NEOGEO MVS, es una máquina recreativa de monedas lanzada en 1990 por la compañía japonesa de juegos SNK Corporation. Su CPU es técnicamente un sistema basado en 68000 de 16/32 bits con un coprocesador Z80 de 8/16 bits, mientras que su chipset GPU tiene un bus de datos gráficos de 24 bits.

La MVS ofrece a los propietarios la posibilidad de colocar hasta seis cartuchos diferentes en un solo armario, una característica única que también era una consideración económica clave para los operadores con espacio limitado, además de ahorrar dinero a largo plazo. Con sus juegos almacenados en cartuchos independientes, un mueble de juego puede cambiarse por otro título intercambiando el cartucho ROM del juego y la carátula del mueble.
La Neo Geo MVS fue un éxito comercial en todo el mundo tras su lanzamiento en los salones recreativos, convirtiéndose en una de las máquinas con mayores ganancias en los salones de todos los mercados.

También se fabricó una versión para consolas domésticas, llamada Advanced Entertainment System (AES). A diferencia de los sistemas anteriores, el Neo Geo AES pretendía reproducir la misma calidad de juego que el sistema arcade MVS.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Neo Geo MVS, stilisiert als NEO-GEO MVS, auch als NEOGEO MVS geschrieben, ist ein münzbetriebener Arcade-Automat, der 1990 von der japanischen Spielefirma SNK Corporation herausgebracht wurde. Seine CPU ist technisch gesehen ein 16/32-Bit-System auf 68000-Basis mit einem 8/16-Bit-Z80-Coprozessor, während sein GPU-Chipsatz einen 24-Bit-Grafikdatenbus hat.

Der MVS bietet den Besitzern die Möglichkeit, bis zu sechs verschiedene Kassetten in einem einzigen Gehäuse unterzubringen, ein einzigartiges Merkmal, das für Betreiber mit begrenztem Platzangebot auch ein wichtiger wirtschaftlicher Aspekt war und langfristig Geld spart. Da die Spiele auf eigenständigen Kassetten gespeichert sind, kann eine Spielkonsole gegen einen anderen Titel ausgetauscht werden, indem die ROM-Kassette des Spiels und das Gehäusedesign ausgetauscht werden.
Der Neo Geo MVS war bei seinem Erscheinen in den Spielhallen ein weltweiter kommerzieller Erfolg und wurde zu einem der umsatzstärksten Geräte in verschiedenen Spielhallen auf allen Märkten.

Es wurde auch eine Heimkonsolenversion hergestellt, die Advanced Entertainment System (AES) genannt wurde. Im Gegensatz zu früheren Systemen sollte das Neo Geo AES die gleiche Spielqualität bieten wie das MVS-System für Spielhallen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Neo Geo MVS, stylisé en NEO-GEO MVS, également écrit NEOGEO MVS, est une machine d'arcade à pièces commercialisée en 1990 par la société de jeux japonaise SNK Corporation. Son processeur est techniquement un système à base de 68000 16/32 bits avec un coprocesseur Z80 8/16 bits, tandis que son chipset GPU dispose d'un bus de données graphiques 24 bits.

Le MVS offre aux propriétaires la possibilité de placer jusqu'à six cartouches différentes dans une seule armoire, une caractéristique unique qui était également une considération économique clé pour les opérateurs disposant d'un espace limité, ainsi qu'une économie d'argent à long terme. Les jeux étant stockés sur des cartouches autonomes, il est possible de remplacer un boîtier par un autre jeu en échangeant la cartouche ROM du jeu et l'illustration du boîtier.
Le Neo Geo MVS a connu un succès commercial mondial dès sa sortie dans les salles d'arcade, devenant l'une des machines les plus rentables dans les salles d'arcade de tous les marchés.

Une version pour console de salon a également été produite, appelée Advanced Entertainment System (AES). Contrairement aux systèmes précédents, le Neo Geo AES était destiné à reproduire la même qualité de jeu que le système d'arcade MVS.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Neo Geo MVS, stilizzato come NEO-GEO MVS, scritto anche come NEOGEO MVS, è una macchina arcade a gettoni rilasciata nel 1990 dalla società giapponese SNK Corporation. La sua CPU è tecnicamente un sistema a 16/32 bit basato su 68000 con un coprocessore Z80 a 8/16 bit, mentre il chipset GPU ha un bus dati grafico a 24 bit.

L'MVS offre ai proprietari la possibilità di inserire fino a sei cartucce diverse in un singolo cabinet, una caratteristica unica che è stata anche una considerazione economica fondamentale per gli operatori con spazi limitati, oltre che un risparmio a lungo termine. Grazie ai giochi memorizzati su cartucce autonome, un mobile può essere sostituito con un titolo diverso scambiando la cartuccia ROM del gioco e la grafica del mobile.
Il Neo Geo MVS è stato un successo commerciale mondiale al momento dell'uscita nelle sale giochi, diventando una delle macchine che ha guadagnato di più nei vari mercati.

Fu realizzata anche una versione per console domestica, chiamata Advanced Entertainment System (AES). A differenza dei sistemi precedenti, il Neo Geo AES era destinato a riprodurre la stessa qualità di gioco del sistema arcade MVS.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Neo Geo MVS, estilizado como NEO-GEO MVS, escrito também como NEOGEO MVS, é um sistema de fliperama lançado em 1990 pela empresa japonesa de jogos SNK Corporation. Seu processador é tecnicamente um chip de 16/32 bits baseado no 68000 com um coprocessador Z80 de 8/16 bits, enquanto o chip GPU possui um barramento de dados gráfico de 24 bits.

O MVS oferece aos proprietários a capacidade de inserir até seis cartuchos diferentes em uma única caixa, um recurso exclusivo que também foi um fator econômico chave para operadores com espaço limitado, bem como uma economia de dinheiro a longo prazo. Com os jogos armazenados em cartuchos independentes, a máquina de jogos pode ser trocada para um título diferente de jogo, trocando o cartucho ROM do jogo e a arte da caixa.

O Neo Geo MVS alcançou um sucesso comercial mundial após seu lançamento em arcades, tornando-se uma das máquinas de maior bilheteria em vários estabelecimentos em todo o mercado.

Também foi lançada uma versão para console doméstico, chamada Advanced Entertainment System (AES). Ao contrário de sistemas anteriores, o Neo Geo AES tinha como objetivo reproduzir a mesma qualidade de jogo que o sistema MVS de fliperama.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
