<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.43</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.355</pos>
			<maxSize>0.256</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.355" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.43</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.355</pos>
			<maxSize>0.246</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.355" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1990</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>SNK</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Neo Geo</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Neo Geo, stylised as NEO•GEO, also written as NEOGEO, is a cartridge-based arcade system board and fourth-generation home video game console released on April 26, 1990, by Japanese game company SNK Corporation. It was the first system in SNK's Neo Geo family. The Neo Geo was marketed as 24-bit; its CPU is technically a 16/32-bit 68000-based system with an 8/16-bit Z80 coprocessor, while its GPU chipset has a 24-bit graphics data bus.

The Neo Geo originally launched as the MVS (Multi Video System) coin-operated arcade machine. The MVS offers owners the ability to put up to six different cartridges into a single cabinet, a unique feature that was also a key economic consideration for operators with limited floorspace, as well as saving money long-term. With its games stored on self-contained cartridges, a game cabinet can be exchanged for a different game title by swapping the game's ROM cartridge and cabinet artwork. A home console version was also made, called AES (Advanced Entertainment System). It was originally launched as a rental console for video game stores in Japan (called Neo Geo Rental System), with its high price causing SNK not to release it for home use – this was later reversed due to high demand and it came into the market as a luxury console. The AES had the same raw specs as the MVS and had full compatibility, thus managed to bring a true arcade experience to home users. The Neo Geo was revived along with the brand overall in December 2012 through the introduction of the Neo Geo X handheld and home system.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Neo Geo – konsola gier wideo stworzona przez firmę SNK w 1990 roku. Była dostępna w dwóch wersjach: AES (Advanced Entertainment System) jako konsola domowa i MVS (Multi Video System) jako automat do gier. Konsola oferowała kolorową grafikę 2D oraz dźwięk wysokiej jakości. Zostały na nią wydane 154 gry. Jako nośnika danych używała kartridży. W następnej generacji konsol, w 1994 roku pojawiło się Neo Geo CD - z specyfikacją techniczną taką jak w zwykłym Neo Geo, wykorzystujące jako nośnik płyty CD.

W 2009 roku Neo Geo zostało umieszczone na 19 miejscu na liście najlepszych konsol w historii, stworzonej przez IGN

Najrzadszą grą na ten system (a także jedną z najrzadszych na świecie) jest Kizuna Encounter w wersji PAL - wyprodukowano tylko 12 kopii z czego 7 jest zaginionych (prawdopodobnie zniszczone)</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая система, созданная японской компанией SNK в 1989 году. Больше всего она была известна как система для игровых автоматов (arcade), а также выпускалась как отдельная игровая приставка (console). Система для игровых автоматов (MVS — Multi Video System) отличалась от приставки (AES — Advanced Entertainment System) наличием слотов для установки до 6 ROM-картриджей одновременно. Приставка появилась в широкой продаже на год позже (в 1990) и не имела такой популярности как игровой автомат, из-за её высокой стоимости для конечного пользователя. Ещё позже (в 1994 году) была выпущена версия приставки с CD-дисководом («Neo Geo CD»), которая также не получила популярности.

Игры, выпускавшиеся под данную приставку, предлагали пользователям довольно качественную 2D-графику и высококачественное звуковое сопровождение.

Игровая система базировалась на 16-битном процессоре Motorola 68000 (12 МГц) (или его клонах) и 8-битном Z80 (4 МГц), который использовался как звуковой сопроцессор. Для создания звуковых эффектов опционально мог использоваться 15-канальный звуковой чип Yamaha YM2610. Основная память (ОЗУ) — 64 Кб, видеопамять 68 Кб, память под звук — 2 Кб. Разрешение экрана — 320х224.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Neo Geo, estilizada como NEO-GEO, también escrita como NEOGEO, es una placa de sistema arcade basada en cartuchos y videoconsola doméstica de cuarta generación lanzada el 26 de abril de 1990 por la compañía japonesa de videojuegos SNK Corporation. Fue el primer sistema de la familia Neo Geo de SNK. La Neo Geo se comercializó como un sistema de 24 bits; su CPU es técnicamente un sistema basado en 68000 de 16/32 bits con un coprocesador Z80 de 8/16 bits, mientras que su chipset GPU tiene un bus de datos gráficos de 24 bits.

La Neo Geo se lanzó originalmente como máquina recreativa MVS (Multi Video System) que funcionaba con monedas. La MVS ofrece a los propietarios la posibilidad de colocar hasta seis cartuchos diferentes en un solo mueble, una característica única que también era una consideración económica clave para los operadores con un espacio limitado, además de ahorrar dinero a largo plazo. Con sus juegos almacenados en cartuchos independientes, un mueble de juego puede cambiarse por otro título intercambiando el cartucho ROM del juego y la carátula del mueble. También se fabricó una versión para consolas domésticas, llamada AES (Advanced Entertainment System). Se lanzó originalmente como consola de alquiler para tiendas de videojuegos en Japón (llamada Neo Geo Rental System), y su elevado precio hizo que SNK no la lanzara para uso doméstico, algo que se revirtió más tarde debido a la gran demanda y salió al mercado como consola de lujo. La AES tenía las mismas especificaciones básicas que la MVS y era totalmente compatible, por lo que consiguió ofrecer una auténtica experiencia arcade a los usuarios domésticos. La Neo Geo revivió junto con la marca en general en diciembre de 2012 con la introducción de la consola portátil y doméstica Neo Geo X.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Neo Geo, stilisiert als NEO-GEO, auch als NEOGEO geschrieben, ist ein Cartridge-basiertes Arcade-System und eine Heimvideospielkonsole der vierten Generation, die am 26. April 1990 von der japanischen Spielefirma SNK Corporation veröffentlicht wurde. Es war das erste System der Neo Geo-Familie von SNK. Der Neo Geo wurde als 24-Bit-System vermarktet; seine CPU ist technisch gesehen ein 16/32-Bit-System auf 68000-Basis mit einem 8/16-Bit-Z80-Coprozessor, während sein GPU-Chipsatz einen 24-Bit-Grafikdatenbus hat.

Der Neo Geo kam ursprünglich als MVS (Multi Video System) auf den Markt, ein münzbetriebener Arcade-Automat. Das MVS bietet den Besitzern die Möglichkeit, bis zu sechs verschiedene Kassetten in ein einziges Gehäuse zu packen, ein einzigartiges Merkmal, das für Betreiber mit begrenztem Platzangebot auch ein wichtiger wirtschaftlicher Aspekt war und langfristig Geld sparte. Da die Spiele auf eigenständigen Kassetten gespeichert sind, kann eine Spielkonsole gegen einen anderen Titel ausgetauscht werden, indem die ROM-Kassette des Spiels und das Gehäuse-Artwork ausgetauscht werden. Es wurde auch eine Heimkonsolenversion hergestellt, die AES (Advanced Entertainment System) genannt wurde. Ursprünglich wurde es als Verleihkonsole für Videospielläden in Japan eingeführt (Neo Geo Rental System), wobei der hohe Preis SNK dazu veranlasste, es nicht für den Heimgebrauch freizugeben - dies wurde später aufgrund der hohen Nachfrage rückgängig gemacht und es kam als Luxuskonsole auf den Markt. Das AES hatte die gleichen Spezifikationen wie das MVS und war voll kompatibel, so dass es den Heimanwendern ein echtes Arcade-Erlebnis bieten konnte. Der Neo Geo wurde zusammen mit der Marke insgesamt im Dezember 2012 durch die Einführung des Neo Geo X Handhelds und Heimsystems wiederbelebt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Neo Geo, stylisé en NEO-GEO, également écrit NEOGEO, est un système d'arcade à cartouche et une console de jeu vidéo de salon de quatrième génération, sorti le 26 avril 1990, par la société de jeux japonaise SNK Corporation. C'est le premier système de la famille Neo Geo de SNK. La Neo Geo a été commercialisée en tant que système 24 bits ; son processeur est techniquement un système 16/32 bits à base de 68000 avec un coprocesseur Z80 8/16 bits, tandis que son chipset GPU a un bus de données graphiques 24 bits.

Le Neo Geo a été lancé à l'origine comme machine d'arcade à pièces MVS (Multi Video System). Le MVS offre aux propriétaires la possibilité de placer jusqu'à six cartouches différentes dans un seul meuble, une caractéristique unique qui était également une considération économique clé pour les opérateurs disposant d'un espace limité, ainsi qu'une économie d'argent à long terme. Les jeux étant stockés sur des cartouches autonomes, une armoire peut être remplacée par un autre titre en échangeant la cartouche ROM du jeu et l'illustration de l'armoire. Une version pour console de salon a également été produite, appelée AES (Advanced Entertainment System). À l'origine, elle a été lancée comme console de location pour les magasins de jeux vidéo au Japon (appelée Neo Geo Rental System). Son prix élevé a incité SNK à ne pas la commercialiser pour un usage domestique, mais cette décision a été annulée plus tard en raison de la forte demande et la console est apparue sur le marché comme une console de luxe. L'AES avait les mêmes spécifications que le MVS et était entièrement compatible, ce qui lui a permis d'offrir une véritable expérience d'arcade aux particuliers. La Neo Geo a été relancée en même temps que la marque dans son ensemble en décembre 2012 avec l'introduction de la console portable et de salon Neo Geo X.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Neo Geo, stilizzato come NEO-GEO, scritto anche come NEOGEO, è un sistema arcade a cartuccia e una console per videogiochi domestica di quarta generazione rilasciata il 26 aprile 1990 dalla società giapponese SNK Corporation. È stato il primo sistema della famiglia Neo Geo di SNK. Il Neo Geo è stato commercializzato come 24-bit; la sua CPU è tecnicamente un sistema a 16/32-bit basato su 68000 con un coprocessore Z80 a 8/16-bit, mentre il suo chipset GPU ha un bus dati grafico a 24-bit.

Il Neo Geo è stato originariamente lanciato come macchina arcade a gettoni MVS (Multi Video System). L'MVS offre ai proprietari la possibilità di inserire fino a sei cartucce diverse in un singolo cabinet, una caratteristica unica che era anche una considerazione economica fondamentale per gli operatori con spazi limitati, oltre che un risparmio a lungo termine. Grazie ai giochi memorizzati su cartucce autonome, un cabinet può essere sostituito con un titolo diverso scambiando la cartuccia ROM del gioco e la grafica del cabinet. È stata realizzata anche una versione per console domestica, chiamata AES (Advanced Entertainment System). Inizialmente fu lanciata come console a noleggio per i negozi di videogiochi in Giappone (chiamata Neo Geo Rental System), e il suo prezzo elevato spinse SNK a non rilasciarla per uso domestico; in seguito, a causa dell'elevata domanda, la console fu introdotta sul mercato come console di lusso. L'AES aveva le stesse specifiche grezze dell'MVS e la piena compatibilità, riuscendo così a portare una vera esperienza arcade agli utenti domestici. Il Neo Geo è stato rilanciato insieme al marchio nel dicembre 2012 con l'introduzione del sistema portatile e domestico Neo Geo X.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Neo Geo – console de videogame criada pela empresa SNK em 1990. Estava disponível em duas versões: AES (Advanced Entertainment System) como console doméstico e MVS (Multi Video System) como máquina de arcade. O console oferecia gráficos coloridos em 2D e som de alta qualidade. Foram lançados 154 jogos para ela. Usava cartuchos como mídia de dados. Na próxima geração de consoles, em 1994, surgiu o Neo Geo CD - com especificações técnicas como o Neo Geo normal, usando CD como mídia.

Em 2009, o Neo Geo foi classificado em 19º lugar na lista das melhores consoles de todos os tempos, criada pela IGN.

O jogo mais raro para este sistema (e também um dos mais raros do mundo) é Kizuna Encounter na versão PAL - apenas 12 cópias foram produzidas, das quais 7 estão desaparecidas (provavelmente destruídas).</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
