<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.347</pos>
			<maxSize>0.36</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.4</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.347" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.347</pos>
			<maxSize>0.345</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.46</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.385</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.347" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1986</text>
		</text>
		<!-- Support different dates for regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="us">
			<text>1985</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>1983</text>
		</text>
		<!-- -->
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Nintendo</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Entertainment System HD</text>
		</text>
		<!-- Support different names for regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="us"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>Family Computer HD</text>
		</text>
		<!-- -->
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>HD Packs make it possible to replace a game’s graphics, audio and music with high definition alternatives. This can be used in many ways, for example, one could keep the game’s original resolution and simply improve its graphics by adding more colors and shading or replacing only the sounds and music and going through the old game with the new sound.

Currently supported in the Mesen emulator. For HD tiles to work, the name of the folder with tiles must match the name of the ROM, and the folder with tiles must be located in the HdPacks folder.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Pakiety HD umożliwiają zastąpienie grafiki, dźwięku i muzyki w grze alternatywami w wysokiej rozdzielczości. Można to wykorzystać na wiele sposobów, na przykład można zachować oryginalną rozdzielczość gry i po prostu poprawić jej grafikę, dodając więcej kolorów i cieniowania lub zastępując tylko dźwięki i muzykę i przechodząc starą grę z nowym dźwiękiem.

Obecnie obsługiwane w emulatorze Mesen. Aby kafelki HD działały, nazwa folderu z kafelkami musi odpowiadać nazwie pamięci ROM, a folder z kafelkami musi znajdować się w folderze HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="ru">HD паки позволяют заменить графику, звук и музыку в игре на альтернативные варианты высокого разрешения. Это можно использовать по-разному, например, сохранить оригинальное разрешение игры и просто улучшить ее графику, добавив больше цветов и теней или заменить только звуки и музыку и пройти старую игру с новым звучанием.

В настоящее время поддерживается в эмуляторе Mesen. Для работы HD тайлов нужно чтобы имя папки с тайлами совпадало с именем рома, а также папки с тайлами должны находится в папке HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="es">Los paquetes HD permiten sustituir los gráficos, el audio y la música de un juego por alternativas de alta definición. Esto se puede utilizar de muchas maneras, por ejemplo, se podría mantener la resolución original del juego y simplemente mejorar sus gráficos añadiendo más colores y sombreado o sustituir sólo los sonidos y la música y pasar el juego antiguo con el nuevo sonido.

Actualmente soportado en el emulador Mesen. Para que los tiles HD funcionen, el nombre de la carpeta con los tiles debe coincidir con el nombre de la ROM, y la carpeta con los tiles debe estar ubicada en la carpeta HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="de">HD Packs ermöglichen es, die Grafik, den Ton und die Musik eines Spiels durch hochauflösende Alternativen zu ersetzen. Dies kann auf viele Arten genutzt werden, zum Beispiel könnte man die ursprüngliche Auflösung des Spiels beibehalten und einfach die Grafik verbessern, indem man mehr Farben und Schattierungen hinzufügt oder nur den Sound und die Musik ersetzt und das alte Spiel mit dem neuen Sound durchspielt.

Derzeit wird dies im Mesen-Emulator unterstützt. Damit die HD-Kacheln funktionieren, muss der Name des Ordners mit den Kacheln mit dem Namen des ROM übereinstimmen, und der Ordner mit den Kacheln muss sich im Ordner HdPacks befinden.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Les HD Packs permettent de remplacer les graphismes, le son et la musique d'un jeu par des alternatives haute définition. Cela peut être utilisé de plusieurs façons, par exemple, on peut garder la résolution originale du jeu et simplement améliorer ses graphismes en ajoutant plus de couleurs et d'ombres ou en remplaçant seulement les sons et la musique et en parcourant l'ancien jeu avec le nouveau son.

Actuellement pris en charge par l'émulateur Mesen. Pour que les tuiles HD fonctionnent, le nom du dossier contenant les tuiles doit correspondre au nom de la ROM, et le dossier contenant les tuiles doit être situé dans le dossier HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="it">I pacchetti HD consentono di sostituire la grafica, l'audio e la musica di un gioco con alternative ad alta definizione. Questo può essere utilizzato in molti modi: ad esempio, si può mantenere la risoluzione originale del gioco e migliorarne semplicemente la grafica aggiungendo più colori e ombreggiature, oppure sostituire solo i suoni e la musica e rivedere il vecchio gioco con il nuovo audio.

Attualmente è supportato dall'emulatore Mesen. Affinché le piastrelle HD funzionino, il nome della cartella con le piastrelle deve corrispondere al nome della ROM e la cartella con le piastrelle deve trovarsi nella cartella HdPacks.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
