<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.347</pos>
			<maxSize>0.36</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.4</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.347" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.347</pos>
			<maxSize>0.345</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.46</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.385</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.347" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1986</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Nintendo</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Entertainment System</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant" extra="true">
			<text>HD Packs</text>
			<text lang="pl">Pakiety HD</text>
			<text lang="ru">HD-Паки</text>
			<text lang="es">Paquetes HD</text>
			<text lang="de">HD-Pakete</text>
			<text lang="fr">Packs HD</text>
			<text lang="it">HD Packs</text>
			<text lang="pt">Pacotes HD</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>HD Packs make it possible to replace a game’s graphics, audio and music with high definition alternatives. This can be used in many ways, for example, one could keep the game’s original resolution and simply improve its graphics by adding more colors and shading or replacing only the sounds and music and going through the old game with the new sound.

Currently supported in the Mesen emulator. For HD textures to work, the name of the folder with textures must match the name of the ROM, and the folder with textures must be located in the HdPacks folder.</text>
			<text lang="it">I pacchetti HD consentono di sostituire la grafica, l'audio e la musica di un gioco con alternative ad alta definizione. Questo può essere utilizzato in molti modi: ad esempio, si può mantenere la risoluzione originale del gioco e migliorarne semplicemente la grafica aggiungendo più colori e ombreggiature, oppure sostituire solo i suoni e la musica e rivedere il vecchio gioco con il nuovo audio.

Attualmente è supportato dall'emulatore Mesen. Affinché le texture HD funzionino, il nome della cartella con le texture deve corrispondere al nome della ROM e la cartella con le texture deve trovarsi nella cartella HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Les HD Packs permettent de remplacer les graphismes, le son et la musique d'un jeu par des alternatives haute définition. Cela peut être utilisé de différentes manières, par exemple en conservant la résolution d'origine du jeu et en améliorant simplement ses graphismes par l'ajout de couleurs et d'ombres ou en remplaçant uniquement les sons et la musique et en parcourant l'ancien jeu avec le nouveau son.

Actuellement pris en charge par l'émulateur Mesen. Pour que les textures HD fonctionnent, le nom du dossier contenant les textures doit correspondre au nom de la ROM, et le dossier contenant les textures doit être situé dans le dossier HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="de">HD Packs ermöglichen es, die Grafik, den Ton und die Musik eines Spiels durch hochauflösende Alternativen zu ersetzen. Dies kann auf viele Arten genutzt werden, zum Beispiel könnte man die ursprüngliche Auflösung des Spiels beibehalten und einfach die Grafik verbessern, indem man mehr Farben und Schattierungen hinzufügt oder nur die Sounds und die Musik ersetzt und das alte Spiel mit dem neuen Sound durchspielt.

Derzeit wird dies im Mesen-Emulator unterstützt. Damit die HD-Texturen funktionieren, muss der Name des Ordners mit den Texturen mit dem Namen des ROM übereinstimmen, und der Ordner mit den Texturen muss sich im Ordner HdPacks befinden.</text>
			<text lang="es">Los paquetes HD permiten sustituir los gráficos, el audio y la música de un juego por alternativas de alta definición. Esto se puede utilizar de muchas maneras, por ejemplo, se podría mantener la resolución original del juego y simplemente mejorar sus gráficos añadiendo más colores y sombreados o sustituir sólo los sonidos y la música y pasar el juego antiguo con el nuevo sonido.

Actualmente es compatible con el emulador Mesen. Para que las texturas HD funcionen, el nombre de la carpeta con las texturas debe coincidir con el nombre de la ROM, y la carpeta con las texturas debe estar ubicada en la carpeta HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="ru">HD-паки позволяют заменить графику, звук и музыку в игре на альтернативные варианты в высоком разрешении. Это можно использовать по-разному, например, сохранить исходное разрешение игры и просто улучшить ее графику, добавив больше цветов и оттенков, или заменить только звуки и музыку, пройдя старую игру с новым звуком.

В настоящее время поддерживается в эмуляторе Mesen. Чтобы HD-текстуры работали, название папки с текстурами должно совпадать с названием ROM, а сама папка с текстурами должна находиться в папке HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Pakiety HD umożliwiają zastąpienie grafiki, dźwięku i muzyki w grze alternatywami w wysokiej rozdzielczości. Można to wykorzystać na wiele sposobów, na przykład można zachować oryginalną rozdzielczość gry i po prostu poprawić jej grafikę, dodając więcej kolorów i cieniowania lub zastępując tylko dźwięki i muzykę i przechodząc starą grę z nowym dźwiękiem.

Obecnie obsługiwane przez emulator Mesen. Aby tekstury HD działały, nazwa folderu z teksturami musi być zgodna z nazwą pamięci ROM, a folder z teksturami musi znajdować się w folderze HdPacks.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Pacotes HD permitem substituir gráficos, áudio e música no jogo por alternativas de alta resolução. Isso pode ser usado de várias maneiras, por exemplo, você pode manter a resolução original do jogo e simplesmente melhorar seus gráficos, adicionando mais cores e sombreamento ou substituindo apenas os sons e música e jogando o jogo antigo com um novo som.

Atualmente suportado pelo emulador Mesen. Para que as texturas HD funcionem, o nome da pasta com as texturas deve corresponder ao nome do ROM e a pasta com as texturas deve estar localizada na pasta HdPacks.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>