<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.237</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.208 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.227</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.208 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1992</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Camerica</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Aladdin Deck Enhancer</text>
		</text>
		<!-- Support different names for regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="us"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>Family Computer</text>
		</text>
		<!-- -->
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Aladdin Deck Enhancer is a system-enhancing adaptor to use Compact Cartridges on the Nintendo Entertainment System. It was produced by Camerica and developed by Codemasters but not licensed by Nintendo.
 
The Aladdin Deck Enhancer contains a bypass Security Circuit Chip, a Memory Control Chip, and a Graphics Chip, which work with the lock-out chip and other features inside the NES. First, the Compact Cartridge is inserted into the Aladdin Deck Enhancer, which is shaped the same as a standard NES cartridge, and then this is inserted into the Control Deck. Inside the slot where the Compact Cartridge is placed is a recessed switch, which changes the Security/Region settings from position A to position B.
It contains 8 kilobytes of RAM for graphics use, and provides a cheaper means with which to make the game cartridges, mainly because each cartridge requires its own 10NES lock-out chip, RAM, and extra circuitry.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Aladdin Deck Enhancer to systemowy adapter umożliwiający korzystanie z Compact Cartridges na Nintendo Entertainment System. Został wyprodukowany przez Camerica i opracowany przez Codemasters, ale nie był licencjonowany przez Nintendo.
 
Aladdin Deck Enhancer zawiera układ obejścia zabezpieczeń, układ kontroli pamięci i układ graficzny, które współpracują z układem blokady i innymi funkcjami wewnątrz NES. Najpierw wkłada się Compact Cartridge do Aladdin Deck Enhancer, który ma taki sam kształt jak standardowy kartridż NES, a następnie wkłada się go do Control Deck. Wewnątrz gniazda, w którym umieszczony jest Compact Cartridge, znajduje się wpuszczony przełącznik, który zmienia ustawienia Security/Region z pozycji A do pozycji B.
Zawiera on 8 kilobajtów pamięci RAM do użytku graficznego i zapewnia tańszy sposób tworzenia kartridży z grami, głównie dlatego, że każdy kartridż wymaga własnego układu blokady 10NES, pamięci RAM i dodatkowych obwodów.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Aladdin Deck Enhancer - это системный адаптер для использования компакт-картриджей на Nintendo Entertainment System. Он был произведен компанией Camerica и разработан компанией Codemasters, но не был лицензирован Nintendo.
 
Aladdin Deck Enhancer содержит микросхему защиты обхода, микросхему управления памятью и графическую микросхему, которые работают с микросхемой блокировки и другими функциями NES. Сначала в Aladdin Deck Enhancer вставляется компакт-картридж, по форме не отличающийся от стандартного картриджа NES, а затем он вставляется в Control Deck. Внутри слота, куда помещается компакт-картридж, находится утопленный переключатель, который переключает настройки безопасности/региона из положения A в положение B.
Компакт-картридж содержит 8 килобайт оперативной памяти для работы с графикой и обеспечивает удешевление производства игровых картриджей, поскольку для каждого картриджа требуется своя микросхема блокировки 10NES, оперативная память и дополнительные схемы.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Aladdin Deck Enhancer es un adaptador que mejora la consola para utilizar cartuchos compactos en la Nintendo Entertainment System. Fue producido por Camerica y desarrollado por Codemasters, pero no tiene licencia de Nintendo.
 
El Aladdin Deck Enhancer contiene un chip de circuito de seguridad de derivación, un chip de control de memoria y un chip gráfico, que funcionan con el chip de bloqueo y otras funciones de la NES. Primero se inserta el cartucho compacto en el Aladdin Deck Enhancer, que tiene la misma forma que un cartucho estándar de NES, y luego se inserta en el Control Deck. Dentro de la ranura donde se coloca el Cartucho Compacto hay un interruptor empotrado, que cambia la configuración de Seguridad/Región de la posición A a la posición B.
Contiene 8 kilobytes de RAM para uso gráfico, y proporciona un medio más barato con el que fabricar los cartuchos de juego, principalmente porque cada cartucho requiere su propio chip de bloqueo 10NES, RAM y circuitería extra.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Aladdin Deck Enhancer ist ein systemverbessernder Adapter zur Verwendung von Compact Cartridges auf dem Nintendo Entertainment System. Er wurde von Camerica produziert und von Codemasters entwickelt, aber nicht von Nintendo lizenziert.
 
Der Aladdin Deck Enhancer enthält einen Bypass Security Circuit Chip, einen Memory Control Chip und einen Grafikchip, die mit dem Lock-Out Chip und anderen Funktionen des NES zusammenarbeiten. Zuerst wird die Compact Cartridge in den Aladdin Deck Enhancer eingelegt, der die gleiche Form wie eine normale NES-Cartridge hat, und dann wird diese in das Control Deck eingelegt. In dem Schlitz, in den die Compact Cartridge eingesetzt wird, befindet sich ein versenkter Schalter, mit dem die Sicherheits-/Regionseinstellungen von Position A auf Position B geändert werden.
Die Compact Cartridge enthält 8 Kilobyte RAM für Grafikzwecke und ermöglicht eine kostengünstigere Herstellung von Spielkassetten, da für jede Kassette ein eigener 10NES-Lockout-Chip, RAM und zusätzliche Schaltkreise erforderlich sind.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Aladdin Deck Enhancer est un adaptateur permettant d'utiliser des cartouches compactes sur la Nintendo Entertainment System. Il a été produit par Camerica et développé par Codemasters, mais n'a pas été autorisé par Nintendo.
 
L'Aladdin Deck Enhancer contient un circuit de sécurité de dérivation, une puce de contrôle de la mémoire et une puce graphique, qui fonctionnent avec la puce de verrouillage et d'autres fonctions à l'intérieur du NES. Tout d'abord, la cartouche compacte est insérée dans l'Aladdin Deck Enhancer, qui a la même forme qu'une cartouche NES standard, puis elle est insérée dans le Control Deck. Dans la fente où la cartouche compacte est placée se trouve un interrupteur encastré qui fait passer les paramètres de sécurité/région de la position A à la position B.
Elle contient 8 kilo-octets de RAM pour les graphiques et permet de fabriquer les cartouches de jeu à moindre coût, principalement parce que chaque cartouche nécessite sa propre puce de verrouillage 10NES, de la RAM et des circuits supplémentaires.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'Aladdin Deck Enhancer è un adattatore per l'utilizzo di cartucce compatte su Nintendo Entertainment System. È stato prodotto da Camerica e sviluppato da Codemasters, ma non è stato concesso in licenza da Nintendo.
 
L'Aladdin Deck Enhancer contiene un chip di sicurezza per il bypass, un chip di controllo della memoria e un chip grafico, che funzionano con il chip di blocco e altre funzioni del NES. Per prima cosa, la cartuccia compatta viene inserita nell'Aladdin Deck Enhancer, che ha la stessa forma di una cartuccia NES standard, e poi viene inserita nel Control Deck. All'interno dello slot in cui è inserita la cartuccia compatta si trova un interruttore incassato, che cambia le impostazioni di sicurezza/regione dalla posizione A a quella B.
Contiene 8 kilobyte di RAM per l'uso della grafica e fornisce un mezzo più economico per realizzare le cartucce di gioco, soprattutto perché ogni cartuccia richiede il proprio chip di blocco 10NES, la RAM e i circuiti aggiuntivi.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
