<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.455</pos>
			<maxSize>0.32</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.30</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.455" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1998</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>SNK</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Neo Geo Pocket</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Neo Geo Pocket is a monochrome handheld game console released by SNK. It was the company's first handheld system and is part of the Neo Geo family. It debuted in Japan in late 1998 but never saw an American release, being exclusive to Japan, Asia and Europe.

The Neo Geo Pocket is considered to be an unsuccessful console. Lower than expected sales resulted in its discontinuation in 1999, and was immediately succeeded by the Neo Geo Pocket Color, a full color device allowing the system to compete more easily with the dominant Game Boy Color handheld, and which also saw an American release. Though the system enjoyed only a short life, there were some significant games released on the system such as Samurai Shodown, and King of Fighters R-1.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Neo Geo Pocket – przenośna konsola firmy SNK. Pojawiła się w 1998 roku i była dostępna jedynie w Japonii i Hongkongu. Nie zdobyła wielkiej popularności, już w 1999 roku SNK zdecydowało się o zakończeniu jej produkcji. Konsola miała czarno-biały ekran, jej następcą jest Neo Geo Pocket Color, wyświetlający już kolory.

Na Neo Geo Pocket pokazało się tylko 10 gier (Melan Chan's Growth Diary, Puzzle Link, Pocket Tennis, Neo Cup 98, Neo Cup 98 plus, King of Fighters, Samurai Shodown, Master of Syougi, Neo Cherry Master oraz Baseball Stars) jednak istniała na niej możliwość odpalenia części gier z następcy.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Neo-Geo Pocket est la première console portable de SNK. Elle est sortie au Japon fin 1998, et a été arrêtée en 1999, à l'arrivée de la Neo-Geo Pocket Color, à cause de ventes plus faibles que prévu pour la Neo-Geo Pocket monochrome.

Ce système a été seulement commercialisé sur les marchés japonais et hong-kongais. Bien qu'il ait eu une courte vie, quelques jeux importants sont sortis dessus tels que Samurai Shodown, et King of Fighters R-1.

La Neo-Geo Pocket peut jouer une grande partie des nouveaux jeux en couleur. Il existe toutefois des exceptions notables, telles que Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure ou SNK vs. Capcom: Match of the Millennium et The Last Blade. La Neo-Geo Pocket Color, elle, est entièrement rétro-compatible.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Портативная игровая приставка, созданная компанией SNK Playmore и выпущенная в 1998 году. Цветная версия приставки, названная Neo Geo Pocket Color, была выпущена в мае 1999 года.

Neo Geo Pocket была запущена 27 октября 1998 года в продажу в Японии. У приставки был жидкокристаллический экран, способный воспроизводить восемь оттенков серого, разъем для стереонаушников, запас в 20 часов автономной работы и встроенный аккумулятор для сохранений. На портативном устройстве также предусмотрены некоторые основные функции карманных персональных компьютеров, такие как часы, календарь и генератор гороскопов. Как и у Game Boy, игровые картриджи вставлялись в заднюю часть устройства.

Neo Geo Pocket считается неудачной игровой приставкой. Более низкие, чем ожидалось, продажи привели к прекращению её производства в 1999 году, и сразу же была выпущена полноцветная версия под названием Neo Geo Pocket Color. Несмотря на то, что система просуществовала недолго, на ней было выпущено несколько важных игр, таких как Samurai Shodown и King of Fighters R-1.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Neo Geo Pocket è una console portatile monocromatica rilasciata da SNK. È stata la prima console portatile dell'azienda e fa parte della famiglia Neo Geo. Ha debuttato in Giappone alla fine del 1998, ma non ha mai visto un'uscita americana, essendo un'esclusiva di Giappone, Asia ed Europa.

Il Neo Geo Pocket è considerato una console di scarso successo. Le vendite inferiori alle aspettative ne determinarono l'interruzione nel 1999 e fu immediatamente sostituito dal Neo Geo Pocket Color, un dispositivo a colori che permetteva al sistema di competere più facilmente con la console portatile Game Boy Color, anch'essa dominante, e che vide un'uscita americana. Sebbene il sistema abbia avuto una vita breve, vi sono stati pubblicati alcuni giochi significativi come Samurai Shodown e King of Fighters R-1.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
