<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.47</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.49</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.468</pos>
			<maxSize>0.332</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.468" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.47</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.49</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.4785</pos>
			<maxSize>0.296</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.4785" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1999</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>SNK</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Neo Geo Pocket Color</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Neo Geo Pocket Color is a 16-bit color handheld video game console manufactured by SNK. It is a successor to SNK's monochrome Neo Geo Pocket handheld which debuted in 1998 in Japan, with the Color being fully backward compatible. The Neo Geo Pocket Color was released on March 16, 1999 in Japan, August 6, 1999 in North America, and on October 1, 1999 in Europe, entering markets all dominated by Nintendo, competing with Nintendo's Game Boy Color.

After a good sales start in both the U.S. and Japan with 14 launch titles (a record at the time), subsequent low retail support in the U.S., lack of communication with third-party developers by SNK's American management, the popularity of Nintendo's Pokémon franchise and anticipation of the 32-bit Game Boy Advance, and strong competition from Bandai's WonderSwan in Japan, led to a sales decline in both regions.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Neo Geo Pocket Color – przenośna konsola gier wideo firmy SNK, jest następczynią Neo Geo Pocket. Konsola kosztowała $69.95, i była dostępna w sześciu kolorach: Camouflage Blue, Carbon Black, Crystal White, Platinum Blue, Platinum Silver i Stone Blue. Została wycofana ze sklepów w Europie w 2000 roku, ze względu na niskie wyniki sprzedaży - na rynkach azjatyckich utrzymała się do 2001 roku. Była kompatybilna wstecz z grami dostępnymi na Neo Geo Pocket.

Dane techniczne:
- CPU: 6.144 MHz Toshiba TLCS900H oraz 3.072 MHz Z80
- Ekran: rozdzielczość 160x152, 146 kolorów jednocześnie na ekranie, z palety 4096
- Nośniki: 4 MB kartridże
- Zasilanie: 2 x baterie AA, pozwalały na mniej więcej 40 godzin gry</text>
			<text lang="ru">Портативная игровая приставка. Через 2 месяца после выхода монохромной Neo-Geo Pocket, конкурент SNK — Nintendo выпустил цветную версию своей портативной приставки — Game Boy Color. Поскольку в новом продукте Nintendo был цветной экран, продукт SNK начал продаваться в меньших количествах и чтобы не потерять спрос, в 1999 году была создана цветная версия приставки — Neo Geo Pocket Color. По некоторым параметрам она даже обгоняла Game Boy Color, но консоль не сумела захватить более 2% мирового рынка и уже через год поддержка была прекращена.

Через месяц, после выхода консоли, Sega объявила о сотрудничестве с создателями Neo-Geo. Для Pocket Color выпущена игра Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure. Игра стала успешной, благодаря чему доход получили и Sega и SNK Playmore.

Для Neo Geo Pocket было выпущено лишь 10 монохромных игр из 82. Остальные выпускались уже для Neo Geo Pocket Color.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Neo Geo Pocket Color es una videoconsola portátil en color de 16 bits fabricada por SNK. Es la sucesora de la consola monocroma Neo Geo Pocket de SNK, que debutó en 1998 en Japón, y es totalmente compatible con versiones anteriores. La Neo Geo Pocket Color salió a la venta el 16 de marzo de 1999 en Japón, el 6 de agosto de 1999 en Norteamérica y el 1 de octubre de 1999 en Europa, entrando así en los mercados dominados por Nintendo y compitiendo con la Game Boy Color de Nintendo.

Tras un buen comienzo de ventas tanto en EE.UU. como en Japón, con 14 títulos de lanzamiento (un récord en aquella época), el escaso apoyo posterior de los minoristas en EE.UU., la falta de comunicación con los desarrolladores de terceros por parte de la dirección estadounidense de SNK, la popularidad de la franquicia Pokémon de Nintendo y la anticipación de la Game Boy Advance de 32 bits, así como la fuerte competencia de WonderSwan de Bandai en Japón, provocaron un descenso de las ventas en ambas regiones.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Neo Geo Pocket Color ist eine 16-Bit-Farb-Handheld-Videospielkonsole, die von SNK hergestellt wird. Es ist der Nachfolger von SNKs monochromem Neo Geo Pocket Handheld, der 1998 in Japan auf den Markt kam, wobei der Color vollständig abwärtskompatibel ist. Der Neo Geo Pocket Color wurde am 16. März 1999 in Japan, am 6. August 1999 in Nordamerika und am 1. Oktober 1999 in Europa veröffentlicht und trat damit in die von Nintendo dominierten Märkte ein und konkurrierte mit dem Game Boy Color von Nintendo.

Nach einem guten Verkaufsstart sowohl in den USA als auch in Japan mit 14 Launch-Titeln (damals ein Rekord), führten die geringe Unterstützung des Einzelhandels in den USA, die mangelnde Kommunikation mit Drittentwicklern durch das amerikanische Management von SNK, die Popularität von Nintendos Pokémon-Franchise und die Vorfreude auf den 32-Bit Game Boy Advance sowie die starke Konkurrenz durch Bandais WonderSwan in Japan zu einem Verkaufsrückgang in beiden Regionen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Neo Geo Pocket Color est une console de jeu vidéo portable couleur 16 bits fabriquée par SNK. Elle succède à la console de poche monochrome Neo Geo Pocket de SNK qui a fait ses débuts en 1998 au Japon, la Color étant entièrement rétrocompatible. La Neo Geo Pocket Color est sortie le 16 mars 1999 au Japon, le 6 août 1999 en Amérique du Nord et le 1er octobre 1999 en Europe, sur des marchés dominés par Nintendo, en concurrence avec la Game Boy Color de Nintendo.

Après un bon démarrage des ventes aux États-Unis et au Japon avec 14 titres de lancement (un record à l'époque), le faible soutien des détaillants aux États-Unis, le manque de communication avec les développeurs tiers de la part de la direction américaine de SNK, la popularité de la franchise Pokémon de Nintendo et l'anticipation de la Game Boy Advance 32 bits, ainsi que la forte concurrence de la WonderSwan de Bandai au Japon, ont entraîné une baisse des ventes dans les deux régions.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Neo Geo Pocket Color è una console per videogiochi portatile a colori a 16 bit prodotta da SNK. È il successore della console portatile monocromatica Neo Geo Pocket di SNK, che ha debuttato nel 1998 in Giappone, e il Color è completamente retrocompatibile. Il Neo Geo Pocket Color è stato rilasciato il 16 marzo 1999 in Giappone, il 6 agosto 1999 in Nord America e il 1° ottobre 1999 in Europa, entrando nei mercati dominati da Nintendo e facendo concorrenza al Game Boy Color di Nintendo.

Dopo un buon inizio di vendite sia negli Stati Uniti che in Giappone, con 14 titoli di lancio (un record all'epoca), il successivo scarso supporto al dettaglio negli Stati Uniti, la mancanza di comunicazione con gli sviluppatori di terze parti da parte della dirigenza americana di SNK, la popolarità del franchise Pokémon di Nintendo e l'anticipazione del Game Boy Advance a 32 bit, nonché la forte concorrenza del WonderSwan di Bandai in Giappone, portarono a un calo delle vendite in entrambe le regioni.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
