<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.496 0.49</pos>
			<maxSize>0.225</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.216 0.49" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/megadrive.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/megadrive.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.496 0.49</pos>
			<maxSize>0.215</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.216 0.49" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1995</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sega</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Nomad</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Genesis Nomad, also known as Sega Nomad, is a handheld game console manufactured by Sega and released in North America in October 1995. The Nomad is a portable variation of the Sega Genesis home video game console (known as the Mega Drive outside North America). It could also be used with a television set via a video port. It was based on the Mega Jet, a portable version of the home console designed for use on airline flights in Japan.

The Nomad was the last handheld console released by Sega. Released late in the Genesis era, it had a short lifespan. It was sold exclusively in North America, and uses regional lockout. Sega's focus on the Sega Saturn left the Nomad under-supported, and it was incompatible with several Genesis peripherals, including the Power Base Converter, the Sega CD, and the 32X. About 1 million units of the Nomad were sold, and it is considered a commercial failure.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Genesis Nomad, znana również jako Sega Nomad, to przenośna konsola do gier wyprodukowana przez firmę Sega i wydana w Ameryce Północnej w październiku 1995 roku. Nomad jest przenośną wersją domowej konsoli do gier wideo Sega Genesis (znanej jako Mega Drive poza Ameryką Północną). Mogła być również używana z telewizorem za pośrednictwem portu wideo. Bazował na Mega Jet, przenośnej wersji konsoli domowej zaprojektowanej do użytku podczas lotów lotniczych w Japonii.

Nomad był ostatnią konsolą przenośną wydaną przez firmę Sega. Wydana pod koniec ery Genesis, miała krótką żywotność. Była sprzedawana wyłącznie w Ameryce Północnej i korzystała z blokady regionalnej. Skupienie się firmy Sega na konsoli Sega Saturn sprawiło, że Nomad nie był w pełni wspierany i był niekompatybilny z kilkoma urządzeniami peryferyjnymi Genesis, w tym Power Base Converter, Sega CD i 32X. Sprzedano około 1 miliona egzemplarzy Nomada i jest on uważany za komercyjną porażkę.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Genesis Nomad, также известная как Sega Nomad, - портативная игровая консоль производства компании Sega, выпущенная в Северной Америке в октябре 1995 года. Nomad является портативной версией домашней видеоигровой консоли Sega Genesis (за пределами Северной Америки известной как Mega Drive). Она также могла использоваться с телевизором через видеопорт. Она была создана на основе Mega Jet, портативной версии домашней консоли, предназначенной для использования на авиарейсах в Японии.

Nomad стала последней портативной консолью, выпущенной компанией Sega. Выпущенная в конце эпохи Genesis, она имела короткий срок службы. Она продавалась исключительно в Северной Америке и использовала региональную блокировку. Из-за того, что компания Sega сосредоточилась на выпуске Sega Saturn, Nomad не получила достаточной поддержки, и была несовместима с некоторыми периферийными устройствами Genesis, включая Power Base Converter, Sega CD и 32X. Было продано около 1 млн. экземпляров Nomad, и эта модель считается коммерчески неудачной.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Genesis Nomad, también conocida como Sega Nomad, es una videoconsola portátil fabricada por Sega y lanzada en Norteamérica en octubre de 1995. La Nomad es una variante portátil de la videoconsola doméstica Sega Genesis (conocida como Mega Drive fuera de Norteamérica). También podía utilizarse con un televisor a través de un puerto de vídeo. Se basaba en la Mega Jet, una versión portátil de la consola doméstica diseñada para su uso en los vuelos de las aerolíneas japonesas.

La Nomad fue la última consola portátil lanzada por Sega. Lanzada a finales de la era Genesis, tuvo una vida corta. Se vendió exclusivamente en Norteamérica y utiliza bloqueo regional. Sega se centró en la Sega Saturn, por lo que la Nomad no recibió suficiente apoyo y era incompatible con varios periféricos de la Genesis, como el Power Base Converter, el Sega CD y la 32X. Se vendieron alrededor de un millón de unidades del Nomad, que se considera un fracaso comercial.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Genesis Nomad, auch bekannt als Sega Nomad, ist eine tragbare Spielkonsole, die von Sega hergestellt und im Oktober 1995 in Nordamerika veröffentlicht wurde. Der Nomad ist eine tragbare Variante der Sega Genesis Heimvideospielkonsole (außerhalb Nordamerikas als Mega Drive bekannt). Über einen Videoanschluss konnte sie auch mit einem Fernsehgerät verwendet werden. Es basierte auf dem Mega Jet, einer tragbaren Version der Heimkonsole, die für den Einsatz auf Flugreisen in Japan entwickelt wurde.

Der Nomad war die letzte Handheld-Konsole, die von Sega veröffentlicht wurde. Sie wurde spät in der Genesis-Ära veröffentlicht und hatte nur eine kurze Lebensdauer. Sie wurde ausschließlich in Nordamerika verkauft und verwendet eine regionale Sperre. Da Sega sich auf den Sega Saturn konzentrierte, wurde das Nomad nicht ausreichend unterstützt und war mit verschiedenen Genesis-Peripheriegeräten, wie dem Power Base Converter, der Sega CD und dem 32X, nicht kompatibel. Etwa 1 Million Einheiten des Nomad wurden verkauft, und es wird als kommerzieller Misserfolg betrachtet.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Genesis Nomad, également connue sous le nom de Sega Nomad, est une console de jeu portable fabriquée par Sega et commercialisée en Amérique du Nord en octobre 1995. La Nomad est une variante portable de la console de jeu vidéo de salon Sega Genesis (connue sous le nom de Mega Drive en dehors de l'Amérique du Nord). Elle pouvait également être utilisée avec un téléviseur grâce à un port vidéo. Il était basé sur le Mega Jet, une version portable de la console de salon conçue pour être utilisée sur les vols des compagnies aériennes au Japon.

La Nomad a été la dernière console portable commercialisée par Sega. Sortie à la fin de l'ère Genesis, elle n'a eu qu'une courte durée de vie. Elle a été vendue exclusivement en Amérique du Nord et utilise un système de verrouillage régional. Sega s'étant concentré sur la Sega Saturn, la Nomad n'a pas bénéficié d'un soutien suffisant et elle était incompatible avec plusieurs périphériques de la Genesis, notamment le convertisseur Power Base, le Sega CD et le 32X. Le Nomad a été vendu à environ 1 million d'exemplaires et est considéré comme un échec commercial.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Genesis Nomad, noto anche come Sega Nomad, è una console di gioco portatile prodotta da Sega e rilasciata in Nord America nell'ottobre 1995. Il Nomad è una variante portatile della console per videogiochi domestica Sega Genesis (nota come Mega Drive fuori dal Nord America). Poteva essere utilizzato anche con un televisore tramite una porta video. Era basato sul Mega Jet, una versione portatile della console domestica progettata per l'uso sui voli aerei in Giappone.

Il Nomad fu l'ultima console portatile rilasciata da Sega. Rilasciata alla fine dell'era Genesis, ebbe una vita breve. È stata venduta esclusivamente in Nord America e utilizza il blocco regionale. L'attenzione di Sega per il Sega Saturn ha reso il Nomad poco supportato e incompatibile con diverse periferiche del Genesis, tra cui il Power Base Converter, il Sega CD e il 32X. Il Nomad fu venduto in circa 1 milione di unità ed è considerato un fallimento commerciale.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
