<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.48 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.48 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.20 0.4" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.48 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.48 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.20 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1978</text>
		</text>
		<!-- Support different dates for regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="eu">
			<text>1978</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="us">
			<text>1979</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		<!-- -->
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Philips</text>
		</text>
		<!-- Support different names for regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true" region="eu">
			<text>Philips</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true" region="us">
			<text>Magnavox</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>Kōton Trading Toitarii Enterprise</text>
		</text>
		<!-- -->
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Videopac G7000</text>
		</text>
		<!-- Support different names for regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="us">
			<text>Odyssey²</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>Odyssey²</text>
		</text>
		<!-- -->
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Magnavox Odyssey 2 (stylized as Magnavox Odyssey²), also known as Philips Odyssey 2, is a second generation home video game console that was released in 1978. It was sold in Europe as the Philips Videopac G7000, in Brazil as the Philips Odyssey and in Japan as Odyssey2 (オデッセイ2 odessei2). The Odyssey 2 was one of the major three home consoles prior to the 1983 video game market crash, along with Atari 2600 and Intellivision.

In the early 1970s, Magnavox pioneered the home video game industry by successfully bringing the first home console to market, the Odyssey, which was quickly followed by a number of later models, each with a few technological improvements. In 1978, Magnavox, now a subsidiary of North American Philips, decided to release an all-new successor, Odyssey 2.

In 2009, the video game website IGN named the Odyssey 2 the 21st greatest video game console, out of its list of 25.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Magnavox Odyssey 2 (stylizowany jako Magnavox Odyssey²), znany również jako Philips Odyssey 2, to domowa konsola gier wideo drugiej generacji, która została wydana w 1978 roku. Była sprzedawana w Europie jako Philips Videopac G7000, w Brazylii jako Philips Odyssey, a w Japonii jako Odyssey2 (オデッセイ2 odessei2). Odyssey 2 była jedną z trzech głównych konsol domowych przed krachem rynku gier wideo w 1983 roku, wraz z Atari 2600 i Intellivision.

Na początku lat 70. firma Magnavox była pionierem w branży domowych gier wideo, z powodzeniem wprowadzając na rynek pierwszą konsolę domową, Odyssey, po której szybko pojawiło się kilka późniejszych modeli, każdy z kilkoma ulepszeniami technologicznymi. W 1978 roku Magnavox, obecnie spółka zależna północnoamerykańskiego Philipsa, zdecydowała się na wypuszczenie zupełnie nowego następcy, Odyssey 2.

W 2009 roku serwis internetowy IGN, zajmujący się grami wideo, uznał Odyssey 2 za 21. najlepszą konsolę do gier wideo z listy 25.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка, выпущенная в 1978 году. В Европе известна как Philips Videopac G7000, в Бразилии — Philips Odyssey, в США — Magnavox Odyssey² и Philips Odyssey², а также под несколькими другими названиями.

В начале 1970-х компания Magnavox была инноватором индустрии домашних видеоигр. Они начали очень удачно, представив на рынке игровую приставку Odyssey, за которой последовало несколько моделей с некоторыми технологическими улучшениями. В 1978 году Magnavox (в это время она уже стала дочерней компанией North American Philips) выпустила Odyssey², свою вторую игровую консоль, которую относят ко второму поколению игровых систем.

Одной из сильнейших сторон приставки был модуль синтеза речи, который выпускался в качестве дополнительного модуля для речевых/музыкальных/звуковых эффектов.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Magnavox Odyssey 2 (estilizada como Magnavox Odyssey²), también conocida como Philips Odyssey 2, es una videoconsola doméstica de segunda generación que salió a la venta en 1978. Se vendió en Europa como Philips Videopac G7000, en Brasil como Philips Odyssey y en Japón como Odyssey2 (オデッセイ2 odessei2). La Odyssey 2 fue una de las tres principales consolas domésticas antes de la caída del mercado de los videojuegos en 1983, junto con la Atari 2600 y la Intellivision.

A principios de la década de 1970, Magnavox fue pionera en la industria de los videojuegos domésticos al sacar al mercado con éxito la primera consola doméstica, la Odyssey, a la que siguieron rápidamente varios modelos posteriores, cada uno con algunas mejoras tecnológicas. En 1978, Magnavox, ahora filial de la norteamericana Philips, decidió lanzar una sucesora totalmente nueva, la Odyssey 2.

En 2009, el sitio web de videojuegos IGN nombró a la Odyssey 2 la 21ª mejor videoconsola, de su lista de 25.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Magnavox Odyssey 2 (stilisiert als Magnavox Odyssey²), auch bekannt als Philips Odyssey 2, ist eine Heimvideospielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die 1978 veröffentlicht wurde. Sie wurde in Europa als Philips Videopac G7000, in Brasilien als Philips Odyssey und in Japan als Odyssey2 (オデッセイ2 odessei2) verkauft. Der Odyssey 2 war neben dem Atari 2600 und dem Intellivision eine der drei wichtigsten Heimkonsolen vor dem Zusammenbruch des Videospielmarktes 1983.

Anfang der 1970er Jahre leistete Magnavox Pionierarbeit in der Heimvideospielbranche, indem es die erste Heimkonsole, die Odyssey, auf den Markt brachte, auf die bald eine Reihe weiterer Modelle folgten, die jeweils einige technische Verbesserungen enthielten. 1978 beschloss Magnavox, inzwischen eine Tochtergesellschaft von North American Philips, ein völlig neues Nachfolgemodell, Odyssey 2, auf den Markt zu bringen.

Im Jahr 2009 wurde die Odyssey 2 von der Videospiel-Website IGN als 21. von 25 besten Videospielkonsolen bezeichnet.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Magnavox Odyssey 2 (stylisée en Magnavox Odyssey²), également connue sous le nom de Philips Odyssey 2, est une console de jeux vidéo de salon de deuxième génération sortie en 1978. Elle a été vendue en Europe sous le nom de Philips Videopac G7000, au Brésil sous le nom de Philips Odyssey et au Japon sous le nom d'Odyssey2 (オデッセイ2 odessei2). L'Odyssey 2 était l'une des trois principales consoles de salon avant l'effondrement du marché des jeux vidéo en 1983, avec l'Atari 2600 et l'Intellivision.

Au début des années 1970, Magnavox a fait œuvre de pionnier dans l'industrie du jeu vidéo domestique en commercialisant avec succès la première console de salon, l'Odyssey, qui a été rapidement suivie d'un certain nombre de modèles ultérieurs, chacun comportant quelques améliorations technologiques. En 1978, Magnavox, devenue une filiale de la société nord-américaine Philips, a décidé de lancer un tout nouveau successeur, l'Odyssey 2.

En 2009, le site de jeux vidéo IGN a désigné l'Odyssey 2 comme la 21e plus grande console de jeux vidéo, sur une liste de 25.</text>
			<text lang="it">La Magnavox Odyssey 2 (stilizzata come Magnavox Odyssey²), nota anche come Philips Odyssey 2, è una console per videogiochi domestica di seconda generazione uscita nel 1978. È stata venduta in Europa come Philips Videopac G7000, in Brasile come Philips Odyssey e in Giappone come Odyssey2 (オデッセイ2 odessei2). L'Odyssey 2 è stata una delle tre principali console domestiche prima del crollo del mercato dei videogiochi del 1983, insieme all'Atari 2600 e all'Intellivision.

All'inizio degli anni '70, Magnavox è stata pioniera nel settore dei videogiochi domestici portando con successo sul mercato la prima console domestica, l'Odyssey, che è stata rapidamente seguita da una serie di modelli successivi, ciascuno con alcuni miglioramenti tecnologici. Nel 1978, Magnavox, ora sussidiaria della nordamericana Philips, decise di lanciare sul mercato un successore completamente nuovo, Odyssey 2.

Nel 2009, il sito web di videogiochi IGN ha nominato l'Odyssey 2 la 21a più grande console per videogiochi, su una lista di 25.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
