<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.48 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.20 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1978</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>Magnavox
Odyssey2</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Magnavox Odyssey 2 (stylized as Magnavox Odyssey²), also known as Philips Odyssey 2, is a second generation home video game console that was released in 1978. It was sold in Europe as the Philips Videopac G7000, in Brazil as the Philips Odyssey and in Japan as Odyssey2 (オデッセイ2 odessei2). The Odyssey 2 was one of the major three home consoles prior to the 1983 video game market crash, along with Atari 2600 and Intellivision.

In the early 1970s, Magnavox pioneered the home video game industry by successfully bringing the first home console to market, the Odyssey, which was quickly followed by a number of later models, each with a few technological improvements (see Magnavox Odyssey series). In 1978, Magnavox, now a subsidiary of North American Philips, decided to release an all-new successor, Odyssey 2.

In 2009, the video game website IGN named the Odyssey 2 the 21st greatest video game console, out of its list of 25.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Videopac est une console de jeux vidéo conçue par Magnavox, fabriquée par Philips et commercialisée à la fin des années 1970 et au début des années 1980 sous les marques Philips (Videopac/Odyssey), Radiola-Radiotechnique (Videopac), Schneider (Videopac), Siera (Videopac), Magnavox (Odyssey²), Brandt (Jopac), Continental Edison (Jopac) et Saba (Jopac).

Les cartouches Videopac possédaient toutes un numéro et leurs titres étaient traduits dans les langues des pays de commercialisation. Il n'était pas rare, surtout pour les premières cartouches à avoir été commercialisées que plusieurs jeux soient disponibles sur une cartouche. La sélection s'effectuait à l'aide du clavier intégré aux consoles.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка, выпущенная в 1978 году. В Европе известна как Philips Videopac G7000, в Бразилии — Philips Odyssey, в США — Magnavox Odyssey² и Philips Odyssey², а также под несколькими другими названиями.

В начале 1970-х компания Magnavox была инноватором индустрии домашних видеоигр. Они начали очень удачно, представив на рынке игровую приставку Odyssey, за которой последовало несколько моделей с некоторыми технологическими улучшениями. В 1978 году Magnavox (в это время она уже стала дочерней компанией North American Philips) выпустила Odyssey², свою вторую игровую консоль, которую относят ко второму поколению игровых систем.

Одной из сильнейших сторон приставки был модуль синтеза речи, который выпускался в качестве дополнительного модуля для речевых/музыкальных/звуковых эффектов.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>