<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.27</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.37 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.44 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.16 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/odyssey2.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/odyssey2.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.27</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.37 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.44 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.2</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.16 0.36" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1980</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Philips</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>P2000T</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Philips P2000T home computer was Philips' first real entry in the home computer market in 1980, after the Philips Videopac G7000 game system (better known in North America as the Magnavox Odyssey²) which they already sold to compete with the Atari 2600 and similar game systems.

Philips used components they already produced for other markets (television sets and dictation machines) to quickly design a small computer system. It was partially designed by Austrian professor Dieter Hammer. They also copied the ROM cartridge system from their Videopac G7000 game system. One of these cartridges contained Microsoft BASIC. It was also possible to use cassette tape floppies.
</text>
			<text lang="pl">Komputer domowy Philips P2000T był pierwszym prawdziwym wejściem firmy Philips na rynek komputerów domowych w 1980 roku, po systemie gier Philips Videopac G7000 (lepiej znanym w Ameryce Północnej jako Magnavox Odyssey²), który był już sprzedawany w celu konkurowania z Atari 2600 i podobnymi systemami gier.

Philips wykorzystał komponenty, które już wcześniej produkował na inne rynki (telewizory i maszyny do dyktowania), aby szybko zaprojektować mały system komputerowy. Został on częściowo zaprojektowany przez austriackiego profesora Dietera Hammera. Skopiowano również system kaset ROM z ich systemu gier Videopac G7000. Jedna z tych kaset zawierała Microsoft BASIC. Możliwe było również użycie dyskietek z taśmy magnetofonowej.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Домашний компьютер Philips P2000T стал первым реальным выходом компании Philips на рынок домашних компьютеров в 1980 году, после игровой системы Philips Videopac G7000 (более известной в Северной Америке как Magnavox Odyssey²), которую они уже продавали, чтобы конкурировать с Atari 2600 и аналогичными игровыми системами.

Компания Philips использовала компоненты, которые уже производила для других рынков (телевизоры и диктофоны), для быстрого создания небольшой компьютерной системы. Она была частично разработана австрийским профессором Дитером Хаммером. Они также скопировали систему картриджей ROM со своей игровой системы Videopac G7000. Один из этих картриджей содержал Microsoft BASIC. Также можно было использовать дискеты на кассетной ленте.</text>
			<text lang="es">El ordenador doméstico Philips P2000T fue la primera entrada real de Philips en el mercado de los ordenadores domésticos en 1980, después del sistema de juego Philips Videopac G7000 (más conocido en Norteamérica como Magnavox Odyssey²) que ya vendían para competir con el Atari 2600 y otros sistemas de juego similares.

Philips utilizó componentes que ya producía para otros mercados (televisores y dictáfonos) para diseñar rápidamente un pequeño sistema informático. Fue diseñado parcialmente por el profesor austriaco Dieter Hammer. También copiaron el sistema de cartuchos ROM de su sistema de juegos Videopac G7000. Uno de estos cartuchos contenía Microsoft BASIC. También era posible utilizar disquetes de cinta de casete.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Philips P2000T Heimcomputer war der erste wirkliche Einstieg von Philips in den Heimcomputermarkt im Jahr 1980, nach dem Philips Videopac G7000 Spielsystem (in Nordamerika besser bekannt als Magnavox Odyssey²), das sie bereits verkauften, um mit dem Atari 2600 und ähnlichen Spielsystemen zu konkurrieren.

Philips verwendete Komponenten, die sie bereits für andere Märkte (Fernsehgeräte und Diktiergeräte) hergestellt hatten, um schnell ein kleines Computersystem zu entwickeln. Es wurde teilweise von dem österreichischen Professor Dieter Hammer entworfen. Sie kopierten auch das ROM-Kassettensystem von ihrem Spielsystem Videopac G7000. Eine dieser Kassetten enthielt Microsoft BASIC. Es war auch möglich, Kassetten mit Disketten zu verwenden.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'ordinateur domestique Philips P2000T a été la première véritable entrée de Philips sur le marché des ordinateurs domestiques en 1980, après la console de jeu Philips Videopac G7000 (mieux connue en Amérique du Nord sous le nom de Magnavox Odyssey²) qu'elle avait déjà vendue pour concurrencer l'Atari 2600 et d'autres consoles de jeu similaires.

Philips a utilisé des composants qu'elle produisait déjà pour d'autres marchés (téléviseurs et dictaphones) pour concevoir rapidement un petit système informatique. Celui-ci a été partiellement conçu par le professeur autrichien Dieter Hammer. Philips a également copié le système de cartouches ROM de son système de jeu Videopac G7000. L'une de ces cartouches contenait Microsoft BASIC. Il était également possible d'utiliser des disquettes sur cassette.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il computer domestico Philips P2000T è stato il primo vero ingresso di Philips nel mercato dei computer domestici nel 1980, dopo il sistema di gioco Philips Videopac G7000 (meglio conosciuto in Nord America come Magnavox Odyssey²), già venduto per competere con l'Atari 2600 e sistemi di gioco simili.

Philips utilizzò i componenti già prodotti per altri mercati (televisori e dettatrici) per progettare rapidamente un piccolo sistema informatico. Il sistema fu parzialmente progettato dal professore austriaco Dieter Hammer. Inoltre, copiarono il sistema di cartucce ROM dal loro sistema di gioco Videopac G7000. Una di queste cartucce conteneva il Microsoft BASIC. Era anche possibile utilizzare floppy su cassetta.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
