<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.502 0.5</pos>
			<rotation>90</rotation>
			<maxSize>0.37</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.48</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.39</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.222 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.47</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.485</origin>
			<pos>0.504 0.46</pos>
			<maxSize>0.48</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.224 0.46" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1996</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Palm Inc.</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Palm Pilot</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Palm was a line of personal digital assistants (PDAs) and mobile phones developed by California-based Palm, Inc., originally called Palm Computing, Inc. Palm devices are often remembered as the first wildly popular handheld computers, responsible for ushering in the smartphone era.

The first Palm device, the PalmPilot 1000, was released in 1996 and proved to be popular. It led a growing market for portable computing devices where previous attempts such as Apple's Newton failed or others like Hewlett-Packard's 200LX only serving a niche target market.

Most of Palm's PDAs and mobile phones ran the in-house Palm OS software which was later also licensed to other OEMs.
</text>
			<text lang="pl">Palm to linia osobistych asystentów cyfrowych (PDA) i telefonów komórkowych opracowanych przez kalifornijską firmę Palm, Inc, pierwotnie nazywaną Palm Computing, Inc. Urządzenia Palm są często pamiętane jako pierwsze szalenie popularne komputery przenośne, odpowiedzialne za zapoczątkowanie ery smartfonów.

Pierwsze urządzenie Palm, PalmPilot 1000, zostało wydane w 1996 roku i okazało się popularne. Prowadził on rosnący rynek przenośnych urządzeń komputerowych, gdzie poprzednie próby, takie jak Newton firmy Apple, zawiodły lub inne, takie jak 200LX firmy Hewlett-Packard, służyły tylko niszowemu rynkowi docelowemu.

Większość palmowych urządzeń PDA i telefonów komórkowych działało na wewnętrznym oprogramowaniu Palm OS, które później było również licencjonowane innym producentom OEM.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Palm - это линейка персональных цифровых помощников (PDA) и мобильных телефонов, разработанных калифорнийской компанией Palm, Inc, первоначально называвшейся Palm Computing, Inc. Устройства Palm часто вспоминают как первые дико популярные карманные компьютеры, положившие начало эре смартфонов.

Первое устройство Palm, PalmPilot 1000, было выпущено в 1996 году и оказалось популярным. Оно возглавило растущий рынок портативных вычислительных устройств, где предыдущие попытки, такие как Newton от Apple, не увенчались успехом, а другие, такие как 200LX от Hewlett-Packard, обслуживали только нишу целевого рынка.

Большинство КПК и мобильных телефонов Palm работали на собственном программном обеспечении Palm OS, которое позже было лицензировано и другим производителям комплектующих.</text>
			<text lang="es">Palm fue una línea de asistentes personales digitales (PDA) y teléfonos móviles desarrollada por la empresa californiana Palm, Inc, originalmente llamada Palm Computing, Inc. Los dispositivos Palm se recuerdan a menudo como los primeros ordenadores de mano tremendamente populares, responsables del inicio de la era de los smartphones.

El primer dispositivo Palm, el PalmPilot 1000, salió al mercado en 1996 y demostró su popularidad. Encabezó un mercado creciente de dispositivos informáticos portátiles donde intentos anteriores como el Newton de Apple fracasaron u otros como el 200LX de Hewlett-Packard sólo sirvieron a un nicho de mercado objetivo.

La mayoría de las PDA y teléfonos móviles de Palm funcionaban con el software Palm OS, que más tarde se licenció a otros fabricantes.</text>
			<text lang="de">Palm war eine Reihe von Personal Digital Assistants (PDAs) und Mobiltelefonen, die von der in Kalifornien ansässigen Palm, Inc. entwickelt wurden, die ursprünglich Palm Computing, Inc. hieß. Palm-Geräte werden oft als die ersten sehr beliebten Handheld-Computer bezeichnet, die das Zeitalter der Smartphones einleiteten.

Das erste Palm-Gerät, der PalmPilot 1000, wurde 1996 auf den Markt gebracht und erwies sich als sehr beliebt. Es führte einen wachsenden Markt für tragbare Computer an, wo frühere Versuche wie der Newton von Apple scheiterten oder andere wie der 200LX von Hewlett-Packard nur einen Nischenmarkt bedienten.

Die meisten PDAs und Mobiltelefone von Palm liefen mit der hauseigenen Palm OS-Software, die später auch an andere OEMs lizenziert wurde.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Palm est une gamme d'assistants numériques personnels (PDA) et de téléphones mobiles développée par la société californienne Palm, Inc. qui s'appelait à l'origine Palm Computing, Inc. Les appareils Palm sont souvent considérés comme les premiers ordinateurs de poche très populaires, qui ont inauguré l'ère des smartphones.

Le premier appareil Palm, le PalmPilot 1000, est sorti en 1996 et s'est avéré très populaire. Il a été à l'origine d'un marché en pleine expansion pour les appareils informatiques portables, alors que les tentatives précédentes, comme le Newton d'Apple, avaient échoué ou que d'autres, comme le 200LX de Hewlett-Packard, n'avaient servi qu'un marché cible de niche.

La plupart des PDA et des téléphones mobiles de Palm fonctionnent avec le logiciel interne Palm OS, qui a ensuite été cédé sous licence à d'autres fabricants de matériel informatique.</text>
			<text lang="it">Palm è stata una linea di assistenti digitali personali (PDA) e telefoni cellulari sviluppata dalla società californiana Palm, Inc., originariamente chiamata Palm Computing, Inc. I dispositivi Palm sono spesso ricordati come i primi computer palmari estremamente popolari, responsabili di aver dato il via all'era degli smartphone.

Il primo dispositivo Palm, il PalmPilot 1000, è stato rilasciato nel 1996 e si è rivelato molto popolare. Ha guidato un mercato in crescita per i dispositivi informatici portatili dove i tentativi precedenti, come il Newton di Apple, sono falliti o altri, come il 200LX di Hewlett-Packard, hanno servito solo una nicchia di mercato.

La maggior parte dei PDA e dei telefoni cellulari di Palm utilizzava il software Palm OS interno, che in seguito è stato concesso in licenza anche ad altri OEM.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
