<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.502 0.394</pos>
			<maxSize>0.345</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.222 0.394" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1996</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Palm Inc.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Palm Pilot</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>Palm was a line of personal digital assistants (PDAs) and mobile phones developed by California-based Palm, Inc., originally called Palm Computing, Inc. Palm devices are often remembered as the first wildly popular handheld computers, responsible for ushering in the smartphone era.

The first Palm device, the PalmPilot 1000, was released in 1996 and proved to be popular. It led a growing market for portable computing devices where previous attempts such as Apple's Newton failed or others like Hewlett-Packard's 200LX only serving a niche target market.

Most of Palm's PDAs and mobile phones ran the in-house Palm OS software which was later also licensed to other OEMs.
</text>
			<text lang="pl">Palm to linia osobistych asystentów cyfrowych (PDA) i telefonów komórkowych opracowanych przez kalifornijską firmę Palm, Inc, pierwotnie nazywaną Palm Computing, Inc. Urządzenia Palm są często pamiętane jako pierwsze szalenie popularne komputery przenośne, odpowiedzialne za zapoczątkowanie ery smartfonów.

Pierwsze urządzenie Palm, PalmPilot 1000, zostało wydane w 1996 roku i okazało się popularne. Prowadził on rosnący rynek przenośnych urządzeń komputerowych, gdzie poprzednie próby, takie jak Newton firmy Apple, zawiodły lub inne, takie jak 200LX firmy Hewlett-Packard, służyły tylko niszowemu rynkowi docelowemu.

Większość palmowych urządzeń PDA i telefonów komórkowych działało na wewnętrznym oprogramowaniu Palm OS, które później było również licencjonowane innym producentom OEM.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Palm - это линейка персональных цифровых помощников (PDA) и мобильных телефонов, разработанных калифорнийской компанией Palm, Inc, первоначально называвшейся Palm Computing, Inc. Устройства Palm часто вспоминают как первые дико популярные карманные компьютеры, положившие начало эре смартфонов.

Первое устройство Palm, PalmPilot 1000, было выпущено в 1996 году и оказалось популярным. Оно возглавило растущий рынок портативных вычислительных устройств, где предыдущие попытки, такие как Newton от Apple, не увенчались успехом, а другие, такие как 200LX от Hewlett-Packard, обслуживали только нишу целевого рынка.

Большинство КПК и мобильных телефонов Palm работали на собственном программном обеспечении Palm OS, которое позже было лицензировано и другим производителям комплектующих.</text>
			<text lang="it">Palm è stata una linea di assistenti digitali personali (PDA) e telefoni cellulari sviluppata dalla società californiana Palm, Inc., originariamente chiamata Palm Computing, Inc. I dispositivi Palm sono spesso ricordati come i primi computer palmari estremamente popolari, responsabili di aver dato il via all'era degli smartphone.

Il primo dispositivo Palm, il PalmPilot 1000, è stato rilasciato nel 1996 e si è rivelato molto popolare. Ha guidato un mercato in crescita per i dispositivi informatici portatili dove i tentativi precedenti, come il Newton di Apple, sono falliti o altri, come il 200LX di Hewlett-Packard, hanno servito solo una nicchia di mercato.

La maggior parte dei PDA e dei telefoni cellulari di Palm utilizzava il software Palm OS interno, che in seguito è stato concesso in licenza anche ad altri OEM.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
