<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.365</pos>
			<maxSize>0.20</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.21 0.365" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.365</pos>
			<maxSize>0.19</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.21 0.365" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Nec</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>PC-9800 Series</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>NEC PC-9801 - a not-quite-industry-standard PC line of personal computers developed in 1982 in Japan by NEC Corporation based on IBM solutions, aimed exclusively at the Japanese market.

The first model was a 16-bit architecture with an Intel 8086 processor clocked at 5 MHz and 128 KB of RAM. It shipped with graphics cards capable of displaying 8 colors at 640x400 resolution - a clear performance differentiator compared to PCs of the time.

Initially conceived as a solution for industrial and office applications, by 1987 the PC-9801 series captured nearly 90% of the Japanese personal computer market. Over time, as power increased and graphics and sound effects were appreciated by home users (especially gamers), it also became popular for non-commercial applications - the Touhou Project series, for example, made its debut.</text>
			<text lang="pl">NEC PC-9801 – nie w pełni kompatybilna z przemysłowym standardem PC lina komputerów osobistych stworzona w 1982 w Japonii przez NEC Corporation na bazie rozwiązań IBM, skierowana wyłącznie na rynek japoński.

Pierwszy model był architekturą 16-bitową z procesorem Intel 8086 taktowanym zegarem 5 MHz oraz 128 KB pamięci RAM. Dostarczany z kartami grafiki zdolnymi wyświetlać 8 kolorów w rozdzielczości 640x400 - co wyraźnie wyróżniało się osiągami w stosunku do ówczesnych PC.

Początkowo pomyślany jako rozwiązanie dla zastosowań przemysłowych i biurowych, w roku 1987 seria PC-9801 zajęła blisko 90% japońskiego rynku komputerów osobistych. Z czasem, wraz ze wzrostem mocy i docenieniem efektów graficznych i dźwiękowych przez użytkowników domowych (zwłaszcza graczy) stał się popularny także w niekomercyjnych zastosowaniach – zadebiutowała na nich np seria Touhou Project.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Форм-фактор компьютеров производства NEC, доминировавший на японском рынке персональных компьютеров для дома и бизнеса в 1980—1990-х годах.

Первая модель стандарта PC-98 — PC-9801 — была выпущена в октябре 1982 года. Она была оснащена процессором Intel 8086 с частотой 5 МГц, двумя графическими контроллерами µPD7220 (один для текста, другой для графики), 128 Кб оперативной памяти, расширяемой до 640 Кб. 8-цветный дисплей имел максимальное разрешение 640×400 пикселей. Следующая модель, PC-9801E, появившаяся в 1983 году была оснащена процессором 8086-2, который мог переключаться между частотами в 5 и 8 МГц. В начале 1990-х 50 % всех проданных в Японии компьютеров были PC-98. Последним из представителей линейки этих компьютеров был PC-9821Ra43, основанный на процессоре Celeron с частотой 433 МГц, появившийся в 2000 году.</text>
			<text lang="es">NEC PC-9801 - una línea de ordenadores personales no del todo estándar desarrollada en 1982 en Japón por NEC Corporation sobre la base de soluciones IBM, destinada exclusivamente al mercado japonés.

El primer modelo tenía una arquitectura de 16 bits con un procesador Intel 8086 a 5 MHz y 128 KB de RAM. Se suministraba con tarjetas gráficas capaces de mostrar 8 colores a una resolución de 640x400, lo que suponía una clara diferencia de rendimiento con respecto a los PC de la época.

Concebida inicialmente como una solución para aplicaciones industriales y de oficina, en 1987 la serie PC-9801 acaparaba casi el 90% del mercado japonés de ordenadores personales. Con el tiempo, a medida que aumentaba la potencia y los gráficos y efectos de sonido eran apreciados por los usuarios domésticos (especialmente los jugadores), también se hizo popular para aplicaciones no comerciales: debutó, por ejemplo, la serie Touhou Project.</text>
			<text lang="de">NEC PC-9801 - eine nicht ganz dem Industriestandard entsprechende PC-Reihe von Personal Computern, die 1982 in Japan von der NEC Corporation auf der Grundlage von IBM-Lösungen entwickelt wurde und ausschließlich für den japanischen Markt bestimmt war.

Das erste Modell verfügte über eine 16-Bit-Architektur mit einem mit 5 MHz getakteten Intel 8086-Prozessor und 128 KB RAM. Es wurde mit Grafikkarten ausgeliefert, die 8 Farben bei einer Auflösung von 640x400 darstellen konnten - ein deutliches Leistungsunterscheidungsmerkmal zu den damaligen PCs.

Ursprünglich als Lösung für Industrie- und Büroanwendungen konzipiert, eroberte die PC-9801-Serie bis 1987 fast 90 % des japanischen PC-Marktes. Im Laufe der Zeit, als die Leistung zunahm und Grafik- und Soundeffekte von Heimanwendern (vor allem von Spielern) geschätzt wurden, wurden sie auch für nicht-kommerzielle Anwendungen beliebt - die Touhou Project-Serie zum Beispiel hatte ihr Debüt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">NEC PC-9801 - ligne d'ordinateurs personnels ne répondant pas aux normes industrielles, développée en 1982 au Japon par NEC Corporation sur la base de solutions IBM et destinée exclusivement au marché japonais.

Le premier modèle était une architecture 16 bits avec un processeur Intel 8086 cadencé à 5 MHz et 128 KB de RAM. Il était livré avec des cartes graphiques capables d'afficher 8 couleurs à une résolution de 640x400, ce qui constituait une nette différence de performance par rapport aux PC de l'époque.

Conçue à l'origine comme une solution pour les applications industrielles et bureautiques, la série PC-9801 a conquis en 1987 près de 90 % du marché japonais des ordinateurs personnels. Au fil du temps, avec l'augmentation de la puissance et l'appréciation des graphiques et des effets sonores par les particuliers (en particulier les joueurs), elle est également devenue populaire pour les applications non commerciales - la série Touhou Project, par exemple, a fait ses débuts.</text>
			<text lang="it">NEC PC-9801 è stata una linea di personal computer sviluppata nel 1982 in Giappone da NEC Corporation sulla base di soluzioni IBM e destinata esclusivamente al mercato giapponese.

Il primo modello aveva un'architettura a 16 bit con processore Intel 8086 a 5 MHz e 128 KB di RAM. Veniva fornito con schede grafiche in grado di visualizzare 8 colori alla risoluzione di 640x400, un chiaro elemento di differenziazione delle prestazioni rispetto ai PC dell'epoca.

Inizialmente concepita come soluzione per applicazioni industriali e d'ufficio, nel 1987 la serie PC-9801 aveva conquistato quasi il 90% del mercato giapponese dei personal computer. Nel corso del tempo, con l'aumento della potenza e l'apprezzamento della grafica e degli effetti sonori da parte degli utenti domestici (in particolare i giocatori), divenne popolare anche per applicazioni non commerciali - la serie Touhou Project, ad esempio, fece il suo debutto.</text>
			<text lang="pt">NEC PC-9801 – uma linha de computadores pessoais não totalmente compatível com o padrão industrial PC, criada em 1982 no Japão pela NEC Corporation com base em soluções da IBM, direcionada exclusivamente para o mercado japonês.

O primeiro modelo era uma arquitetura de 16 bits com um processador Intel 8086 com clock de 5 MHz e 128 KB de RAM. Era fornecido com placas gráficas capazes de exibir 8 cores em resolução de 640x400 – o que o diferenciava claramente em termos de desempenho em relação aos PCs da época.

Inicialmente concebido como solução para aplicações industriais e de escritório, em 1987 a série PC-9801 ocupou cerca de 90% do mercado japonês de computadores pessoais. Com o tempo, com o aumento de sua potência e a valorização dos efeitos gráficos e sonoros pelos usuários domésticos (especialmente os jogadores), ele se tornou popular também em aplicações não comerciais – como, por exemplo, a série Touhou Project estreou neles.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
