<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.36</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.415</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.415" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.36</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.415</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.415" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1987</text>
		</text>
	<!-- Regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="us">
			<text>1987</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true" region="jp"/>
		
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Nec</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>PC Engine</text>
		</text>
	<!-- Regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="us">
			<text>TurboGrafx-16</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="jp"/>
		
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The TurboGrafx-16, known as the PC Engine in Japan and France, is a 16-bit fourth-generation home video game console designed by Hudson Soft and sold by NEC Home Electronics. It was released in Japan in 1987 and in North America in 1989. The Japanese model was imported and distributed in France in 1989, and the United Kingdom and Spain received a version based on the American model known as simply TurboGrafx. It was the first console released in the 16-bit era, although it used a modified 8-bit CPU. In Japan, the system was launched as a competitor to the Famicom, but the delayed United States release meant that it ended up competing with the Sega Genesis and later the Super Nintendo Entertainment System.

The TurboGrafx-16 has an 8-bit CPU, a 16-bit video color encoder, and a 16-bit video display controller. The GPUs are capable of displaying 482 colors simultaneously, out of 512. With dimensions of just 14 cm × 14 cm × 3.8 cm (5.5 in × 5.5 in × 1.5 in), the Japanese PC Engine is the smallest major home game console ever made. Games were released on HuCard cartridges and later the CD-ROM optical format with the TurboGrafx-CD add-on.</text>
			<text lang="pl">TurboGrafx-16 Am.Płn./PC EngineJP – 8-bitowa konsola z 16-bitowym układem graficznym, wydana po raz pierwszy 30 października 1987 roku w Japonii, gdzie znana jest pod nazwą PC Engine. Swoją premierę w Ameryce Północnej konsola miała 29 sierpnia 1989. TurboGrafx-16 nie miał oficjalnej premiery PAL, ale bardzo ograniczona ilość konsol dostała się głównie na rynek Wielkiej Brytanii.

Konsola powstała dzięki współpracy pomiędzy Hudson Soft (odpowiedzialny głównie za produkcję chipów) oraz NEC. Charakterystyczną cechą konsoli był jej niewielki rozmiar, osiągnięty głównie dzięki zastosowaniu tylko trzech układów scalonych oraz używania niewielkich, przypominających karty płatnicze nośników danych, znanych pod nazwą „HuCard” (od Hudson Card; w wersji Amerykańskiej znana bardziej jako „TurboChip”). TurboGrafx-16 był pierwszą konsolą, używającą jako nośnika danych płyty CD-ROM.

Początkowo PC Engine osiągnął znaczny sukces w Japonii, gdzie cieszył się lepszymi wynikami sprzedaży niż nawet Nintendo Famicom. Japońska popularność konsoli nie przekładała się jednak na zainteresowanie w Ameryce Północnej, gdzie konsola nie sprzedawała się tak dobrze, głównie z powodu słabego wsparcia twórców oraz wydawców gier.</text>
			<text lang="ru">8-16 разрядная игровая приставка, выпущенная NEC в Японии 30 октября 1987 года, в Северной Америке в конце августа 1989 года под именем TurboGrafx-16. В регионе PAL приставка не продавалась, если не считать релиза в 1990 году в Великобритании. Эта версия называлась TurboGrafx и была выпущена в очень ограниченном количестве. Неофициально эта версия продавалась во Франции и Бенилюксе.

PC Engine была 8-разрядной приставкой с двойным 16-разрядным графическим процессором, с возможностью отображения 482 цветов одновременно.

PC Engine по тем временам была системой нового поколения. Носителем был картридж в формате HuCard. Компания NEC первая стала выпускать игры на компакт-дисках, в которые можно было играть, используя дополнительное устройство — Turbografx CD.

Небольшие размеры PC Engine — всего 14 см x 14 см x 3.8 см (5.5 дюймов x 5.5 дюймов x 1.5 дюйма) — позволили ей стать рекордсменом в звании самой маленькой игровой приставки из когда-либо созданных, по версии книги рекордов Гиннесса в области компьютерных игр (англ. Guinness World Records Gamer’s Edition, 2008).

В 2009 году PC Engine была помещена на тринадцатое место в списке «25 игровых приставок всех времён» по версии сайта IGN.</text>
			<text lang="es">La TurboGrafx-16, conocida como PC Engine en Japón y Francia, es una videoconsola doméstica de 16 bits de cuarta generación diseñada por Hudson Soft y comercializada por NEC Home Electronics. Salió a la venta en Japón en 1987 y en Norteamérica en 1989. El modelo japonés se importó y distribuyó en Francia en 1989, y el Reino Unido y España recibieron una versión basada en el modelo americano conocida simplemente como TurboGrafx. Fue la primera consola lanzada en la era de los 16 bits, aunque utilizaba una CPU modificada de 8 bits. En Japón, la consola se lanzó como competidora de la Famicom, pero el retraso en su lanzamiento en Estados Unidos hizo que acabara compitiendo con la Sega Genesis y, más tarde, con la Super Nintendo Entertainment System.

El TurboGrafx-16 tiene una CPU de 8 bits, un codificador de color de vídeo de 16 bits y un controlador de pantalla de vídeo de 16 bits. La GPU es capaz de mostrar 482 colores simultáneamente, de un total de 512. Con unas dimensiones de sólo 14 cm × 14 cm × 3,8 cm (5,5 in × 5,5 in × 1,5 in), la PC Engine japonesa es la videoconsola doméstica más pequeña jamás fabricada. Los juegos se lanzaron en cartuchos HuCard y, más tarde, en formato óptico CD-ROM con el complemento TurboGrafx-CD.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der TurboGrafx-16, in Japan und Frankreich als PC Engine bekannt, ist eine 16-Bit-Heimvideospielkonsole der vierten Generation, die von Hudson Soft entwickelt und von NEC Home Electronics verkauft wurde. Sie wurde 1987 in Japan und 1989 in Nordamerika veröffentlicht. Das japanische Modell wurde 1989 nach Frankreich importiert und dort vertrieben, und das Vereinigte Königreich und Spanien erhielten eine Version, die auf dem amerikanischen Modell basierte und einfach TurboGrafx genannt wurde. Es war die erste Konsole, die in der 16-Bit-Ära veröffentlicht wurde, obwohl sie eine modifizierte 8-Bit-CPU verwendete. In Japan wurde das System als Konkurrent des Famicom auf den Markt gebracht, aber die verzögerte Veröffentlichung in den USA bedeutete, dass es schließlich mit dem Sega Genesis und später dem Super Nintendo Entertainment System konkurrierte.

Der TurboGrafx-16 hat eine 8-Bit-CPU, einen 16-Bit-Videofarbcodierer und einen 16-Bit-Videobildschirm-Controller. Die Grafikprozessoren sind in der Lage, 482 von 512 Farben gleichzeitig darzustellen. Mit Abmessungen von nur 14 cm × 14 cm × 3,8 cm ist die japanische PC-Engine die kleinste große Heimspielkonsole, die je hergestellt wurde. Die Spiele wurden auf HuCard-Kassetten und später im optischen CD-ROM-Format mit dem TurboGrafx-CD-Add-on veröffentlicht.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La TurboGrafx-16, connue sous le nom de PC Engine au Japon et en France, est une console de jeux vidéo 16 bits de quatrième génération conçue par Hudson Soft et vendue par NEC Home Electronics. Elle est sortie au Japon en 1987 et en Amérique du Nord en 1989. Le modèle japonais a été importé et distribué en France en 1989, et le Royaume-Uni et l'Espagne ont reçu une version basée sur le modèle américain, connue sous le nom de TurboGrafx. Il s'agit de la première console de l'ère 16 bits, bien qu'elle utilise un processeur 8 bits modifié. Au Japon, la console a été lancée pour concurrencer la Famicom, mais sa sortie retardée aux États-Unis l'a mise en concurrence avec la Sega Genesis et, plus tard, avec la Super Nintendo Entertainment System.

Le TurboGrafx-16 possède un processeur 8 bits, un encodeur de couleurs vidéo 16 bits et un contrôleur d'affichage vidéo 16 bits. Les GPU sont capables d'afficher 482 couleurs simultanément, sur 512. Avec des dimensions de seulement 14 cm × 14 cm × 3,8 cm (5,5 in × 5,5 in × 1,5 in), la PC Engine japonaise est la plus petite console de jeu de salon jamais fabriquée. Les jeux ont été publiés sur des cartouches HuCard et, plus tard, au format optique CD-ROM avec l'extension TurboGrafx-CD.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il TurboGrafx-16, noto come PC Engine in Giappone e Francia, è una console per videogiochi domestici di quarta generazione a 16 bit progettata da Hudson Soft e venduta da NEC Home Electronics. È stata rilasciata in Giappone nel 1987 e in Nord America nel 1989. Il modello giapponese è stato importato e distribuito in Francia nel 1989, mentre il Regno Unito e la Spagna hanno ricevuto una versione basata sul modello americano, nota semplicemente come TurboGrafx. Fu la prima console rilasciata nell'era dei 16 bit, sebbene utilizzasse una CPU modificata a 8 bit. In Giappone, la console fu lanciata come concorrente del Famicom, ma il ritardo nell'uscita negli Stati Uniti fece sì che finisse per competere con il Sega Genesis e successivamente con il Super Nintendo Entertainment System.

Il TurboGrafx-16 è dotato di una CPU a 8 bit, un codificatore video a 16 bit e un controller video a 16 bit. Le GPU sono in grado di visualizzare 482 colori simultaneamente, su 512. Con dimensioni di soli 14 cm × 14 cm × 3,8 cm (5,5 in × 5,5 in × 1,5 in), il PC Engine giapponese è la più piccola console per videogiochi mai realizzata. I giochi sono stati rilasciati su cartucce HuCard e successivamente sul formato ottico CD-ROM con il componente aggiuntivo TurboGrafx-CD.</text>
			<text lang="pt">TurboGrafx-16 Am.Płn./PC EngineJP – console de 8 bits com um chip gráfico de 16 bits, lançada pela primeira vez em 30 de outubro de 1987 no Japão, onde é conhecida como PC Engine. A console estreou na América do Norte em 29 de agosto de 1989. O TurboGrafx-16 não teve lançamento oficial PAL, mas uma quantidade muito limitada de consoles chegou principalmente ao mercado do Reino Unido.

A console nasceu da colaboração entre a Hudson Soft (principalmente responsável pela produção de chips) e a NEC. Uma característica distintiva da console era seu pequeno tamanho, alcançado principalmente pelo uso de apenas três chips e pela utilização de pequenos cartuchos de dados, semelhantes a cartões de crédito, conhecidos como "HuCard" (de Hudson Card; na versão americana, conhecida mais como "TurboChip"). O TurboGrafx-16 foi o primeiro console a usar um disco CD-ROM como meio de armazenamento de dados.

Inicialmente, o PC Engine obteve grande sucesso no Japão, onde teve melhores resultados de vendas do que até mesmo o Nintendo Famicom. No entanto, a popularidade japonesa do console não se traduziu em interesse na América do Norte, onde o console não se vendeu tão bem, principalmente devido ao fraco apoio dos desenvolvedores e editores de jogos.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
