<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.3 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.393 0.455</pos>
			<maxSize>0.275</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.113 0.455" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.3 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.393 0.455</pos>
			<maxSize>0.265</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.113 0.455" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1961</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Digital Equipment Corporation</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>PDP-1</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) is the first computer in Digital Equipment Corporation's PDP series and was first produced in 1959. It is famous for being the computer most important in the creation of hacker culture at Massachusetts Institute of Technology, BBN and elsewhere.
The PDP-1 is the original hardware for playing history's first game on a minicomputer, Steve Russell's Spacewar!

The PDP-1 uses an 18-bit word size and has 4096 words as standard main memory, upgradable to 65,536 words.
It is built mostly of DEC 1000-series System Building Blocks, using micro-alloy and micro-alloy diffused transistors with a rated switching speed of 5 MHz. The System Building Blocks are packaged into several 19-inch racks. The racks are themselves packaged into a single large mainframe case, with a hexagonal control panel containing switches and lights mounted to lie at table-top height at one end of the mainframe. Above the control panel is the system's standard input/output solution, a punched tape reader and writer.

The PDP-1 weighed about 730 kg (1,600 lb).
</text>
			<text lang="pl">PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) to pierwszy komputer z serii PDP firmy Digital Equipment Corporation, wyprodukowany w 1959 roku. Jest znany jako komputer, który miał największy wpływ na powstanie kultury hakerów w Massachusetts Institute of Technology, BBN i innych miejscach.
PDP-1 to oryginalny sprzęt, na którym można było zagrać w pierwszą w historii grę na minikomputerze - Spacewar Steve'a Russella!

PDP-1 używa 18-bitowego rozmiaru znaków i ma 4096 znaków jako standardową pamięć główną, z możliwością rozszerzenia do 65 536 znaków.
Zbudowany jest głównie z System Building Blocks serii DEC 1000, z wykorzystaniem tranzystorów mikrostopowych i mikrostopowych rozproszonych o znamionowej szybkości przełączania 5 MHz. Bloki systemowe są umieszczone w kilku 19-calowych stojakach. Same szafy są umieszczone w jednej dużej obudowie typu mainframe, z sześciokątnym panelem sterowania zawierającym przełączniki i kontrolki, zamontowanym na wysokości stołu na jednym końcu szafy. Nad panelem kontrolnym znajduje się standardowe rozwiązanie wejścia/wyjścia systemu - czytnik i nagrywarka taśmy dziurkowanej.

PDP-1 ważyła około 730 kg (1600 funtów).</text>
			<text lang="ru">(Programmed Data Processor-1) — первый компьютер из серии PDP, произведённый Digital Equipment Corporation в 1960 году.

PDP-1 был создан на основе идей компьютера TX-0, созданного в Лаборатории Линкольна в Массачусетском технологическом институте. Команда разработчиков TX-0, TX-1 и TX-2 покинула проект и основала компанию Digital Equipment Corporation, а PDP-1 стал первым продуктом компании.

Всего было продано 50 экземпляров PDP-1. Серийный номер 1 был продан компании Bolt Beranek and Newman (BBN), а второй — бесплатно подарен МТИ.

PDP-1 имел 18-битное машинное слово и 4 килослова основной памяти (эквивалентно 9 КБ) с возможностью расширения до 64 килослов (144 КБ). Цикл перемагничивания памяти на ферритовых элементах занимал 5 микросекунд (примерно соответствует тактовой частоте 200 КГц); соответственно, большинство арифметических операций занимало 10 микросекунд (100 000 операций в секунду), потому что они имели два обращения к памяти: одно для инструкции, другое - для операндов.</text>
			<text lang="es">El PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) es el primer ordenador de la serie PDP de Digital Equipment Corporation y se fabricó por primera vez en 1959. Es famoso por ser el ordenador más importante en la creación de la cultura hacker en el Instituto Tecnológico de Massachusetts, BBN y otros lugares.
El PDP-1 es el hardware original para jugar al primer juego de la historia en un miniordenador, el Spacewar! de Steve Russell.

El PDP-1 utiliza un tamaño de palabra de 18 bits y tiene 4096 palabras como memoria principal estándar, ampliable a 65.536 palabras.
Está construido principalmente con System Building Blocks DEC de la serie 1000, que utilizan transistores difusos de microaleación y microaleación con una velocidad nominal de conmutación de 5 MHz. Los System Building Blocks están empaquetados en varios racks de 19 pulgadas. A su vez, los bastidores están empaquetados en una única caja grande de ordenador central, con un panel de control hexagonal que contiene interruptores y luces montados a la altura de una mesa en un extremo del ordenador central. Encima del panel de control se encuentra la solución de entrada/salida estándar del sistema, un lector y grabador de cinta perforada.

El PDP-1 pesaba unos 730 kg.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) ist der erste Computer der PDP-Serie der Digital Equipment Corporation und wurde erstmals 1959 hergestellt. Er ist bekannt dafür, dass er der wichtigste Computer für die Entstehung der Hackerkultur am Massachusetts Institute of Technology, bei BBN und anderswo war.
Die PDP-1 ist die Originalhardware für das erste Spiel der Geschichte auf einem Minicomputer, Steve Russells Spacewar!

Die PDP-1 verwendet eine 18-Bit-Wortgröße und hat 4096 Wörter als Standard-Hauptspeicher, der auf 65.536 Wörter aufrüstbar ist.
Sie besteht größtenteils aus System Building Blocks der DEC 1000-Serie, die Mikrolegierungs- und Mikrolegierungs-Diffusionstransistoren mit einer Nennschaltgeschwindigkeit von 5 MHz verwenden. Die System Building Blocks sind in mehrere 19-Zoll-Racks verpackt. Die Racks selbst sind in einem einzigen großen Mainframe-Gehäuse untergebracht, an dessen einem Ende in Tischhöhe ein sechseckiges Bedienfeld mit Schaltern und Leuchten angebracht ist. Über dem Bedienfeld befindet sich die Standard-Ein-/Ausgabelösung des Systems, ein Lochbandleser und -schreiber.

Die PDP-1 wog etwa 730 kg (1.600 lb).</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) est le premier ordinateur de la série PDP de Digital Equipment Corporation et a été produit pour la première fois en 1959. Il est célèbre pour avoir été l'ordinateur le plus important dans la création de la culture hacker au Massachusetts Institute of Technology, à BBN et ailleurs.
Le PDP-1 est le matériel original pour jouer au premier jeu de l'histoire sur un mini-ordinateur, Spacewar ! de Steve Russell.

Le PDP-1 utilise une taille de mot de 18 bits et dispose d'une mémoire principale standard de 4096 mots, extensible à 65 536 mots.
Il est construit principalement à partir de DEC 1000-series System Building Blocks, utilisant des transistors diffusés en micro-alliage et micro-alliage avec une vitesse de commutation nominale de 5 MHz. Les System Building Blocks sont emballés dans plusieurs racks de 19 pouces. Les racks sont eux-mêmes emballés dans un seul grand boîtier d'ordinateur central, avec un panneau de commande hexagonal contenant des interrupteurs et des voyants montés à hauteur de table à l'une des extrémités de l'ordinateur central. Au-dessus du panneau de commande se trouve la solution d'entrée/sortie standard du système, un lecteur et un graveur de bandes perforées.

Le PDP-1 pesait environ 730 kg.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) è il primo computer della serie PDP di Digital Equipment Corporation e fu prodotto per la prima volta nel 1959. È famoso per essere stato il computer più importante per la creazione della cultura hacker al Massachusetts Institute of Technology, alla BBN e altrove.
Il PDP-1 è l'hardware originale per giocare al primo gioco della storia su minicomputer, Spacewar! di Steve Russell.

Il PDP-1 utilizza una dimensione di word di 18 bit e ha 4096 word come memoria principale standard, aggiornabili a 65.536 parole.
È costruito principalmente con i System Building Block della serie DEC 1000, che utilizzano transistor diffusi in micro-lega e micro-lega con una velocità di commutazione nominale di 5 MHz. I blocchi di sistema sono imballati in diversi rack da 19 pollici. I rack sono a loro volta imballati in un unico grande contenitore per mainframe, con un pannello di controllo esagonale contenente interruttori e luci montato all'altezza di un tavolo a un'estremità del mainframe. Sopra il pannello di controllo si trova la soluzione di input/output standard del sistema, un lettore e uno scrittore di nastri perforati.

Il PDP-1 pesava circa 730 kg.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
