<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.345</pos>
			<maxSize>0.284</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.37 0.5</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.345" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>2014</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>PICO-8</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>PICO-8 is a fantasy console for making, sharing and playing tiny games and other computer programs. It feels like a regular console, but runs on Windows / Mac / Linux. When you turn it on, the machine greets you with a commandline, a suite of cartridge creation tools, and an online cartridge browser called SPLORE.</text>
			<text lang="pl">PICO-8 jest fantazyjną konsolą do tworzenia, dzielenia się i grania w małe gry i inne programy komputerowe. Wygląda jak zwykła konsola, ale działa na Windowsie / Macu / Linuksie. Kiedy ją włączasz, wita cię wierszem poleceń, zestawem narzędzi do tworzenia kartridży oraz przeglądarką kartridży online o nazwie SPLORE.</text>
			<text lang="ru">PICO-8 является вымышленной консолью для создания, обмена и воспроизведения крошечных игр и других компьютерных программ. Когда вы включите её, машина встречает вас строкой для ввода Lua-команд и предоставляет простые встроенные инструменты для создания собственных картриджей.</text>
			<text lang="es">PICO-8 es una consola de fantasía para crear, compartir y jugar a pequeños juegos y otros programas informáticos. Parece una consola normal, pero funciona con Windows / Mac / Linux. Al encenderla, la máquina te da la bienvenida con una línea de comandos, un conjunto de herramientas de creación de cartuchos y un navegador de cartuchos en línea llamado SPLORE.</text>
			<text lang="de">PICO-8 ist eine fantastische Konsole zum Erstellen, Teilen und Spielen von kleinen Spielen und anderen Computerprogrammen. Sie fühlt sich an wie eine normale Konsole, läuft aber unter Windows/Mac/Linux. Beim Einschalten begrüßt dich das Gerät mit einer Kommandozeile, einer Reihe von Tools zur Erstellung von Cartridges und einem Online-Cartridge-Browser namens SPLORE.</text>
			<text lang="fr">PICO-8 est une console fantaisiste permettant de créer, de partager et de jouer à des jeux miniatures et à d'autres programmes informatiques. Elle ressemble à une console classique, mais fonctionne sous Windows / Mac / Linux. Lorsque vous l'allumez, la machine vous accueille avec une ligne de commande, une suite d'outils de création de cartouches et un navigateur de cartouches en ligne appelé SPLORE.</text>
			<text lang="it">PICO-8 è una console di fantasia per creare, condividere e giocare con piccoli giochi e altri programmi per computer. Sembra una normale console, ma funziona su Windows / Mac / Linux. Quando la si accende, la macchina ci accoglie con una linea di comando, una suite di strumenti per la creazione di cartucce e un browser online per le cartucce chiamato SPLORE.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
