<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysart" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/fpinball.png</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/4K/fpinball.png</path>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.395</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.455</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.405</pos>
			<maxSize>0.245</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.405" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/fpinball.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/fpinball.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.395</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.455</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.408</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.408" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2017</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Zen Studios</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Pinball FX3</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Pinball FX 3 is a pinball simulator video game developed and published by Zen Studios and released for Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 in September 2017 and then released for the Nintendo Switch in December 2017.

Pinball FX 3 allows players to play one of several simulated pinball tables, and includes online scoreboard support for informal competition with other players. The game is aimed to provide a more engaging multiplayer experience than previous titles; the game will provide support for asynchronous competitive multiplayer options, and tournament-style play. There will be shared leaderboards and multiplayer options among platforms, although PlayStation 4 players can only compete with users playing through Steam on Windows due to Sony's initial decision to prohibit cross-platform play between its PlayStation 4 and other consoles.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Pinball FX 3 to symulator pinballu gra wideo opracowana i opublikowana przez Zen Studios i wydana dla Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 we wrześniu 2017 roku, a następnie wydana dla Nintendo Switch w grudniu 2017 roku.

Pinball FX 3 pozwala graczom grać w jeden z kilku symulowanych stołów pinballowych i zawiera wsparcie tablicy wyników online dla nieformalnej rywalizacji z innymi graczami. Gra ma na celu zapewnienie bardziej wciągającego doświadczenia wieloosobowego niż poprzednie tytuły; gra zapewni wsparcie dla asynchronicznych opcji konkurencyjnego multiplayera, a także gry w stylu turniejowym. Będą wspólne tablice liderów i opcje multiplayer między platformami, chociaż gracze PlayStation 4 mogą konkurować tylko z użytkownikami grającymi przez Steam na Windows ze względu na początkową decyzję Sony o zakazie gry międzyplatformowej między PlayStation 4 i innymi konsolami.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Cамая масштабная игра в пинбол, которая придется по душе всем поклонникам этой классической аркады. Многопользовательские соревнования, пользовательские турниры и игры лиги — у вас будут безграничные возможности для игры в пинбол.

Pinball FX3 включает обширную библиотеку столов, оформленных в стиле самых известных брендов, включая Aliens™,Family Guy, TellTale's The Walking Dead, Portal® и т. д.

- Давно не играли в пинбол? Pinball FX3 включает новый режим для одного игрока, где вы сможете вдоволь потренироваться!
- Все столы получили обновленную графику и дополнительные эффекты.
- Все столы включают новые игровые режимы, новые бонусы, дополнительные предметы и многое другое!</text>
			<text lang="es">Pinball FX 3 es un videojuego simulador de pinball desarrollado y publicado por Zen Studios y lanzado para Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 en septiembre de 2017 y posteriormente lanzado para Nintendo Switch en diciembre de 2017.

Pinball FX 3 permite a los jugadores jugar en una de varias mesas de pinball simuladas, e incluye soporte de marcador en línea para la competencia informal con otros jugadores. El juego pretende ofrecer una experiencia multijugador más atractiva que los títulos anteriores; el juego ofrecerá soporte para opciones multijugador competitivas asíncronas, y juego de estilo torneo. Habrá tablas de clasificación compartidas y opciones multijugador entre plataformas, aunque los jugadores de PlayStation 4 solo podrán competir con usuarios que jueguen a través de Steam en Windows debido a la decisión inicial de Sony de prohibir el juego multiplataforma entre su PlayStation 4 y otras consolas.</text>
			<text lang="de">Pinball FX 3 ist ein von Zen Studios entwickeltes und veröffentlichtes Flipper-Simulator-Videospiel, das im September 2017 für Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 und im Dezember 2017 für die Nintendo Switch veröffentlicht wurde.

Pinball FX 3 ermöglicht es den Spielern, an einem von mehreren simulierten Flippertischen zu spielen, und beinhaltet eine Online-Scoreboard-Unterstützung für einen informellen Wettbewerb mit anderen Spielern. Das Spiel soll eine fesselndere Multiplayer-Erfahrung bieten als frühere Titel; das Spiel wird asynchrone kompetitive Multiplayer-Optionen und turnierähnliche Spiele unterstützen. Es wird gemeinsame Bestenlisten und Multiplayer-Optionen für verschiedene Plattformen geben. Allerdings können PlayStation 4-Spieler nur mit Nutzern konkurrieren, die über Steam auf Windows spielen, da Sony ursprünglich beschlossen hatte, das plattformübergreifende Spielen zwischen der PlayStation 4 und anderen Konsolen zu verbieten.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Pinball FX 3 est un jeu vidéo de simulation de flipper développé et édité par Zen Studios et sorti sur Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 en septembre 2017 puis sur Nintendo Switch en décembre 2017.

Pinball FX 3 permet aux joueurs de jouer à l'une des nombreuses tables de flipper simulées, et inclut un support de tableau de bord en ligne pour une compétition informelle avec d'autres joueurs. Le jeu vise à fournir une expérience multijoueur plus engageante que les titres précédents ; le jeu fournira un support pour les options multijoueurs compétitives asynchrones, et le jeu de style tournoi. Les tableaux de classement et les options multijoueurs seront partagés entre les plateformes, bien que les joueurs de la PlayStation 4 ne puissent rivaliser qu'avec les utilisateurs jouant via Steam sur Windows, en raison de la décision initiale de Sony d'interdire les jeux multiplateformes entre la PlayStation 4 et les autres consoles.</text>
			<text lang="it">Pinball FX 3 è un simulatore di flipper sviluppato e pubblicato da Zen Studios e pubblicato per Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 nel settembre 2017 e poi rilasciato per Nintendo Switch nel dicembre 2017.

Pinball FX 3 permette ai giocatori di giocare su uno dei diversi tavoli da flipper simulati e include il supporto del tabellone online per una competizione informale con altri giocatori. Il gioco mira a fornire un'esperienza multigiocatore più coinvolgente rispetto ai titoli precedenti; il gioco offre il supporto per le opzioni multigiocatore competitive asincrone e per il gioco in stile torneo. Le classifiche e le opzioni multigiocatore saranno condivise tra le varie piattaforme, anche se i giocatori di PlayStation 4 potranno competere solo con utenti che giocano tramite Steam su Windows, a causa della decisione iniziale di Sony di vietare il gioco multipiattaforma tra PlayStation 4 e altre console.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Pinball FX 3 é um simulador de pinball, um jogo eletrônico desenvolvido e publicado pela Zen Studios e lançado para Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 em setembro de 2017, e posteriormente lançado para Nintendo Switch em dezembro de 2017.

Pinball FX 3 permite que os jogadores joguem em uma das várias mesas de pinball simuladas e inclui suporte para classificação online para competição informal com outros jogadores. O jogo tem como objetivo fornecer uma experiência multijogador mais envolvente do que os títulos anteriores; o jogo fornecerá suporte para opções de multijogador competitivo assíncronas, bem como jogos no estilo torneio. Haverá tabelas de classificação compartilhadas e opções multijogador entre plataformas, embora os jogadores do PlayStation 4 só possam competir com usuários que jogam via Steam no Windows, devido à decisão inicial da Sony de proibir jogos entre plataformas entre PlayStation 4 e outros consoles.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
