<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysart" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/fpinball.png</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/4K/fpinball.png</path>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.395</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.455</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.405</pos>
			<maxSize>0.245</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.405" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/fpinball.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/fpinball.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.395</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.455</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.408</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.408" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2023</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Zen Studios</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Pinball M</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Get ready to tilt into terror. The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life.

Spine-chilling features:

- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free
- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage
- Thrilling competition
- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation

Press start and flip for your life!</text>
			<text lang="pl">Przygotuj się na grozę. Nowa, inspirowana horrorem platforma pinballowa dla nieustraszonych graczy. Udowodnij swoje umiejętności na najbardziej złowieszczych, krwawych i złych stołach, jakie kiedykolwiek powstały.

Mrożące krew w żyłach funkcje:

- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director's Cut - doświadcz horroru bez ograniczeń za darmo
- Biblioteka zupełnie nowych, nigdy wcześniej nie widzianych stołów pełnych strachu i rzezi
- Ekscytująca rywalizacja
- Najlepsza symulacja pinballa od Zen Studios

Naciśnij start i walcz o życie!</text>
			<text lang="ru">Приготовьтесь погрузиться в настоящий кошмар с новой пинбол-платформой в жанре ужасов. Проявите свое мастерство и бесстрашие на самых жутких, омерзительных и крутых столах в истории.

Леденящие кровь особенности:

- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut — неописуемый древний ужас, бесплатно и без ограничений.
- Библиотека с новейшими столами, на которых вас ждет море страха и беспощадная резня.
- Захватывающие соревнования.
- Лучшая симуляция пинбола от Zen Studios.

Нажмите на кнопку старта и переверните свою жизнь!</text>
			<text lang="es">Prepárate para el terror. La nueva plataforma de pinball inspirada en el terror para jugadores intrépidos. Demuestra tus habilidades en las mesas más siniestras, sangrientas y malvadas jamás creadas.

Características escalofriantes:

- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director's Cut: experimenta el horror sobrenatural sin restricciones y gratis.
- Una biblioteca de mesas nuevas, nunca vistas, llenas de miedo y carnicería.
- Emocionante competición
- La simulación de pinball definitiva de Zen Studios

Pulsa Start y ¡sálvese quien pueda!</text>
			<text lang="de">Mach dich bereit, in den Terror zu stürzen. Die neue, von Horror inspirierte Flipperplattform für furchtlose Spieler. Beweisen Sie Ihr Können auf den unheimlichsten, blutigsten und krassesten Tischen, die je zum Leben erweckt wurden.

Gruselige Features:

- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director's Cut - erlebe das eldritische Grauen uneingeschränkt und kostenlos
- Eine Bibliothek mit brandneuen, noch nie zuvor gesehenen Tischen voller Angst und Gemetzel
- Spannende Wettkämpfe
- Zen Studios' ultimative Flipper-Simulation

Drücken Sie auf Start und flippern Sie um Ihr Leben!</text>
			<text lang="fr">Préparez-vous à basculer dans la terreur. La nouvelle plateforme de flipper inspirée de l'horreur pour les joueurs intrépides. Démontrez vos talents sur les tables les plus sinistres, les plus sanglantes et les plus méchantes jamais créées.

Des caractéristiques qui font froid dans le dos :

- Wrath of the Elder Gods : Director's Cut - vivez l'horreur sans restriction et gratuitement.
- Une bibliothèque de tables inédites, pleines de peur et de carnage.
- Une compétition palpitante
- L'ultime simulation de flipper de Zen Studios

Appuyez sur le bouton "Start" et jouez pour sauver votre vie !</text>
			<text lang="it">Preparatevi a fare un salto nel terrore. La nuova piattaforma di flipper ispirata all'horror per giocatori impavidi. Dimostrate le vostre abilità sui tavoli più sinistri, cruenti e cattivi mai portati in vita.

Caratteristiche da brivido:

- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director's Cut - l'esperienza dell'orrore infernale è gratuita e senza limiti.
- Una libreria di tavoli inediti, mai visti prima, pieni di paura e carneficina
- Competizione avvincente
- La simulazione di flipper più avanzata di Zen Studios

Premete il pulsante di avvio e lanciatevi per la vostra vita!</text>
			<text lang="pt">Prepare-se para o terror. Uma nova plataforma de pinball inspirada em horror para jogadores destemidos. Prove suas habilidades nas mesas mais sinistras, sangrentas e perversas já criadas.

Recursos arrepiantes:

- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director's Cut - experimente o horror sem limites gratuitamente
- Biblioteca de mesas totalmente novas e nunca antes vistas, cheias de medo e massacre
- Competição emocionante
- A melhor simulação de pinball da Zen Studios

Pressione iniciar e lute pela sua vida!</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
