<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysart" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/fpinball.png</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/4K/fpinball.png</path>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.395</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.455</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.405</pos>
			<maxSize>0.245</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.405" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/fpinball.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/fpinball.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.395</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.455</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.408</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.408" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2010</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Zen Studios</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Pinball FX</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Pinball FX 2 is a pinball video game for Xbox 360, Xbox One, and Microsoft Windows (XP and higher) and is the sequel to Pinball FX. It was developed by Zen Studios and published by Microsoft Studios. It was released on October 27, 2010, via the Xbox Live Arcade service. The game includes several new features, such as local multiplayer and the ability to tweak table settings. Players can also import all of the tables from Pinball FX they had previously purchased. The Windows 8 version of Pinball FX 2 was released on the Windows Store on October 27, 2012, two years after the original XBLA release. The game was subsequently released for other Windows platforms via Steam on May 10, 2013. Pinball FX 2 was announced for Windows Phone in February 2012. A sequel, Pinball FX 3 was released in September 2017.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Pinball FX 2 to gra wideo w pinball na konsole Xbox 360, Xbox One i Microsoft Windows (XP i nowsze), będąca kontynuacją Pinball FX. Została opracowana przez Zen Studios i wydana przez Microsoft Studios. Gra została wydana 27 października 2010 roku za pośrednictwem usługi Xbox Live Arcade. Gra zawiera kilka nowych funkcji, takich jak lokalny tryb wieloosobowy i możliwość dostosowania ustawień stołu. Gracze mogą również importować wszystkie zakupione wcześniej stoły z Pinball FX. Wersja Pinball FX 2 dla systemu Windows 8 została wydana w sklepie Windows Store 27 października 2012 roku, dwa lata po oryginalnym wydaniu na XBLA. Gra została następnie wydana na inne platformy Windows za pośrednictwem Steam 10 maja 2013 roku. Pinball FX 2 został zapowiedziany na Windows Phone w lutym 2012 roku. Kontynuacja, Pinball FX 3, została wydana we wrześniu 2017 roku.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Pinball FX 2 - видеоигра в жанре пинбола для Xbox 360, Xbox One и Microsoft Windows (XP и выше), продолжение Pinball FX. Она была разработана Zen Studios и издана Microsoft Studios. Игра была выпущена 27 октября 2010 года в сервисе Xbox Live Arcade. Игра включает в себя несколько новых функций, таких как локальный мультиплеер и возможность изменять настройки стола. Игроки также могут импортировать все столы из Pinball FX, которые они ранее приобрели. Версия Pinball FX 2 для Windows 8 была выпущена в Windows Store 27 октября 2012 года, спустя два года после релиза в XBLA. Впоследствии игра была выпущена для других платформ Windows через Steam 10 мая 2013 года. Pinball FX 2 был анонсирован для Windows Phone в феврале 2012 года. Сиквел, Pinball FX 3, был выпущен в сентябре 2017 года.</text>
			<text lang="es">Pinball FX 2 es un videojuego de pinball para Xbox 360, Xbox One y Microsoft Windows (XP y superior) y es la secuela de Pinball FX. Fue desarrollado por Zen Studios y publicado por Microsoft Studios. Salió a la venta el 27 de octubre de 2010 a través del servicio Xbox Live Arcade. El juego incluye varias características nuevas, como multijugador local y la posibilidad de ajustar la configuración de las mesas. Los jugadores también pueden importar todas las mesas de Pinball FX que hayan comprado anteriormente. La versión para Windows 8 de Pinball FX 2 se lanzó en la Windows Store el 27 de octubre de 2012, dos años después del lanzamiento original en XBLA. El juego se lanzó posteriormente para otras plataformas Windows a través de Steam el 10 de mayo de 2013. Pinball FX 2 se anunció para Windows Phone en febrero de 2012. La secuela, Pinball FX 3, se lanzó en septiembre de 2017.</text>
			<text lang="de">Pinball FX 2 ist ein Flipper-Videospiel für Xbox 360, Xbox One und Microsoft Windows (XP und höher) und ist der Nachfolger von Pinball FX. Es wurde von Zen Studios entwickelt und von Microsoft Studios veröffentlicht. Es wurde am 27. Oktober 2010 über den Xbox Live Arcade-Dienst veröffentlicht. Das Spiel enthält mehrere neue Funktionen, wie z. B. den lokalen Mehrspielermodus und die Möglichkeit, die Tischeinstellungen zu verändern. Die Spieler können auch alle Tische aus Pinball FX importieren, die sie zuvor erworben haben. Die Windows 8-Version von Pinball FX 2 wurde am 27. Oktober 2012 im Windows Store veröffentlicht, zwei Jahre nach der ursprünglichen XBLA-Version. Das Spiel wurde anschließend am 10. Mai 2013 für andere Windows-Plattformen über Steam veröffentlicht. Pinball FX 2 wurde im Februar 2012 für Windows Phone angekündigt. Eine Fortsetzung, Pinball FX 3, wurde im September 2017 veröffentlicht.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Pinball FX 2 est un jeu vidéo de flipper pour Xbox 360, Xbox One et Microsoft Windows (XP et versions ultérieures) et constitue la suite de Pinball FX. Il a été développé par Zen Studios et édité par Microsoft Studios. Il est sorti le 27 octobre 2010 sur le service Xbox Live Arcade. Le jeu comprend plusieurs nouvelles fonctionnalités, telles que le multijoueur local et la possibilité d'ajuster les paramètres des tables. Les joueurs peuvent également importer toutes les tables de Pinball FX qu'ils ont achetées précédemment. La version Windows 8 de Pinball FX 2 est sortie sur le Windows Store le 27 octobre 2012, deux ans après la sortie originale sur XBLA. Le jeu est ensuite sorti sur d'autres plateformes Windows via Steam le 10 mai 2013. Pinball FX 2 a été annoncé pour Windows Phone en février 2012. Une suite, Pinball FX 3, est sortie en septembre 2017.</text>
			<text lang="it">Pinball FX 2 è un videogioco di flipper per Xbox 360, Xbox One e Microsoft Windows (XP e versioni successive) ed è il seguito di Pinball FX. È stato sviluppato da Zen Studios e pubblicato da Microsoft Studios. È stato pubblicato il 27 ottobre 2010 tramite il servizio Xbox Live Arcade. Il gioco include diverse nuove funzionalità, come il multiplayer locale e la possibilità di modificare le impostazioni dei tavoli. I giocatori possono anche importare tutti i tavoli di Pinball FX acquistati in precedenza. La versione per Windows 8 di Pinball FX 2 è stata pubblicata sul Windows Store il 27 ottobre 2012, due anni dopo la versione originale per XBLA. Il gioco è stato successivamente rilasciato per altre piattaforme Windows tramite Steam il 10 maggio 2013. Pinball FX 2 è stato annunciato per Windows Phone nel febbraio 2012. Un sequel, Pinball FX 3, è stato pubblicato nel settembre 2017.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
