<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.364</pos>
			<maxSize>0.33</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.364" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1998</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Plug &amp; Play TV Games</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>TV game (TV game for short) or plug and play game (plug-'n'-play game for short) is an interactive entertainment device designed for use on a television set that integrates the video game console with the game controller.

The term "TV game" can be used to refer to any number of self-contained, portable game systems operating on either batteries or an electronic power supply which plugs directly into a TV or VCR. The game software is built directly into the unit, which is typically designed to look like a toy or classic game console/controller with the addition of two AV ports. These systems usually contain either highly specialized games or activities, or a collection of classic games. Thus, it could be viewed as a video game console without interchangeable game software. As the game software is integrated into the game unit and almost never designed to be changed by the user, these game systems are typically sold by retailers as electronic toys or collectibles rather than game consoles.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Gra plug and play (w skrócie gra plug-'n'-play) to interaktywne urządzenie rozrywkowe przeznaczone do użytku na telewizorze, które integruje konsolę do gier wideo z kontrolerem gry.

Termin "gra telewizyjna" może być stosowany w odniesieniu do dowolnej liczby niezależnych, przenośnych systemów gier działających na baterie lub zasilanie elektroniczne, które podłącza się bezpośrednio do telewizora lub magnetowidu. Oprogramowanie gry jest wbudowane bezpośrednio w jednostkę, która jest zazwyczaj zaprojektowana tak, aby wyglądała jak zabawka lub klasyczna konsola/kontroler do gier z dodatkiem dwóch portów AV. Systemy te zazwyczaj zawierają albo wysoce wyspecjalizowane gry lub zajęcia, albo kolekcję klasycznych gier. Można je zatem postrzegać jako konsolę do gier wideo bez wymiennego oprogramowania do gier. Ponieważ oprogramowanie do gier jest zintegrowane z jednostką gry i prawie nigdy nie jest przeznaczone do zmiany przez użytkownika, te systemy gier są zazwyczaj sprzedawane przez sprzedawców detalicznych raczej jako elektroniczne zabawki lub przedmioty kolekcjonerskie niż jako konsole do gier.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Специальное устройство «все в одном», обычно работающее от батарей, которое подключается непосредственно к телевизору. Основным их производителем является Jakks Pacific, хотя они также производятся такими компаниями, как Radica, Tiger Electronics, Majesco и Techno Source.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il gioco televisivo (in breve TV game) o gioco plug and play (in breve plug-'n'-play game) è un dispositivo di intrattenimento interattivo progettato per essere utilizzato su un televisore che integra la console per videogiochi con il controller di gioco.

Il termine "gioco televisivo" può essere utilizzato per indicare un numero qualsiasi di sistemi di gioco portatili e autonomi che funzionano a batterie o con un alimentatore elettronico che si collega direttamente a un televisore o a un videoregistratore. Il software di gioco è incorporato direttamente nell'unità, che in genere è progettata per assomigliare a una console/controller giocattolo o a un gioco classico, con l'aggiunta di due porte AV. Questi sistemi di solito contengono giochi o attività altamente specializzate, oppure una collezione di giochi classici. Pertanto, possono essere considerati come una console per videogiochi senza software di gioco intercambiabile. Poiché il software di gioco è integrato nell'unità di gioco e non è quasi mai progettato per essere modificato dall'utente, questi sistemi di gioco sono in genere venduti dai rivenditori come giocattoli elettronici o oggetti da collezione piuttosto che come console di gioco.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
