<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.347</pos>
			<maxSize>0.36</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.4</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.347" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.347</pos>
			<maxSize>0.345</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.46</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.385</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.347" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2006</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sony</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>PlayStation 3</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The PlayStation 3 (PS3) is a home video game console developed by Sony Computer Entertainment. It is the successor to PlayStation 2, and is part of the PlayStation brand of consoles. It was first released on November 11, 2006 in Japan, November 17, 2006 in North America, and March 23, 2007 in Europe and Australia. The PlayStation 3 competed primarily against Microsoft's Xbox 360 and Nintendo's Wii as part of the seventh generation of video game consoles.

The console was first officially announced at E3 2005, and was released at the end of 2006. It was the first console to use Blu-ray Disc as its primary storage medium. The console was the first PlayStation to integrate social gaming services, including the PlayStation Network, as well as the first to be controllable from a handheld console, through its remote connectivity with PlayStation Portable and PlayStation Vita. In September 2009, the Slim model of the PlayStation 3 was released. It no longer provided the hardware ability to run PS2 games. It was lighter and thinner than the original version, and featured a redesigned logo and marketing design, as well as a minor start-up change in software. A Super Slim variation was then released in late 2012, further refining and redesigning the console.</text>
			<text lang="pl">PlayStation 3 (jap. プレイステーション3, Pureisutēshon Surī, skrót PS3; do września 2009 znak towarowy PLAYSTATION 3) – konsola gier wideo wyprodukowana przez Sony Computer Entertainment. 11 listopada 2006 roku miała miejsce premiera w Japonii, a 17 listopada w Ameryce Północnej. W Europie konsola pojawiła się 23 marca 2007 roku. Jest bezpośrednią konkurencją dla konsol siódmej generacji: Xboksa 360 przedsiębiorstwa Microsoft oraz Wii wyprodukowanej przez Nintendo.

Konsola została oficjalnie zapowiedziana przez Sony na targach Electronic Entertainment Expo w maju 2005 roku. PlayStation 3 stała się pierwszą konsolą na rynku, która wykorzystywała format Blu-ray jako podstawowy nośnik danych. Innymi ważnymi cechami konsoli jest darmowy dostęp do usług sieciowych takich jak PlayStation Network (umożliwiająca dostęp do PlayStation Store oraz PlayStation Plus) oraz możliwość połączenia jej z przenośnymi konsolami PlayStation Portable oraz PlayStation Vita.

PlayStation 3 doczekała się dwóch zasadniczych rewizji, zmieniających gruntownie wygląd zewnętrzny konsoli oraz zmniejszających koszty produkcji sprzętu, poprzez zastosowanie miniaturyzacji użytych w niej technologii. Pierwsza z nich, o nazwie „Slim”, została wydana we wrześniu 2009 roku – wraz z nią Sony zmieniło też logo konsoli, znak towarowy oraz ogólny wizerunek sprzętu. Premiera ostatniej wersji o nazwie „Super Slim” odbyła się jesienią 2012 roku. W obydwu przypadkach zmniejszeniu uległy gabaryty konsoli, jej waga, pobór prądu oraz rozmiary jej podzespołów.

Do lutego 2017 roku sprzedano ok. 86,8 milionów sztuk konsoli, natomiast liczba gier sprzedanych na tę platformę przekroczyła 947 milionów egzemplarzy.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка седьмого поколения, третья в семействе игровых систем PlayStation (не считая PlayStation Portable). С помощью PS3 можно играть, смотреть фильмы, слушать музыку, отправлять электронную почту и просматривать веб-страницы. С самого момента выпуска приставкой поддерживается большинство игр для консолей предыдущего поколения, PlayStation и PlayStation 2. Главными конкурентами консоли являются Xbox 360 от Microsoft и Wii от Nintendo.

Изначально выход PS3 планировался на 2005 год, но разработчики, которые имели доступ к версии приставки того времени, заявили, что решение ещё слишком сырое (например, в той версии совсем не было GPU, его добавили в самом конце подготовки к запуску). Выход PS3 в Японии состоялся 11 ноября 2006 года, 17 ноября приставка появилась в Северной Америке в первом квартале 2007 года), в марте 2007 года — в Европе, а потом в России.</text>
			<text lang="es">La PlayStation 3 (PS3) es una videoconsola doméstica desarrollada por Sony Computer Entertainment. Es la sucesora de la PlayStation 2 y forma parte de la marca de consolas PlayStation. Salió a la venta el 11 de noviembre de 2006 en Japón, el 17 de noviembre de 2006 en Norteamérica y el 23 de marzo de 2007 en Europa y Australia. La PlayStation 3 compitió principalmente con la Xbox 360 de Microsoft y la Wii de Nintendo como parte de la séptima generación de consolas de videojuegos.

La consola se anunció oficialmente por primera vez en el E3 de 2005 y salió a la venta a finales de 2006. Fue la primera consola en utilizar discos Blu-ray como medio de almacenamiento principal. La consola fue la primera PlayStation en integrar servicios de juegos sociales, incluyendo PlayStation Network, así como la primera en ser controlable desde una consola portátil, a través de su conectividad remota con PlayStation Portable y PlayStation Vita. En septiembre de 2009, salió a la venta el modelo Slim de la PlayStation 3. Ya no ofrecía la capacidad de ejecutar juegos de PS2. Era más ligera y delgada que la versión original, y presentaba un logotipo y un diseño de marketing rediseñados, así como un pequeño cambio de arranque en el software. A finales de 2012 se lanzó una variante Super Slim, que refinaba y rediseñaba aún más la consola.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die PlayStation 3 (PS3) ist eine von Sony Computer Entertainment entwickelte Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch. Sie ist der Nachfolger der PlayStation 2 und gehört zur Konsolenmarke PlayStation. Sie wurde erstmals am 11. November 2006 in Japan, am 17. November 2006 in Nordamerika und am 23. März 2007 in Europa und Australien veröffentlicht. Die PlayStation 3 konkurrierte vor allem mit der Xbox 360 von Microsoft und der Wii von Nintendo als Teil der siebten Generation von Videospielkonsolen.

Die Konsole wurde erstmals auf der E3 2005 offiziell angekündigt und kam Ende 2006 auf den Markt. Sie war die erste Konsole, die Blu-ray Disc als primäres Speichermedium verwendete. Sie war die erste PlayStation-Konsole, die Social-Gaming-Dienste wie das PlayStation Network integrierte, und die erste Konsole, die über eine Remote-Verbindung mit PlayStation Portable und PlayStation Vita von einem Handheld aus gesteuert werden konnte. Im September 2009 wurde das Slim-Modell der PlayStation 3 veröffentlicht. Es bot nicht mehr die Hardware-Fähigkeit, PS2-Spiele auszuführen. Es war leichter und dünner als die ursprüngliche Version und verfügte über ein neu gestaltetes Logo und Marketingdesign sowie eine geringfügige Änderung bei der Software. Ende 2012 wurde dann eine Super-Slim-Variante veröffentlicht, die die Konsole weiter verfeinerte und neu gestaltete.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La PlayStation 3 (PS3) est une console de jeux vidéo de salon développée par Sony Computer Entertainment. Elle succède à la PlayStation 2 et fait partie de la gamme de consoles PlayStation. Elle est sortie le 11 novembre 2006 au Japon, le 17 novembre 2006 en Amérique du Nord et le 23 mars 2007 en Europe et en Australie. La PlayStation 3 était principalement en concurrence avec la Xbox 360 de Microsoft et la Wii de Nintendo dans le cadre de la septième génération de consoles de jeux vidéo.

La console a été officiellement annoncée pour la première fois à l'E3 2005 et est sortie à la fin de l'année 2006. Elle a été la première console à utiliser le disque Blu-ray comme principal support de stockage. La console a été la première PlayStation à intégrer des services de jeux sociaux, notamment le PlayStation Network, et la première à être contrôlable à partir d'une console portable, grâce à sa connectivité à distance avec la PlayStation Portable et la PlayStation Vita. En septembre 2009, le modèle Slim de la PlayStation 3 est sorti. Il n'offre plus la possibilité matérielle de faire tourner les jeux PS2. Plus légère et plus fine que la version originale, elle arbore un logo et un design marketing redessinés, ainsi qu'un changement logiciel mineur au démarrage. Une version Super Slim a ensuite été lancée fin 2012, affinant et redessinant encore la console.</text>
			<text lang="it">La PlayStation 3 (PS3) è una console per videogiochi domestica sviluppata da Sony Computer Entertainment. È il successore della PlayStation 2 e fa parte del marchio di console PlayStation. È stata rilasciata per la prima volta l'11 novembre 2006 in Giappone, il 17 novembre 2006 in Nord America e il 23 marzo 2007 in Europa e Australia. La PlayStation 3 ha gareggiato principalmente contro la Xbox 360 di Microsoft e la Wii di Nintendo come parte della settima generazione di console per videogiochi.

La console è stata annunciata ufficialmente per la prima volta all'E3 2005 ed è stata rilasciata alla fine del 2006. È stata la prima console a utilizzare il Blu-ray Disc come supporto di memorizzazione principale. La console è stata la prima PlayStation a integrare servizi di social gaming, tra cui PlayStation Network, e la prima a poter essere controllata da una console portatile, grazie alla connettività remota con PlayStation Portable e PlayStation Vita. Nel settembre 2009, è stato rilasciato il modello Slim della PlayStation 3. Non offriva più la capacità hardware di eseguire i giochi PS2. Era più leggera e sottile della versione originale e presentava un logo e un design di marketing ridisegnati, oltre a una piccola modifica del software. Alla fine del 2012 è stata rilasciata una variante Super Slim, che ha ulteriormente perfezionato e ridisegnato la console.</text>
			<text lang="pt">PlayStation 3 (jap. プレイステーション3, Pureisutēshon Surī, abreviado PS3; a partir de setembro de 2009, a marca PLAYSTATION 3) – um console de videogame produzido pela Sony Computer Entertainment. Em 11 de novembro de 2006, ocorreu seu lançamento no Japão, e em 17 de novembro, na América do Norte. Na Europa, o console apareceu em 23 de março de 2007. É uma competição direta para consoles de sétima geração: Xbox 360 da Microsoft e Wii, produzido pela Nintendo.

O console foi oficialmente anunciado pela Sony na Electronic Entertainment Expo em maio de 2005. O PlayStation 3 tornou-se o primeiro console no mercado a usar o formato Blu-ray como mídia de dados principal. Outros recursos importantes do console incluem acesso gratuito a serviços online como PlayStation Network (permitindo acesso à PlayStation Store e PlayStation Plus) e a possibilidade de conectá-lo a consoles portáteis PlayStation Portable e PlayStation Vita.

O PlayStation 3 passou por duas revisões principais, mudando drasticamente a aparência externa do console e reduzindo os custos de produção de hardware, por meio da miniaturização das tecnologias usadas nele. A primeira delas, chamada de "Slim", foi lançada em setembro de 2009 - juntamente com ela, a Sony também mudou o logotipo do console, a marca registrada e a aparência geral do equipamento. O lançamento da última versão, chamada de "Super Slim", ocorreu no outono de 2012. Em ambos os casos, as dimensões do console, seu peso, consumo de energia e o tamanho de seus componentes foram reduzidos.

Até fevereiro de 2017, foram vendidas cerca de 86,8 milhões de unidades do console, enquanto o número de jogos vendidos para essa plataforma ultrapassou 947 milhões de cópias.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
