<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.503 0.452</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.223 0.452" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.503 0.452</pos>
			<maxSize>0.19</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.223 0.452" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2021</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Pyxel</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Pyxel is a retro game engine for Python. Thanks to its simple specifications inspired by retro gaming consoles, such as only 16 colors can be displayed and only 4 sounds can be played back at the same time, you can feel free to enjoy making pixel art style games.

Pyxel's specifications and APIs are inspired by PICO-8 and TIC-80.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Pyxel to silnik gier retro dla Pythona. Dzięki prostym specyfikacjom inspirowanym konsolami do gier retro, takim jak możliwość wyświetlania tylko 16 kolorów i odtwarzania tylko 4 dźwięków jednocześnie, możesz swobodnie cieszyć się tworzeniem gier w stylu pixel art.

Specyfikacje i API Pyxela są inspirowane przez PICO-8 i TIC-80.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Pyxel - это движок ретро-игр для Python. Благодаря простым спецификациям, вдохновленным ретро игровыми консолями, таким как отображение только 16 цветов и одновременное воспроизведение только 4 звуков, вы можете наслаждаться созданием игр в стиле пиксель-арт.

Спецификации и API Pyxel вдохновлены PICO-8 и TIC-80.</text>
			<text lang="es">Pyxel es un motor de juegos retro para Python. Gracias a sus sencillas especificaciones inspiradas en las consolas de juegos retro, como que sólo se pueden mostrar 16 colores y reproducir 4 sonidos al mismo tiempo, puedes sentirte libre para disfrutar haciendo juegos de estilo pixel art.

Las especificaciones y API de Pyxel están inspiradas en PICO-8 y TIC-80.</text>
			<text lang="de">Pyxel ist eine Retro-Spiel-Engine für Python. Dank seiner einfachen, von Retro-Spielkonsolen inspirierten Spezifikationen, wie z. B. dass nur 16 Farben angezeigt und nur 4 Töne gleichzeitig abgespielt werden können, können Sie sich frei fühlen, Spiele im Pixel-Art-Stil zu entwickeln.

Die Spezifikationen und APIs von Pyxel sind von PICO-8 und TIC-80 inspiriert.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Pyxel est un moteur de jeu rétro pour Python. Grâce à ses spécifications simples inspirées des consoles de jeux rétro, telles que 16 couleurs seulement peuvent être affichées et 4 sons seulement peuvent être joués en même temps, vous pouvez vous amuser à créer des jeux de style pixel art.

Les spécifications et les API de Pyxel sont inspirées du PICO-8 et du TIC-80.</text>
			<text lang="it">Pyxel è un motore di gioco retrò per Python. Grazie alle sue semplici specifiche ispirate alle console di gioco retrò, come ad esempio la possibilità di visualizzare solo 16 colori e di riprodurre solo 4 suoni contemporaneamente, ci si può divertire a creare giochi in stile pixel art.

Le specifiche e le API di Pyxel si ispirano a PICO-8 e TIC-80.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Pyxel é um motor de jogos retro para Python. Com especificações simples inspiradas em consoles de jogos retro, como a capacidade de exibir apenas 16 cores e tocar apenas 4 sons simultaneamente, você pode aproveitar ao máximo a criação de jogos em estilo pixel art.

As especificações e a API do Pyxel são inspiradas por PICO-8 e TIC-80.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
