<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<pos>0.529 0.461</pos>
			<maxSize>0.28</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.37</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.309</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.249 0.461" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise169.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<pos>0.529 0.4602</pos>
			<maxSize>0.275</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.368</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.307</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.249 0.4602" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2016</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Return to Castle Wolfenstein</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>RealRTCW</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>RealRTCW is a global mod for the classic Wolfenstein, based on the ioRTCW port, which provides support for widescreen resolutions and 64 bit systems. It includes a new graphical renderer, expanded arsenal, reimagined shooting mechanics, new high quality models, textures and sounds.

• Expanded arsenal including 12 new weapons
• New HD models for the original weapons
• HD textures for the environment and characters, preserving the style and atmosphere of the original.
• Support for weather effects - rain and snow
• New items for inventory - adrenaline and bandages
• Real recoil system
• Updated weapon characteristics
• Improved AI
• New high quality sounds
• New interface
• New difficulty level system
• Subtitle support
• Integration with Steam Workshop for custom maps and modifications
• Steam achievements support
• Restored content including a training level and unused soundtrack</text>
			<text lang="pl">RealRTCW to globalny mod do klasycznego Wolfensteina, oparty na porcie ioRTCW, który zapewnia obsługę rozdzielczości panoramicznych i systemów 64-bitowych. Zawiera nowy renderer graficzny, rozszerzony arsenał, przeprojektowaną mechanikę strzelania, nowe wysokiej jakości modele, tekstury i dźwięki.

• Rozszerzony arsenał, w tym 12 nowych broni
• Nowe modele HD dla oryginalnych broni
• Tekstury HD dla otoczenia i postaci, zachowujące styl i atmosferę oryginału.
• Wsparcie dla efektów pogodowych - deszczu i śniegu
• Nowe przedmioty do ekwipunku - adrenalina i bandaże
• Prawdziwy system odrzutu
• Zaktualizowana charakterystyka broni
• Ulepszona sztuczna inteligencja
• Nowe dźwięki wysokiej jakości
• Nowy interfejs
• Nowy system poziomów trudności
• Obsługa napisów
• Integracja z Warsztatem Steam dla niestandardowych map i modyfikacji
• Obsługa osiągnięć Steam
• Przywrócona zawartość, w tym poziom treningowy i niewykorzystana ścieżka dźwiękowa</text>
			<text lang="ru">RealRTCW - глобальный мод для классического Wolfenstein, основан на порте ioRTCW, который обеспечивает поддержку широкоформатных разрешений и 64 битных систем. Он включает в себя новый графический рендер, расширенный арсенал, переосмысленную механику стрельбы, новые высококачественные модели, текстуры и звуки.

• Расширенный арсенал, включающий в себя 12 новых оружий
• Новые HD модели для оригинального оружия
• HD текстуры для окружения и персонажей, сохраняющие стиль и атмосферу оригинала
• Поддержка погодных эффектов - дождь и снег
• Новые предметы для инвентаря - адреналин и бинты
• Система реальной отдачи
• Обновлённые характеристики оружия
• Улучшенный ИИ
• Новые звуки высокого качества
• Новый интерфейс
• Новая система уровней сложности
• Поддержка субтитров
• Интеграция с Steam Workshop для пользовательских карт и модификаций
• Поддержка достижений Steam
• Восстановленный контент включающий в себя тренировочный уровень и неиспользованный саундтрек</text>
			<text lang="es">RealRTCW es un mod global para el clásico Wolfenstein, basado en el port ioRTCW, que proporciona soporte para resoluciones panorámicas y sistemas de 64 bits. Incluye un nuevo renderizador gráfico, arsenal ampliado, mecánica de disparo reimaginada, nuevos modelos de alta calidad, texturas y sonidos.

• Arsenal ampliado con 12 nuevas armas
• Nuevos modelos HD para las armas originales
• Texturas HD para el entorno y los personajes, conservando el estilo y la atmósfera del original.
• Soporte para efectos meteorológicos - lluvia y nieve
• Nuevos objetos para el inventario: adrenalina y vendas.
• Sistema de retroceso real
• Características actualizadas de las armas
• IA mejorada
• Nuevos sonidos de alta calidad
• Nueva interfaz
• Nuevo sistema de niveles de dificultad
• Soporte para subtítulos
• Integración con Steam Workshop para mapas personalizados y modificaciones
• Compatibilidad con logros de Steam
• Contenido restaurado que incluye un nivel de entrenamiento y una banda sonora sin usar</text>
			<text lang="de">RealRTCW ist ein globaler Mod für den Klassiker Wolfenstein, der auf der ioRTCW-Portierung basiert, die Unterstützung für Breitbildauflösungen und 64-Bit-Systeme bietet. Sie enthält einen neuen grafischen Renderer, ein erweitertes Arsenal, eine überarbeitete Schießmechanik, neue hochwertige Modelle, Texturen und Sounds.

• Erweitertes Arsenal mit 12 neuen Waffen
• Neue HD-Modelle für die Originalwaffen
• HD-Texturen für die Umgebung und die Charaktere, die den Stil und die Atmosphäre des Originals beibehalten.
• Unterstützung für Wettereffekte - Regen und Schnee
• Neue Gegenstände für das Inventar - Adrenalin und Bandagen
• Echtes Rückstoßsystem
• Aktualisierte Waffeneigenschaften
• Verbesserte KI
• Neue, hochwertige Sounds
• Neue Benutzeroberfläche
• Neues Schwierigkeitsgradsystem
• Unterstützung von Untertiteln
• Integration mit Steam Workshop für eigene Karten und Modifikationen
• Unterstützung von Steam-Erfolgen
• Wiederhergestellte Inhalte einschließlich eines Trainingslevels und eines nicht verwendeten Soundtracks</text>
			<text lang="fr">RealRTCW est un mod global pour Wolfenstein classique, basé sur le portage ioRTCW, qui prend en charge les résolutions grand écran et les systèmes 64 bits. Il comprend un nouveau moteur de rendu graphique, un arsenal étendu, des mécanismes de tir réimaginés, de nouveaux modèles, textures et sons de haute qualité.

• Arsenal étendu comprenant 12 nouvelles armes
• Nouveaux modèles HD pour les armes originales
• Textures HD pour l'environnement et les personnages, préservant le style et l'atmosphère de l'original.
• Prise en charge des effets météorologiques - pluie et neige
• Nouveaux objets pour l'inventaire - adrénaline et bandages
• Système de recul réel
• Caractéristiques des armes mises à jour
• Amélioration de l'IA
• Nouveaux sons de haute qualité
• Nouvelle interface
• Nouveau système de niveau de difficulté
• Prise en charge des sous-titres
• Intégration avec Steam Workshop pour les cartes personnalisées et les modifications
• Prise en charge des succès Steam
• Contenu restauré comprenant un niveau d'entraînement et une bande-son inutilisée</text>
			<text lang="it">RealRTCW è un mod globale per il classico Wolfenstein, basato sul port ioRTCW, che fornisce il supporto per le risoluzioni widescreen e i sistemi a 64 bit. Include un nuovo renderer grafico, un arsenale ampliato, una meccanica di tiro ripensata, nuovi modelli, texture e suoni di alta qualità.

• Arsenale ampliato con 12 nuove armi
• Nuovi modelli HD per le armi originali
• Texture HD per l'ambiente e i personaggi, che conservano lo stile e l'atmosfera dell'originale.
• Supporto per gli effetti meteorologici - pioggia e neve
• Nuovi oggetti per l'inventario: adrenalina e bende.
• Sistema di rinculo reale
• Caratteristiche delle armi aggiornate
• IA migliorata
• Nuovi suoni di alta qualità
• Nuova interfaccia
• Nuovo sistema di livelli di difficoltà
• Supporto per i sottotitoli
• Integrazione con Steam Workshop per mappe e modifiche personalizzate
• Supporto per gli obiettivi di Steam
• Contenuti ripristinati, tra cui un livello di allenamento e una colonna sonora inutilizzata</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
