<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.52 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.7 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.62 0.5</pos>
			<maxSize>0.26</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.34 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text/>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Collection</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Recordings</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Here you can find the video files generated by emulators when you use the screen recording feature to capture your gameplay. All your recorded gameplay footage is securely stored and easily accessible, allowing you to review, edit, or share your videos whenever you like.</text>
			<text lang="it">Qui si trovano i file video generati dagli emulatori quando si utilizza la funzione di registrazione dello schermo per catturare il gioco. Tutti i filmati di gioco registrati sono archiviati in modo sicuro e facilmente accessibili, consentendo di rivedere, modificare o condividere i video quando si vuole.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Vous trouverez ici les fichiers vidéo générés par les émulateurs lorsque vous utilisez la fonction d'enregistrement d'écran pour capturer votre jeu. Toutes les séquences de jeu enregistrées sont stockées en toute sécurité et facilement accessibles, ce qui vous permet de les revoir, de les modifier ou de les partager quand vous le souhaitez.</text>
			<text lang="de">Hier finden Sie die Videodateien, die von Emulatoren generiert werden, wenn Sie die Bildschirmaufzeichnungsfunktion verwenden, um Ihren Spielverlauf aufzuzeichnen. Das gesamte aufgezeichnete Spielmaterial wird sicher gespeichert und ist leicht zugänglich, so dass Sie Ihre Videos jederzeit überprüfen, bearbeiten oder teilen können.</text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí puedes encontrar los archivos de vídeo generados por los emuladores cuando utilizas la función de grabación de pantalla para capturar tu juego. Todas las secuencias de juego grabadas se almacenan de forma segura y son fácilmente accesibles, lo que te permite revisar, editar o compartir tus vídeos siempre que quieras.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Здесь вы найдете видеофайлы, созданные эмуляторами, когда вы используете функцию записи экрана для съемки игрового процесса. Все записанные видеоролики надежно хранятся и легко доступны, что позволяет просматривать, редактировать или делиться ими в любое удобное время.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Tutaj można znaleźć pliki wideo wygenerowane przez emulatory podczas korzystania z funkcji nagrywania ekranu w celu przechwycenia rozgrywki. Wszystkie nagrania z rozgrywki są bezpiecznie przechowywane i łatwo dostępne, umożliwiając przeglądanie, edytowanie lub udostępnianie filmów w dowolnym momencie.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>