<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<theme defaultView="Icons">
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2020</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Gregory Montoir, Stuart Carnie</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>REminiscence</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>REminiscence is a game engine recreation of the 1992/1993 action adventure game Flashback made by Delphine Software.

It is the spiritual successor of Another World/Out Of This World and it distinguishes itself with rotoscoped graphics, polygonal cutscenes, and a Prince of Persia-style gameplay system.</text>
			<text lang="it">REminiscence è una ricreazione con motore di gioco del gioco d'azione e avventura Flashback del 1992/1993, realizzato da Delphine Software.

È il successore spirituale di Another World/Out Of This World e si distingue per la grafica rotoscopica, le scene d'intermezzo poligonali e un sistema di gioco in stile Prince of Persia.</text>
			<text lang="fr">REminiscence est une recréation par moteur de jeu du jeu d'action et d'aventure Flashback (1992/1993) réalisé par Delphine Software.

C'est le successeur spirituel de Another World/Out Of This World et il se distingue par des graphismes rotoscopés, des cutscenes polygonales et un système de jeu à la Prince of Persia.</text>
			<text lang="de">REminiscence ist eine Nachbildung des Action-Adventures Flashback aus dem Jahr 1992/1993 von Delphine Software.

Es ist der geistige Nachfolger von Another World/Out Of This World und zeichnet sich durch rotoskopierte Grafiken, polygonale Zwischensequenzen und ein Prince of Persia-ähnliches Gameplay-System aus.</text>
			<text lang="es">REminiscence es una recreación con motor de juego del juego de acción y aventura Flashback de 1992/1993 realizado por Delphine Software.

Es el sucesor espiritual de Another World/Out Of This World y se distingue por sus gráficos rotoscopiados, escenas poligonales y un sistema de juego al estilo Prince of Persia.</text>
			<text lang="ru">REminiscence - это воссоздание на игровом движке приключенческой игры Flashback 1992/1993 годов, созданной компанией Delphine Software.

Она является духовным наследником Another World/Out Of This World и отличается ротоскопированной графикой, полигональными сценами и геймплеем в стиле Prince of Persia.</text>
			<text lang="pl">REminiscence to odtworzenie na silniku gry przygodowej gry akcji Flashback z lat 1992/1993, stworzonej przez Delphine Software.
				
Jest to duchowy następca Another World/Out Of This World i wyróżnia się rotoskopową grafiką, wielokątnymi przerywnikami filmowymi i systemem rozgrywki w stylu Prince of Persia.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>