<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.52 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.54 0.45</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.234 0.43" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.38</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.52 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.54 0.45</pos>
			<maxSize>0.202</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.26 0.45" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2019</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Fabian Greffrath</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Taradino</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Taradino port is an SDL2-based port of the classic game Rise of the Triad (ROTT), a classic first-person shooter originally developed by Apogee Software in 1995.

Utilizing SDL2 and SDL_mixer, it replicates the original game's functionality while addressing compatibility with contemporary hardware.</text>
			<text lang="pt">A porta Taradino é uma porta baseada em SDL2 do jogo clássico Rise of the Triad (ROTT), um clássico jogo de tiro em primeira pessoa originalmente desenvolvido pela Apogee Software em 1995.

Utilizando o SDL2 e o SDL_mixer, ele replica a funcionalidade do jogo original, ao mesmo tempo em que aborda a compatibilidade com o hardware contemporâneo.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il port di Taradino è un port basato su SDL2 del gioco classico Rise of the Triad (ROTT), un classico sparatutto in prima persona originariamente sviluppato da Apogee Software nel 1995.

Utilizzando SDL2 e SDL_mixer, replica le funzionalità del gioco originale e allo stesso tempo la compatibilità con l'hardware contemporaneo.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le portage Taradino est un portage basé sur SDL2 du jeu classique Rise of the Triad (ROTT), un jeu de tir à la première personne développé à l'origine par Apogee Software en 1995.

Utilisant SDL2 et SDL_mixer, il reproduit les fonctionnalités du jeu original tout en assurant la compatibilité avec le matériel contemporain.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Taradino-Portierung ist eine SDL2-basierte Portierung des Spieleklassikers Rise of the Triad (ROTT), einem klassischen Ego-Shooter, der ursprünglich 1995 von Apogee Software entwickelt wurde.

Durch die Verwendung von SDL2 und SDL_mixer wird die Funktionalität des Originalspiels nachgebildet, während gleichzeitig die Kompatibilität mit moderner Hardware berücksichtigt wird.</text>
			<text lang="es">El port de Taradino es un port basado en SDL2 del clásico juego Rise of the Triad (ROTT), un shooter clásico en primera persona desarrollado originalmente por Apogee Software en 1995.

Utilizando SDL2 y SDL_mixer, reproduce la funcionalidad del juego original al tiempo que aborda la compatibilidad con el hardware contemporáneo.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Порт Taradino - это основанный на SDL2 порт классической игры Rise of the Triad (ROTT), классического шутера от первого лица, первоначально разработанного компанией Apogee Software в 1995 году.

Используя SDL2 и SDL_mixer, он повторяет функциональность оригинальной игры, обеспечивая совместимость с современным оборудованием.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Port Taradino jest opartym na SDL2 portem klasycznej gry Rise of the Triad (ROTT), klasycznej strzelanki pierwszoosobowej pierwotnie opracowanej przez Apogee Software w 1995 roku.

Wykorzystując SDL2 i SDL_mixer, odtwarza funkcjonalność oryginalnej gry, jednocześnie zapewniając kompatybilność ze współczesnym sprzętem.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
