<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.43</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.358</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.358" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.43</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.358</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.358" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1983</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Bandai</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>RX-78</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Bandai RX-78 is a Japanese 8-bit microcomputer manufactured by Bandai. Its name comes from the RX-78-2 Gundam. It was released in July 1983, and employed a SHARP LH0080A (Zilog Z80A clone) CPU. It ran at a clock speed of 4.1 MHz, and shipped with 30 KB of RAM and 8KB of ROM. It had two joystick ports in a proprietary format using 8-pin DIN connectors.

The computer can generate 27 colors, created from 3 levels of intensity of each RGB channel, arranged into VRAM video planes, with a maximum resolution of 192×184 pixels, and is capable of displaying 30 x 23 text characters using a 6x8 pixel font. Sound was generated by the Texas Instruments SN76489 chip, providing 3 voices in four octaves and noise generator. Software was available on cartridges or cassettes.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Bandai RX-78 to japoński 8-bitowy mikrokomputer produkowany przez firmę Bandai. Jego nazwa pochodzi od Gundama RX-78-2. Został wydany w lipcu 1983 roku i wykorzystywał procesor SHARP LH0080A (klon Zilog Z80A). Działał z częstotliwością taktowania 4,1 MHz i był wyposażony w 30 KB pamięci RAM i 8 KB pamięci ROM. Posiadał dwa porty joysticka w zastrzeżonym formacie wykorzystującym 8-pinowe złącza DIN.

Komputer może wygenerować 27 kolorów, utworzonych z 3 poziomów intensywności każdego kanału RGB, ułożonych w płaszczyznach wideo VRAM, z maksymalną rozdzielczością 192×184 pikseli i jest w stanie wyświetlić 30 x 23 znaków tekstowych przy użyciu czcionki 6x8 pikseli. Dźwięk był generowany przez układ Texas Instruments SN76489, zapewniający 3 głosy w czterech oktawach i generator szumów. Oprogramowanie było dostępne na kartridżach lub kasetach.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Bandai RX-78 - японский 8-разрядный микрокомпьютер, выпускаемый компанией Bandai. Свое название он получил от модели RX-78-2 Gundam. Он был выпущен в июле 1983 года, в нем использовался процессор SHARP LH0080A (клон Zilog Z80A). Он работал на тактовой частоте 4,1 МГц и поставлялся с 30 КБ ОЗУ и 8 КБ ПЗУ. Компьютер имел два порта для подключения джойстиков, выполненных в фирменном формате с использованием 8-контактных разъемов DIN.

Компьютер способен генерировать 27 цветов, создаваемых из 3 уровней интенсивности каждого канала RGB, организованных в видеоплоскости VRAM, с максимальным разрешением 192×184 пикселя, и способен отображать 30×23 текстовых символов, используя шрифт 6х8 пикселей. Звук генерировался микросхемой Texas Instruments SN76489, обеспечивающей 3 голоса в четырех октавах и генератор шума. Программное обеспечение поставлялось на картриджах или кассетах.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Bandai RX-78 ist ein japanischer 8-Bit-Mikrocomputer, der von Bandai hergestellt wird. Sein Name stammt von dem RX-78-2 Gundam. Er wurde im Juli 1983 auf den Markt gebracht und verwendete eine SHARP LH0080A (Zilog Z80A Klon) CPU. Er lief mit einer Taktrate von 4,1 MHz und wurde mit 30 KB RAM und 8KB ROM ausgeliefert. Er hatte zwei Joystick-Anschlüsse in einem proprietären Format mit 8-poligen DIN-Steckern.

Der Computer kann 27 Farben erzeugen, die sich aus 3 Intensitätsstufen jedes RGB-Kanals zusammensetzen, die in VRAM-Videoebenen angeordnet sind, mit einer maximalen Auflösung von 192×184 Pixeln, und ist in der Lage, 30 x 23 Textzeichen mit einer 6x8-Pixel-Schriftart darzustellen. Der Ton wurde vom Texas Instruments SN76489 Chip erzeugt, der 3 Stimmen in vier Oktaven und einen Rauschgenerator bietet. Die Software war auf Cartridges oder Kassetten erhältlich.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Bandai RX-78 est un micro-ordinateur japonais 8 bits fabriqué par Bandai. Son nom provient du Gundam RX-78-2. Il est sorti en juillet 1983 et utilisait un processeur SHARP LH0080A (clone de Zilog Z80A). Il tournait à une vitesse d'horloge de 4,1 MHz et était livré avec 30 Ko de RAM et 8 Ko de ROM. Il disposait de deux ports pour joysticks dans un format propriétaire utilisant des connecteurs DIN à 8 broches.

L'ordinateur peut générer 27 couleurs, créées à partir de 3 niveaux d'intensité de chaque canal RVB, organisées en plans vidéo VRAM, avec une résolution maximale de 192×184 pixels, et est capable d'afficher 30 x 23 caractères de texte en utilisant une police de 6x8 pixels. Le son était généré par la puce Texas Instruments SN76489, fournissant 3 voix sur 4 octaves et un générateur de bruit. Le logiciel était disponible sur cartouches ou cassettes.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Bandai RX-78 è un microcomputer giapponese a 8 bit prodotto da Bandai. Il suo nome deriva dall'RX-78-2 Gundam. Fu rilasciato nel luglio 1983 e utilizzava una CPU SHARP LH0080A (clone dello Zilog Z80A). Funzionava a una velocità di clock di 4,1 MHz e veniva fornito con 30 KB di RAM e 8 KB di ROM. Disponeva di due porte joystick in formato proprietario con connettori DIN a 8 pin.

Il computer è in grado di generare 27 colori, creati da 3 livelli di intensità di ciascun canale RGB, disposti in piani video VRAM, con una risoluzione massima di 192×184 pixel, ed è in grado di visualizzare 30 x 23 caratteri di testo utilizzando un font da 6x8 pixel. Il suono era generato dal chip Texas Instruments SN76489, che forniva 3 voci in quattro ottave e un generatore di rumore. Il software era disponibile su cartucce o cassette.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
