<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.516 0.308</pos>
			<maxSize>0.26</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.236 0.308" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>2001</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>ScummVM</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>Script Creation Utility for Maniac Mansion Virtual Machine (ScummVM) is a set of game engine recreations. Originally designed to play LucasArts adventure games that use the SCUMM system, it also supports a variety of non-SCUMM games by companies like Revolution Software and Adventure Soft. It was originally written by Ludvig Strigeus. Released under the terms of the GNU General Public License, ScummVM is free software.

ScummVM is a re-implementation of the part of the software used to interpret the scripting languages such games used to describe the game world rather than emulating the hardware the games ran on; as such, ScummVM allows the games it supports to be played on platforms other than those for which they were originally released.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">ScummVM est une machine virtuelle qui permet de jouer aux jeux qui utilisent le système SCUMM (comme les jeux d'aventure de LucasArts ou d'Humongous) sur des plates-formes autres que celles originellement supportées par le jeu ; de plus, le logiciel supporte les jeux non-SCUMM suivants : Simon the Sorcerer I et II, Beneath a Steel Sky, The Legend of Kyrandia, Flight of the Amazon Queen et Broken Sword 1 et 2. L'un des buts du programme étant de permettre l'accessibilité à divers utilisateurs utilisant divers systèmes de jouer à ces classiques, diverses versions de ScummVM prenant en charge des systèmes d'exploitation variés sont disponibles : Microsoft Windows, Atari, WinCE, Pocket PC, Mac OS X, Linux, Android, Palm OS, HP webOS, Open webOS, AmigaOS BeOS, Solaris, Dreamcast, MorphOS, Irix, PSP, PS2, GP32, Wii, DS et plus. ScummVM est un logiciel libre, selon les termes de la licence GNU GPL.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Собрание созданных заново (независимо от разработчиков оригиналов) игровых движков, изначально разработанное для запуска игр фирмы LucasArts, использующие систему SCUMM (VM в названии обозначает виртуальная машина, англ. virtual machine). Благодаря продуманной архитектуре ScummVM также поддерживает множество не-SCUMM-игр таких компаний, как Revolution Software и Adventure Soft, для которых разработаны собственные интерфейсы взаимодействия с ресурсами (так называемые движки, англ. engines).

Портируемость кода является одной из основных целей проекта. ScummVM поддерживает в общей сложности около 200 игр, в число которых входят классические квесты на базе SCUMM издателей LucasArts Entertainment и Humongous Entertainment, ранние квесты на базе AGI Sierra Entertainment, квесты различных разработчиков. После слияния кодовой базы проекта FreeSCI в 2009 году ScummVM, начиная с версии 1.2.0, стала поддерживать игры на базе SCI.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>