<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.237</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.208 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<maxSize>0.227</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.208 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1984</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Epoch</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Super Cassette Vision</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Super Cassette Vision (Japanese: スーパーカセットビジョン, Hepburn: Suupaa Kasetto Bijon) is a home video game console made by Epoch Co. and released in Japan on July 17, 1984, and in Europe, specifically France, later in 1984. A successor to the Cassette Vision, it competed with Nintendo's Family Computer and Sega's SG-1000 line in Japan.

The Super Cassette Vision was released in 1984, featuring an 8-bit processor and better performance more in line with its competitors. It was later released in France by ITMC under the Yeno branding. At least 16 games were brought over from Japan for a European release. A version of the system targeted the young female market, the Super Lady Cassette Vision. The console came packed in a pink carrying case, alongside the game Milky Princess.

The system did not take off, and was unable to match the massive popularity of the Nintendo Famicom, leading Epoch to drop out of the console market by 1987.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Super Cassette Vision (japoński: スーパーカセットビジョン, Hepburn: Suupaa Kasetto Bijon) to domowa konsola gier wideo wyprodukowana przez Epoch Co. i wydana w Japonii 17 lipca 1984 roku, a w Europie, a konkretnie we Francji, później w 1984 roku. Następca Cassette Vision, konkurował z Nintendo's Family Computer i Sega's SG-1000 linii w Japonii.

Oryginalna Cassette Vision firmy Epoch została wprowadzona na rynek japoński przez firmę Epoch w 1981 roku, która cieszyła się stałą sprzedażą i przejęła 70% japońskiego rynku konsol domowych w tym czasie, z około 400 000 sprzedanych egzemplarzy. Jednak wprowadzenie systemów nowej generacji od Nintendo, Casio i Sega szybko wyparło oryginalną Cassette Vision, co skłoniło firmę Epoch do szybkiego opracowania następcy. Super Cassette Vision ukazała się w 1984 roku, wyposażona w 8-bitowy procesor i lepszą wydajność, bardziej zbliżoną do konkurencji. Został on później wydany we Francji przez ITMC pod marką Yeno. Co najmniej 16 gier zostało przywiezionych z Japonii na europejską premierę. Wersja systemu przeznaczona dla młodego rynku kobiecego, Super Lady Cassette Vision. Konsola była zapakowana w różową walizkę, wraz z grą Milky Princess. System nie przyjął się i nie był w stanie dorównać ogromnej popularności Nintendo Famicom, co doprowadziło do wycofania się firmy Epoch z rynku konsol w 1987 roku.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Домашняя игровая консоль, разработанная Epoch Co. и выпущенная в Японии 17 июля 1984, а затем в Европе (особенно во Франции) в 1984. Является преемником Cassette Vision, и одно время пытался конкурировать с Nintendo Family Computer а также с Sega SG-1000 в Японии.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Super Cassette Vision (en japonés: スーパーカセットビジョン, Hepburn: Suupaa Kasetto Bijon) es una videoconsola doméstica fabricada por Epoch Co. y lanzada en Japón el 17 de julio de 1984, y en Europa, concretamente en Francia, más tarde en 1984. Sucesora de la Cassette Vision, compitió en Japón con la Family Computer de Nintendo y la línea SG-1000 de Sega.

El Super Cassette Vision salió a la venta en 1984, con un procesador de 8 bits y unas prestaciones más acordes con las de sus competidores. Posteriormente, ITMC lo lanzó en Francia con la marca Yeno. Al menos 16 juegos se trajeron de Japón para su lanzamiento en Europa. Hubo una versión de la consola dirigida al mercado femenino, la Super Lady Cassette Vision. La consola venía embalada en un estuche rosa, junto con el juego Milky Princess.

La consola no despegó y fue incapaz de igualar la enorme popularidad de la Nintendo Famicom, lo que llevó a Epoch a abandonar el mercado de las consolas en 1987.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Super Cassette Vision (japanisch: スーパーカセットビジョン, Hepburn: Suupaa Kasetto Bijon) ist eine Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch, die von Epoch Co. hergestellt und am 17. Juli 1984 in Japan und später im Jahr 1984 in Europa, insbesondere in Frankreich, veröffentlicht wurde. Als Nachfolgerin der Cassette Vision konkurrierte sie in Japan mit Nintendos Family Computer und Segas SG-1000-Reihe.

Die Super Cassette Vision kam 1984 auf den Markt und verfügte über einen 8-Bit-Prozessor und eine bessere Leistung, die derjenigen der Konkurrenz entsprach. Sie wurde später in Frankreich von ITMC unter dem Markennamen Yeno herausgebracht. Mindestens 16 Spiele wurden für eine europäische Veröffentlichung aus Japan mitgebracht. Eine Version des Systems, die Super Lady Cassette Vision, richtete sich an den jungen weiblichen Markt. Die Konsole wurde in einer rosa Tragetasche zusammen mit dem Spiel Milky Princess ausgeliefert.

Das System konnte sich nicht durchsetzen und war nicht in der Lage, mit der großen Popularität des Nintendo Famicom mitzuhalten, was Epoch dazu veranlasste, sich 1987 aus dem Konsolenmarkt zurückzuziehen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Super Cassette Vision (japonaise : スーパーカセットビジョン, Hepburn : Suupaa Kasetto Bijon) est une console de jeu vidéo de salon fabriquée par Epoch Co. et commercialisée au Japon le 17 juillet 1984, et en Europe, plus précisément en France, plus tard en 1984. Succédant à la Cassette Vision, elle était en concurrence avec le Family Computer de Nintendo et la gamme SG-1000 de Sega au Japon.

Le Super Cassette Vision est sorti en 1984, avec un processeur 8 bits et des performances plus proches de celles de ses concurrents. Elle a ensuite été commercialisée en France par ITMC sous la marque Yeno. Au moins 16 jeux ont été importés du Japon pour une sortie européenne. Une version de la console destinée au marché des jeunes femmes, la Super Lady Cassette Vision, a été commercialisée. La console était livrée dans une mallette de transport rose, avec le jeu Milky Princess.

La console n'a pas décollé et n'a pas pu rivaliser avec la popularité massive de la Nintendo Famicom, ce qui a conduit Epoch à abandonner le marché des consoles en 1987.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Super Cassette Vision (giapponese: スーパーカセットビジョン, Hepburn: Suupaa Kasetto Bijon) è una console per videogiochi domestica prodotta da Epoch Co. e rilasciata in Giappone il 17 luglio 1984 e in Europa, in particolare in Francia, più tardi nel 1984. Successore del Cassette Vision, in Giappone era in concorrenza con il Family Computer di Nintendo e la linea SG-1000 di Sega.

Il Super Cassette Vision fu rilasciato nel 1984, con un processore a 8 bit e prestazioni migliori, più in linea con i suoi concorrenti. In seguito fu distribuito in Francia da ITMC con il marchio Yeno. Almeno 16 giochi furono portati dal Giappone per l'uscita europea. Una versione del sistema era destinata al mercato femminile, la Super Lady Cassette Vision. La console era confezionata in una custodia rosa, insieme al gioco Milky Princess.

La console non decollò e non fu in grado di eguagliare l'enorme popolarità del Nintendo Famicom, portando Epoch ad abbandonare il mercato delle console nel 1987.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
