<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.34</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.375</pos>
			<maxSize>0.255</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.375" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.34</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.375</pos>
			<maxSize>0.245</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.375" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1991</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Sega</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Sega CD</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Sega CD, released as the Mega-CD in most regions outside North America and Brazil, is a CD-ROM accessory for the Mega Drive/Genesis designed and produced by Sega as part of the fourth generation of video game consoles. It was released on December 12, 1991 in Japan, October 15, 1992 in North America, and April 2, 1993 in Europe. The Sega CD plays CD-based games and adds hardware functionality such as a faster central processing unit and graphic enhancements like sprite scaling and rotation. It can also play audio CDs and CD+G discs.

The main benefit of CD technology was greater storage, which allowed for games to be nearly 320 times larger than Genesis cartridges. This benefit manifested as full motion video (FMV) games such as the controversial Night Trap, which became a focus of the 1993 congressional hearings on issues of video game violence and ratings. Sega of Japan partnered with JVC to design the Sega CD and refused to consult with Sega of America until the project was complete. Sega of America assembled parts from various "dummy" units to obtain a working prototype. It was redesigned several times by Sega and licensed third-party developers.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Sega CD (Mega-CD w większości regionów poza Ameryką Północną i Brazylią) – akcesorium dodające napęd CD do konsoli gier wideo czwartej generacji firmy Sega – Sega Genesis. Pozwala na granie w gry, które sprzedawane były na płytach kompaktowych. Może również odtwarzać muzykę.

Największą zaletą płyt CD dla programistów piszących na konsolę Genesis była ich duża pojemność w porównaniu do tradycyjnych kartridży. W czasie gdy standardowa pojemność kartridża wynosiła 4 MB – czyli tyle, co jeden utwór muzyczny w formacie MP3 – płyty posiadały pojemność około 700 MB. Dały one możliwość urozmaicenia zawartości tytułów sprzedawanych na konsolę o większą ilość muzyki w wyższej jakości, lepszą grafikę lub nawet sprzedawanie składanek (kilku gier na jednym nośniku).</text>
			<text lang="ru">Дополнение к игровой приставке Sega Mega Drive от компании Sega, было выпущено в Европе, Австралии, Новой Зеландии, Японии и Северной Америке. В Северной Америке система носила название Sega CD. Устройство улучшало возможности Mega Drive и добавляло возможность проигрывать игры, записанные на компакт-диске, слушать аудиодиски и запускать диски формата CD+G.

Основным преимуществом использования технологии компакт-дисков стало увеличение объема, доступного для хранения данных, что позволило играм увеличиться в размерах почти в 320 раз по сравнению с картриджами для Mega Drive. Это преимущество привело к тому, что для приставки выпускались full motion video игры, такие как Night Trap, которая вызвала разногласия вокруг неё и стала предметом слушаний в Конгрессе по вопросам насилия в видеоиграх. Компания Sega разработала приставку в партнерстве с JVC и отказывалась консультироваться со своим американским подразделением до завершения проекта. Американскому подразделению пришлось собрать свои экземпляры из различных компонентов для того чтобы получить рабочий прототип. Приставка неоднократно перепроектировалась и переиздавалась компанией Sega и лицензированными сторонними разработчиками.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Sega CD, lanzado como Mega-CD en la mayoría de las regiones fuera de Norteamérica y Brasil, es un accesorio de CD-ROM para la Mega Drive/Genesis diseñado y producido por Sega como parte de la cuarta generación de consolas de videojuegos. Salió a la venta el 12 de diciembre de 1991 en Japón, el 15 de octubre de 1992 en Norteamérica y el 2 de abril de 1993 en Europa. La Sega CD reproduce juegos basados en CD y añade funciones de hardware, como una unidad central de procesamiento más rápida y mejoras gráficas, como el escalado y la rotación de sprites. También puede reproducir CD de audio y discos CD+G.

La principal ventaja de la tecnología de CD era su mayor capacidad de almacenamiento, que permitía que los juegos fueran casi 320 veces más grandes que los cartuchos de Genesis. Esta ventaja se manifestó en juegos de vídeo de movimiento completo (FMV), como el controvertido Night Trap, que se convirtió en el centro de atención de las audiencias del Congreso de 1993 sobre cuestiones de violencia y clasificación de videojuegos. Sega of Japan se asoció con JVC para diseñar el Sega CD y se negó a consultar con Sega of America hasta que el proyecto estuvo terminado. Sega of America ensambló piezas de varias unidades "ficticias" para obtener un prototipo funcional. Fue rediseñado varias veces por Sega y terceros desarrolladores bajo licencia.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Sega CD, die in den meisten Regionen außerhalb Nordamerikas und Brasiliens als Mega-CD veröffentlicht wurde, ist ein CD-ROM-Zubehör für das Mega Drive/Genesis, das von Sega als Teil der vierten Generation von Videospielkonsolen entwickelt und produziert wurde. Es wurde am 12. Dezember 1991 in Japan, am 15. Oktober 1992 in Nordamerika und am 2. April 1993 in Europa veröffentlicht. Die Sega CD spielt CD-basierte Spiele und bietet zusätzliche Hardwarefunktionen wie eine schnellere Zentraleinheit und grafische Verbesserungen wie die Skalierung und Rotation von Sprites. Sie kann auch Audio-CDs und CD+G-Discs abspielen.

Der Hauptvorteil der CD-Technologie war die größere Speicherkapazität, die es ermöglichte, Spiele fast 320 Mal größer zu machen als bei den Genesis-Cartridges. Dieser Vorteil manifestierte sich in Full-Motion-Video-Spielen (FMV) wie dem umstrittenen Night Trap, das 1993 im Mittelpunkt der Kongressanhörungen zum Thema Gewalt in Videospielen und deren Bewertung stand. Sega of Japan arbeitete bei der Entwicklung der Sega CD mit JVC zusammen und weigerte sich, Sega of America zu konsultieren, bis das Projekt abgeschlossen war. Sega of America baute Teile aus verschiedenen "Dummy"-Geräten zusammen, um einen funktionierenden Prototyp zu erhalten. Die CD wurde von Sega und lizenzierten Drittentwicklern mehrmals umgestaltet.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Sega CD, commercialisé sous le nom de Mega-CD dans la plupart des régions en dehors de l'Amérique du Nord et du Brésil, est un accessoire CD-ROM pour la Mega Drive/Genesis conçu et produit par Sega dans le cadre de la quatrième génération de consoles de jeux vidéo. Il est sorti le 12 décembre 1991 au Japon, le 15 octobre 1992 en Amérique du Nord et le 2 avril 1993 en Europe. Le Sega CD joue à des jeux sur CD et ajoute des fonctionnalités matérielles telles qu'une unité centrale de traitement plus rapide et des améliorations graphiques telles que la mise à l'échelle et la rotation des sprites. Il peut également lire les CD audio et les disques CD+G.

Le principal avantage de la technologie CD est l'augmentation de la capacité de stockage, qui permet aux jeux d'être près de 320 fois plus volumineux que les cartouches Genesis. Cet avantage s'est traduit par des jeux vidéo à mouvement complet (FMV) tels que le controversé Night Trap, qui a été au centre des auditions du Congrès en 1993 sur les questions de la violence dans les jeux vidéo et de leur classification. Sega of Japan s'est associé à JVC pour concevoir le Sega CD et a refusé de consulter Sega of America jusqu'à ce que le projet soit terminé. Sega of America a assemblé des pièces provenant de diverses unités "factices" pour obtenir un prototype fonctionnel. Le CD a été remanié à plusieurs reprises par Sega et par des développeurs tiers sous licence.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Sega CD, pubblicato come Mega-CD nella maggior parte delle regioni al di fuori del Nord America e del Brasile, è un accessorio CD-ROM per il Mega Drive/Genesis progettato e prodotto da Sega come parte della quarta generazione di console per videogiochi. È stato rilasciato il 12 dicembre 1991 in Giappone, il 15 ottobre 1992 in Nord America e il 2 aprile 1993 in Europa. Il Sega CD riproduce giochi basati su CD e aggiunge funzionalità hardware come un'unità di elaborazione centrale più veloce e miglioramenti grafici come la scalatura e la rotazione degli sprite. Può anche riprodurre CD audio e dischi CD+G.

Il principale vantaggio della tecnologia CD era la maggiore capacità di memorizzazione, che consentiva ai giochi di essere quasi 320 volte più grandi delle cartucce Genesis. Questo vantaggio si è manifestato nei giochi full motion video (FMV), come il controverso Night Trap, che è stato al centro delle audizioni del Congresso del 1993 sulle questioni relative alla violenza e alla classificazione dei videogiochi. Sega of Japan si associò a JVC per progettare il Sega CD e rifiutò di consultarsi con Sega of America fino al completamento del progetto. Sega of America assemblò parti di varie unità "fittizie" per ottenere un prototipo funzionante. Il CD fu riprogettato più volte da Sega e da sviluppatori di terze parti su licenza.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
