<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.482 0.395</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.202 0.395" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1983</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>Sega
SG-1000</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The SG-1000 is a home video game console manufactured by Sega and released in Japan, Australia, New Zealand, and other regions. It was Sega's first entry into the home video game hardware business. Introduced in 1983, the SG-1000 was released on the same day that Nintendo released the Family Computer in Japan. The SG-1000 was released in several forms, including the SC-3000 computer and the redesigned SG-1000 II released in 1984. A third iteration of the console, the Sega Mark III, was released in 1985. It provided a custom video display processor over previous iterations and served as the basis for the Master System in 1986, Sega's first internationally released console.

Developed in response to a downturn in arcades in 1982, the SG-1000 was created on the advice of Hayao Nakayama, president of Sega Enterprises, Ltd. Shortly after the release, Sega Enterprises was sold to CSK Corporation, which was followed by the release of the SG-1000 II. The SC-3000 and the SG-1000 line both support a library of 76 ROM cartridge games and 29 Sega My Card games, all of which are fully compatible with the Mark III and the Japanese version of the Master System.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">La SG-1000 (エスジー・セン, Esujī Sen), également connue sous le nom Sega Game 1000, est une console de jeux vidéo de troisième génération conçue et commercialisée par le constructeur japonais Sega Enterprises, Ltd. La console marque l'entrée de Sega dans le jeu vidéo à domicile et constitue une base pour la plus fructueuse Master System. Dévoilée en 1983, la SG-1000 sort le même jour que la Famicom de Nintendo au Japon. Elle est mise sur le marché sous plusieurs formes, comprenant l'ordinateur SC-3000 et la version redessinée SG-1000 II lancée en 1984.

Développée en réponse à un ralentissement du marché des salles d'arcade en 1982, la SG-1000 est créée sur les conseils de Hayao Nakayama, président de Sega of Japan. En compétition directe avec la Famicom, la SG-1000, pourtant plus faible technologiquement, réalise une première année d'exploitation meilleure que prévu, en raison des problèmes techniques que rencontre la console de Nintendo. Peu de temps après sa sortie, Sega est vendu à CSK Corporation et il s'ensuit le lancement du modèle SG-1000 II.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Домашняя игровая приставка производства компании Sega, выпущенная в Японии, Австралии и других регионах. Это была первая попытка Sega заняться производством домашнего игрового оборудования. Представленная в 1983 году, SG-1000 была выпущена в тот же день, когда Nintendo выпустила Family Computer в Японии. SG-1000 была выпущена в нескольких вариантах, в число которых входили домашний компьютер SC-3000 и обновленная версия SG-1000 II, выпущенная в 1984 году. Третья версия приставки, Sega Mark III, была выпущена в 1985 году, и по сравнению с предыдущими вариантами оснащалась специализированным видеопроцессором. Sega Mark III легла в основу Master System, вышедшей в 1986 году первой приставки компании Sega, которая продавалась по всему миру.

Приставка была разработана в ответ на спад в индустрии аркадных игр, начавшийся в 1982 году. SG-1000 была разработана по совету Хаяо Накаямы, президента компании Sega Enterprises, Ltd. Вскоре после выпуска приставки компания Sega Enterprises была продана корпорации CSK Corporation, и за этим последовало издание второй версии приставки, SG-1000 II. И SC-3000 и SG-1000 имеют библиотеку из 76 игр на игровых картриджах и 29 игр на карточках Sega My Card, и все они полностью совместимы с Mark III и японской версией Master System.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>