<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videocrton" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_ON.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<loops>0</loops>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
		</video>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/snes-msu1.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/snes-msu1.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1990</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Nintendo / Sony</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Super NES CD-ROM System</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<!-- Support different names for regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="us"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="jp">
			<text>Super Famicom CD-ROM Adapter</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Super NES CD-ROM System (commonly shortened as the SNES-CD), known as the Super Famicom CD-ROM Adapter in Japan, is an unreleased add-on for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES) video game console. It built upon the functionality of the cartridge-based SNES by adding support for a CD-ROM-based format known as Super Disc.

The SNES-CD was developed in a joint venture between Nintendo and Sony. As well as the SNES add-on, Sony planned to release it as a hybrid console, the PlayStation, similar to Sharp's Twin Famicom and NEC's TurboDuo. Another partnership with Philips yielded a few Nintendo-themed games for the CD-i platform instead of the SNES-CD.

After the SNES-CD was canceled, Sony developed its own console using the PlayStation name. The first PlayStation console became the chief competitor of Nintendo's next console, the Nintendo 64.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Super NES CD-ROM System (powszechnie skracany jako SNES-CD), znany jako Super Famicom CD-ROM Adapter w Japonii, jest niewydanym dodatkiem do konsoli gier wideo Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES). Opierał się na funkcjonalności SNES opartej na kartridżach, dodając wsparcie dla formatu opartego na CD-ROM znanego jako Super Disc.

SNES-CD został opracowany w ramach wspólnego przedsięwzięcia Nintendo i Sony. Oprócz dodatku do SNES-a, Sony planowało wydać go jako hybrydową konsolę, PlayStation, podobną do Twin Famicom firmy Sharp i TurboDuo firmy NEC. Inna współpraca z Philipsem zaowocowała kilkoma grami o tematyce Nintendo na platformę CD-i zamiast SNES-CD.

Po zaprzestaniu produkcji SNES-CD, Sony stworzyło własną konsolę pod nazwą PlayStation. Pierwsza konsola PlayStation stała się głównym konkurentem następnej konsoli Nintendo, Nintendo 64.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Super NES CD-ROM System (обычно сокращенно SNES-CD), известный в Японии как Super Famicom CD-ROM Adapter, - это невыпущенное дополнение для игровой консоли Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES). Оно развивало функциональность SNES на базе картриджа, добавляя поддержку формата CD-ROM, известного как Super Disc.

SNES-CD был разработан совместным предприятием Nintendo и Sony. Помимо дополнения к SNES, Sony планировала выпустить ее в виде гибридной консоли PlayStation, аналогичной Twin Famicom от Sharp и TurboDuo от NEC. Еще одно сотрудничество с Philips позволило выпустить несколько игр на тему Nintendo для платформы CD-i вместо SNES-CD.

После отмены SNES-CD компания Sony разработала собственную консоль под названием PlayStation. Первая консоль PlayStation стала главным конкурентом следующей консоли Nintendo, Nintendo 64.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Super NES CD-ROM System (communément abrégé en SNES-CD), connu sous le nom de Super Famicom CD-ROM Adapter au Japon, est un complément inédit de la console de jeux vidéo Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES). Il s'appuie sur les fonctionnalités de la SNES à cartouche en ajoutant la prise en charge d'un format de CD-ROM connu sous le nom de Super Disc.

Le SNES-CD a été développé dans le cadre d'une coentreprise entre Nintendo et Sony. En plus de l'extension SNES, Sony prévoyait de la commercialiser sous la forme d'une console hybride, la PlayStation, similaire à la Twin Famicom de Sharp et à la TurboDuo de NEC. Un autre partenariat avec Philips a permis de produire quelques jeux sur le thème de Nintendo pour la plate-forme CD-i au lieu du SNES-CD.

Après l'annulation de la SNES-CD, Sony a développé sa propre console sous le nom de PlayStation. La première console PlayStation est devenue le principal concurrent de la prochaine console de Nintendo, la Nintendo 64.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Super NES CD-ROM System (comunemente abbreviato in SNES-CD), noto come Super Famicom CD-ROM Adapter in Giappone, è un componente aggiuntivo inedito per la console per videogiochi Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES). Si basava sulle funzionalità dello SNES a cartuccia, aggiungendo il supporto per un formato basato su CD-ROM, noto come Super Disc.

Lo SNES-CD è stato sviluppato in una joint venture tra Nintendo e Sony. Oltre al componente aggiuntivo per SNES, Sony prevedeva di rilasciare una console ibrida, la PlayStation, simile al Twin Famicom di Sharp e al TurboDuo di NEC. Un'altra collaborazione con Philips portò alla realizzazione di alcuni giochi a tema Nintendo per la piattaforma CD-i invece che per lo SNES-CD.

Dopo la cancellazione dello SNES-CD, Sony sviluppò una propria console con il nome di PlayStation. La prima console PlayStation divenne il principale concorrente della successiva console di Nintendo, il Nintendo 64.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
