<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.25</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.245</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1990</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>byuu</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Super Nintendo MSU-1</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The MSU-1 is a cartridge addon chip (similar to the SuperFx chip) that allows for many enhancements to SNES games including, but not limited to, full-motion video and CD quality sound by adding up to 4GB (yes, 4 gigabytes) of storage for extra content.

Some examples of MSU-1 modded games would be:

Zelda: A Link to the Past done with a fully orchistrated CD quality soundtrack.
Chrono Trigger with all the video cutscenes from the PlayStation version inserted.
Mega Man X with a new CD quality soundtrack.

The MSU-1 chip itself only needs to be in the game cartridge to run on an actual unmodded SNES system. Emulators, on the other hand, need to be modified to support playback of MSU-1 modded games. This is due to the emulator needing to access files outside the ROM while playing the ROM.
The chip does have some limitations, such as only being able to stream one data track at a time, but it essentially turns the SNES into what it could have been with a CD attachment.</text>
			<text lang="pl">MSU1 jest układem rozszerzającym, nie różniącym się zupełnie od SuperFX, SDD-1, CX4 czy serii DSP używanych w takich grach jak Yoshi's Island, Star Ocean, Mega Man X 2 i większości gier ze scenami w Trybie 7. W związku z tym jest to część kartridża z grą. Często spotykanym błędnym przekonaniem jest to, że sprzętowe wsparcie MSU1 wymaga modyfikacji głównej jednostki SNES-a, nie jest to prawda.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игры Super Nintendo, улучшенные с помощью MSU-1
MSU-1 это специальный сопроцессор, добавляющий игровой приставке Super Nintendo несколько интересных возможностей:

- Воспроизведение звука CD-качества (44.1 кГц, 16 бит)
- Воспроизведение потокового видео
- Адресация 4 Гб данных
То есть, примерно то же самое, что ожидалось от Nintendo PlayStation (Super NES CD-ROM).

Благодаря таким возможностям, ROM хакеры могут заменять фоновую музыку в играх на их высококачественные версии, и даже воспроизводить полнометражные видеоролики.
Аббревиатура MSU означает "Media Streaming Unit 1".
Это современная разработка от автора эмуляторов bsnes и higan - byuu. Примерный год создания - 2010, однако, понадобилось много лет, чтобы данный чип расширения получил поддержку со стороны программистов. К сожалению, странички проекта были полностью удалены из веб-архива, поэтому, не удаётся выяснить больше подробностей. Но известно, что MSU1 начинался как 21fx ещё в 2009-м году.</text>
			<text lang="es">El MSU-1 es un chip adicional para cartuchos (similar al chip SuperFx) que permite introducir muchas mejoras en los juegos de SNES, entre otras, vídeo de movimiento completo y sonido con calidad de CD, añadiendo hasta 4 GB (sí, 4 gigabytes) de almacenamiento para contenido adicional.

Algunos ejemplos de juegos modificados con MSU-1 serían:

Zelda: A Link to the Past con una banda sonora de calidad CD totalmente orquestada.
Chrono Trigger con todas las escenas de vídeo de la versión para PlayStation.
Mega Man X con una nueva banda sonora de calidad CD.

El chip MSU-1 sólo necesita estar en el cartucho para funcionar en un sistema SNES sin modificar. En cambio, los emuladores deben modificarse para poder reproducir juegos modificados con MSU-1. Esto se debe a que el emulador no puede reproducir juegos modificados. Esto se debe a que el emulador necesita acceder a archivos fuera de la ROM mientras reproduce la ROM.
El chip tiene algunas limitaciones, como que sólo puede transmitir una pista de datos a la vez, pero básicamente convierte la SNES en lo que podría haber sido con un accesorio de CD.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der MSU-1 ist ein Cartridge-Addon-Chip (ähnlich dem SuperFx-Chip), der viele Erweiterungen für SNES-Spiele ermöglicht, einschließlich, aber nicht beschränkt auf Full-Motion-Video und Sound in CD-Qualität, indem er bis zu 4 GB (ja, 4 Gigabyte) Speicherplatz für zusätzliche Inhalte bietet.

Einige Beispiele für MSU-1 modifizierte Spiele sind:

Zelda: A Link to the Past mit einem vollständig orchestrierten Soundtrack in CD-Qualität.
Chrono Trigger mit allen eingefügten Videoszenen aus der PlayStation-Version.
Mega Man X mit einer neuen Tonspur in CD-Qualität.

Der MSU-1-Chip selbst muss sich nur in der Spielkassette befinden, um auf einem aktuellen, nicht modifizierten SNES-System zu laufen. Emulatoren hingegen müssen modifiziert werden, um die Wiedergabe von MSU-1-modifizierten Spielen zu unterstützen. Das liegt daran, dass der Emulator beim Abspielen des ROMs auf Dateien außerhalb des ROMs zugreifen muss.
Der Chip hat einige Einschränkungen, wie z. B. die Möglichkeit, nur einen Datentrack gleichzeitig zu übertragen, aber er macht das SNES im Wesentlichen zu dem, was es mit einem CD-Aufsatz hätte sein können.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le MSU-1 est une puce d'extension de cartouche (similaire à la puce SuperFx) qui permet de nombreuses améliorations des jeux SNES, y compris, mais sans s'y limiter, la vidéo pleine image et le son de qualité CD, en ajoutant jusqu'à 4 Go (oui, 4 gigaoctets) de stockage pour le contenu supplémentaire.

Voici quelques exemples de jeux modifiés par le MSU-1 :

Zelda : A Link to the Past avec une bande sonore de qualité CD entièrement orchestrée.
Chrono Trigger avec toutes les scènes vidéo de la version PlayStation insérées.
Mega Man X avec une nouvelle bande sonore de qualité CD.

La puce MSU-1 elle-même n'a besoin que d'être dans la cartouche du jeu pour fonctionner sur un système SNES non modifié. Les émulateurs, en revanche, doivent être modifiés pour pouvoir lire les jeux modifiés par la puce MSU-1. Cela est dû au fait que l'émulateur doit accéder à des fichiers en dehors de la ROM pendant la lecture de la ROM.
La puce a quelques limitations, comme le fait de ne pouvoir lire qu'une piste de données à la fois, mais elle transforme essentiellement la SNES en ce qu'elle aurait pu être avec un attachement CD.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'MSU-1 è un chip aggiuntivo per cartucce (simile al chip SuperFx) che consente di apportare numerosi miglioramenti ai giochi SNES, tra cui, ma non solo, video in full-motion e audio di qualità CD, aggiungendo fino a 4 GB (sì, 4 gigabyte) di memoria per contenuti extra.

Alcuni esempi di giochi modificati con MSU-1 sono:

Zelda: A Link to the Past con una colonna sonora di qualità CD completamente orchestrata.
Chrono Trigger con tutte le scene video della versione PlayStation inserite.
Mega Man X con una nuova colonna sonora di qualità CD.

Lo stesso chip MSU-1 deve essere presente nella cartuccia del gioco per funzionare su un sistema SNES non modificato. Gli emulatori, invece, devono essere modificati per supportare la riproduzione dei giochi modificati con MSU-1. Ciò è dovuto al fatto che l'emulatore deve accedere a file esterni alla ROM durante la riproduzione di quest'ultima.
Il chip ha alcune limitazioni, come la possibilità di trasmettere una sola traccia di dati alla volta, ma essenzialmente trasforma lo SNES in quello che avrebbe potuto essere con una periferica CD.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
