<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
  <formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
  <view name="system">
    <image name="background1" extra="true">
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
      </storyboard>
    </image>
    <image name="background" extra="true">
      <zIndex>90</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
      </storyboard>
    </image>
    <video name="videocrton" extra="true">
      <path>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_ON.mp4</path>
      <delay>0</delay>
      <loops>0</loops>
      <effect>none</effect>
      <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
      <pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
      <maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
      <zIndex>26</zIndex>
    </video>
    <video name="videobox" extra="true">
      <path>{random}</path>
      <path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
      <!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
      <path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
      <default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
      <delay>0</delay>
      <effect>none</effect>
      <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
      <pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
      <maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
      <zIndex>25</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
      </storyboard>
    </video>
    <text name="TextDate" extra="true">
      <pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
      <text>1990</text>
      <fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
      <color>666666</color>
      <fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
      <zIndex>140</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
      </storyboard>
    </text>
    <text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
      <pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
      <text>byuu</text>
      <fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
      <color>FFFFFF</color>
      <fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
      <zIndex>140</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
      </storyboard>
    </text>
    <text name="TextName" extra="true">
      <pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
      <size>0.5 0</size>
      <text>Super Nintendo MSU-1</text>
      <fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
      <color>FFFFFF</color>
      <fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
      <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
      <zIndex>140</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
      </storyboard>
    </text>
    <text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
      <size>0.5 0</size>
      <pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
      <text>The MSU-1 is a cartridge addon chip (similar to the SuperFx chip) that allows for many enhancements to SNES games including, but not limited to, full-motion video and CD quality sound by adding up to 4GB (yes, 4 gigabytes) of storage for extra content.

Some examples of MSU-1 modded games would be:

Zelda: A Link to the Past done with a fully orchistrated CD quality soundtrack.
Chrono Trigger with all the video cutscenes from the PlayStation version inserted.
Mega Man X with a new CD quality soundtrack.

The MSU-1 chip itself only needs to be in the game cartridge to run on an actual unmodded SNES system. Emulators, on the other hand, need to be modified to support playback of MSU-1 modded games. This is due to the emulator needing to access files outside the ROM while playing the ROM.
The chip does have some limitations, such as only being able to stream one data track at a time, but it essentially turns the SNES into what it could have been with a CD attachment.</text>
      <text lang="pl">MSU1 jest układem rozszerzającym, nie różniącym się zupełnie od SuperFX, SDD-1, CX4 czy serii DSP używanych w takich grach jak Yoshi's Island, Star Ocean, Mega Man X 2 i większości gier ze scenami w Trybie 7. W związku z tym jest to część kartridża z grą. Często spotykanym błędnym przekonaniem jest to, że sprzętowe wsparcie MSU1 wymaga modyfikacji głównej jednostki SNES-a, nie jest to prawda.</text>
      <text lang="ru">Игры Super Nintendo, улучшенные с помощью MSU-1
MSU-1 это специальный сопроцессор, добавляющий игровой приставке Super Nintendo несколько интересных возможностей:

- Воспроизведение звука CD-качества (44.1 кГц, 16 бит)
- Воспроизведение потокового видео
- Адресация 4 Гб данных
То есть, примерно то же самое, что ожидалось от Nintendo PlayStation (Super NES CD-ROM).

Благодаря таким возможностям, ROM хакеры могут заменять фоновую музыку в играх на их высококачественные версии, и даже воспроизводить полнометражные видеоролики.
Аббревиатура MSU означает "Media Streaming Unit 1".
Это современная разработка от автора эмуляторов bsnes и higan - byuu. Примерный год создания - 2010, однако, понадобилось много лет, чтобы данный чип расширения получил поддержку со стороны программистов. К сожалению, странички проекта были полностью удалены из веб-архива, поэтому, не удаётся выяснить больше подробностей. Но известно, что MSU1 начинался как 21fx ещё в 2009-м году.</text>
      <text lang="it">L'MSU-1 è un chip aggiuntivo per cartucce (simile al chip SuperFx) che consente di apportare numerosi miglioramenti ai giochi SNES, tra cui, ma non solo, video in full-motion e audio di qualità CD, aggiungendo fino a 4 GB (sì, 4 gigabyte) di memoria per contenuti extra.

Alcuni esempi di giochi modificati con MSU-1 sono:

Zelda: A Link to the Past con una colonna sonora di qualità CD completamente orchestrata.
Chrono Trigger con tutte le scene video della versione PlayStation inserite.
Mega Man X con una nuova colonna sonora di qualità CD.

Lo stesso chip MSU-1 deve essere presente nella cartuccia del gioco per funzionare su un sistema SNES non modificato. Gli emulatori, invece, devono essere modificati per supportare la riproduzione dei giochi modificati con MSU-1. Ciò è dovuto al fatto che l'emulatore deve accedere a file esterni alla ROM durante la riproduzione di quest'ultima.
Il chip ha alcune limitazioni, come la possibilità di trasmettere una sola traccia di dati alla volta, ma essenzialmente trasforma lo SNES in quello che avrebbe potuto essere con una periferica CD.</text>
      <fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
      <color>666666</color>
      <fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
      <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
      <zIndex>140</zIndex>
      <storyboard>
        <animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
        <animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
      </storyboard>
    </text>
  </view>
</theme>
