<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.25</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.393</pos>
			<maxSize>0.14</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.18</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.16</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.393" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise169.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.2</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.393</pos>
			<maxSize>0.125</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.16</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.14</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.393" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1995</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Bandai / VTech</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Super Note Club</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Super Note Club computer is an educational device produced by Bandai and VTech in 1995. It is a portable computer with an LCD screen and a QWERTY keyboard, which allowed people to write texts, draw, play games, and learn English.

Equipped with has an internal memory of 256 KB and a lithium battery that lasted up to 100 hours, the Super Note Club also had a monochrome LCD screen with a resolution of 320 x 240 pixels and a serial port to connect to other devices, as well as a port to connect cartridges with additional content and functions.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Komputer Super Note Club to urządzenie edukacyjne wyprodukowane przez Bandai i VTech w 1995 roku. Był to przenośny komputer z ekranem LCD i klawiaturą QWERTY, który pozwalał użytkownikom pisać teksty, rysować, grać w gry i uczyć się angielskiego.

Wyposażony w pamięć wewnętrzną o pojemności 256 KB i baterię litową, która działała do 100 godzin, Super Note Club posiadał również monochromatyczny ekran LCD o rozdzielczości 320 x 240 pikseli i port szeregowy do łączenia się z innymi urządzeniami, a także port do podłączania wkładów z dodatkową zawartością i funkcjami.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Компьютер Super Note Club - это образовательное устройство, выпущенное компаниями Bandai и VTech в 1995 году. Это был портативный компьютер с ЖК-экраном и QWERTY-клавиатурой, позволявший писать тексты, рисовать, играть в игры и изучать английский язык.

Super Note Club оснащался встроенной памятью объемом 256 КБ и литиевой батареей, рассчитанной на работу до 100 часов, а также монохромным ЖК-экраном с разрешением 320 х 240 пикселей и последовательным портом для подключения к другим устройствам, а также портом для подключения картриджей с дополнительным содержимым и функциями.</text>
			<text lang="es">El ordenador Super Note Club es un dispositivo educativo producido por Bandai y VTech en 1995. Se trataba de un ordenador portátil con pantalla LCD y teclado QWERTY, que permitía a los usuarios escribir textos, dibujar, jugar y aprender inglés.

Equipado con una memoria interna de 256 KB y una batería de litio que duraba hasta 100 horas, el Super Note Club también tenía una pantalla LCD monocroma con una resolución de 320 x 240 píxeles y un puerto serie para conectarse a otros dispositivos, así como un puerto para conectar cartuchos con contenidos y funciones adicionales.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Super Note Club Computer ist ein von Bandai und VTech im Jahr 1995 hergestelltes Lerngerät. Es handelte sich um einen tragbaren Computer mit einem LCD-Bildschirm und einer QWERTZ-Tastatur, mit dem die Benutzer Texte schreiben, zeichnen, Spiele spielen und Englisch lernen konnten.

Ausgestattet mit einem internen Speicher von 256 KB und einer Lithium-Batterie, die bis zu 100 Stunden durchhielt, verfügte der Super Note Club auch über einen monochromen LCD-Bildschirm mit einer Auflösung von 320 x 240 Pixeln und einen seriellen Anschluss für die Verbindung mit anderen Geräten sowie einen Anschluss für Kassetten mit zusätzlichen Inhalten und Funktionen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'ordinateur Super Note Club est un appareil éducatif produit par Bandai et VTech en 1995. Il s'agit d'un ordinateur portable doté d'un écran LCD et d'un clavier QWERTY, qui permet d'écrire des textes, de dessiner, de jouer à des jeux et d'apprendre l'anglais.

Doté d'une mémoire interne de 256 Ko et d'une batterie au lithium d'une autonomie de 100 heures, le Super Note Club disposait également d'un écran LCD monochrome d'une résolution de 320 x 240 pixels et d'un port série pour se connecter à d'autres appareils, ainsi que d'un port pour connecter des cartouches avec des contenus et des fonctions supplémentaires.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il computer Super Note Club è un dispositivo educativo prodotto da Bandai e VTech nel 1995. Si tratta di un computer portatile con uno schermo LCD e una tastiera QWERTY, che permetteva di scrivere testi, disegnare, giocare e imparare l’inglese.

Dotato di ha una memoria interna di 256 KB e una batteria al litio che durava fino a 100 ore, il Super Note Club disponeva anche uno schermo LCD monocromatico con una risoluzione di 320 x 240 pixel e una porta seriale per collegarsi ad altri dispositivi, oltre ad una porta per collegare delle cartucce con ulteriori contenuti e funzioni.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
