<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1996</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>SuFami Turbo</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The SuFami Turbo (スーファミターボ), often compared to the Aladdin Deck Enhancer, is an accessory released by Bandai for Nintendo's Super Famicom system and was released in 1996.
			
This device is designed to sit on top of the Super Famicom, and features two cartridge slots. The premise is that games could be produced at a much lower cost and development time, not having to rely on Nintendo for cartridge production. Unlike the Aladdin Deck Enhancer, this device was officially approved by Nintendo under the provision that Bandai handle all the hardware manufacturing itself.

The two cartridge slots are designed to share data between the games. The cartridge placed in slot 1 is the game that will be played, while the cartridge in slot 2 supplies additional data for use in the main game. Of the thirteen games released, nine of them can link up, within each game series.
			</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Super Nintendo Entertainment System (couramment abrégée Super NES ou SNES ou encore Super Nintendo), ou Super Famicom (スーパーファミコン) au Japon, est une console de jeux vidéo du constructeur japonais Nintendo commercialisée à partir de novembre 1990. En Amérique du Nord, la console est sortie avec un look résolument différent. À noter qu'en Corée du Sud, la Super Nintendo est distribuée par Hyundai Electronics sous le nom de Super Comboy (슈퍼 컴보이).

En 1997 et 1998, Nintendo décide de rafraîchir le design en sortant le modèle SNS-101, parfois appelé Super NES 2 aux États-Unis, et la Super Famicom Jr. au Japon.

Pour rivaliser avec la populaire Nintendo Entertainment System / Famicom qui écrase le marché, NEC lance la PC-Engine en 1987, et Sega suit avec sa Mega Drive en 1988. Les deux systèmes offrent alors de bien meilleures performances, notamment graphiques et sonores, que la 8 bits de Nintendo. Bien que la NES continue d'être leader sur le marché des jeux vidéo, le bon accueil de la Mega Drive et de la PC-engine par les différents acteurs du marché contraint Nintendo à créer une console pouvant rivaliser avec ses nouvelles concurrentes.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">16-разрядная игровая приставка. стала второй домашней консолью Nintendo вслед за NES (которая выпускалась в Японии под названием Famicom). В SNES были представлены улучшенные графические и звуковые возможности по сравнению с другими консолями того времени. Кроме того, разработка дополнительных чипов, которые встраивались в картридж игры, позволяла ей оставаться конкурентоспособной на мировом рынке даже после выхода следующего поколения игровых приставок.

Консоль приобрела популярность во многих странах, став самой продаваемой 16-битной приставкой, несмотря на упорную конкуренцию в Северной Америке со стороны Sega. SNES осталась популярна в эпоху 32-битных систем среди фанатов, коллекционеров и энтузиастов, работающих с эмуляцией (которые создают самодельные образы ПЗУ), несмотря на то, что Nintendo прекратила поддержку данной консоли.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>