<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.25</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.333</pos>
			<maxSize>0.235</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.333" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.25</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.333</pos>
			<maxSize>0.225</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.333" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1992</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Watara</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Supervision</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Watara Supervision, also known as the QuickShot Supervision in the UK, is a monochrome handheld game console, originating from Asia, and introduced in 1992 as a cut-price competitor for Nintendo's Game Boy. It came packaged with a game called Crystball, which is similar to Breakout. One unique feature of the Supervision was that it could be linked up to a television via a link cable. Games played in this way would display in four colors, much like Nintendo's Super Game Boy add-on for the SNES. A full color TV link was also in the works, but because of the Supervision's failure to make a major impression among gamers it was cancelled, along with the games which were in development for it.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Watara Supervision – przenośna konsola gier wideo wyprodukowana przez przedsiębiorstwo Watara i wydana w Azji w 1992 roku. W założeniach miała stanowić tańszą konkurencję dla Game Boya.

Pomimo niższej ceny, konsola miała gorszy wyświetlacz od Game Boya oraz niewielką bibliotekę gier, z których większość stanowiły klony znanych hitów. Sprzęt był wydawany pod wieloma markami takimi jak QuickShot (Wielka Brytania), Electrolab (Argentyna), Tiger Boy (Tajwan) i Sherion (Polska). Konsolę sprzedawano razem z grą Crystball, będącą klonem Breakouta.

Dane techniczne:
- 8-bitowy procesor 65C02 (4 MHz)
- wyświetlacz LCD 160x160 pikseli, 4 odcienie szarości
- dźwięk stereo (zapewniały podłączone do konsoli słuchawki)
- kartridże jako nośniki danych
- zasilanie stanowiły 4 baterie AA lub 6V AC/DC adapter</text>
			<text lang="ru">Оригинальная версия Supervision появилась в 1992 году и внешним видом напоминала популярный в то время Game Boy — прямоугольный вертикальный корпус с крестовиной, двумя расположенными по диагонали круглыми кнопками управления (А и В) и двумя вытянутыми узкими кнопками select и start/pause. Данная модель состояла из двух частей — экран и разъём для картриджа сверху и кнопки управления снизу. При желании можно было менять положение верхней части относительно нижней, сгибая её под небольшим углом. Такая версия была выпущена также компанией Tai-Kerr в Гонконге и Китае (Tai-Kerr Boy), в Дании компанией Vini Spil (Vini Supervision), компанией Quickshot в Великобритании (под названием Quickshot Supervision), компанией Hartung в Германии и Голландии (Hartung Supervision) и компанией Audiosonic (Audio Sonic Supervision) во Франции, Италии и ряде других стран Европы.

Другая модель консоли — GB-2000, более похожая внешне на Game Boy, была выпущена компаниями Audiosonic, Vini Spil и самой Watara. Третья модель — 9600, с похожим на GB-2000 корпусом, но сглаженными краями, была выпущена компаниями Magnus и Videojet. Эта модель была доступна в трёх цветовых вариантах — белая, синяя и жёлтая.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Watara Supervision, también conocida como QuickShot Supervision en el Reino Unido, es una videoconsola portátil monocroma originaria de Asia que se presentó en 1992 como competidora a bajo precio de la Game Boy de Nintendo. Venía con un juego llamado Crystball, similar a Breakout. Una característica exclusiva del Supervision era que podía conectarse a un televisor mediante un cable de conexión. Los juegos se mostraban en cuatro colores, como la Super Game Boy de Nintendo para la SNES. También se estaba trabajando en una conexión a televisión a todo color, pero debido a que la Supervision no causó una gran impresión entre los jugadores, se canceló, junto con los juegos que se estaban desarrollando para ella.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Watara Supervision, im Vereinigten Königreich auch als QuickShot Supervision bekannt, ist eine aus Asien stammende monochrome Handheld-Spielkonsole, die 1992 als preisgünstiger Konkurrent zum Game Boy von Nintendo eingeführt wurde. Zum Lieferumfang gehörte ein Spiel namens Crystball, das Breakout ähnelt. Eine Besonderheit des Supervision war, dass er über ein Verbindungskabel mit einem Fernseher verbunden werden konnte. Spiele, die auf diese Weise gespielt wurden, wurden in vier Farben angezeigt, ähnlich wie Nintendos Super Game Boy Add-on für das SNES. Eine Vollfarb-TV-Verbindung war ebenfalls in Arbeit, aber da der Supervision keinen großen Eindruck bei den Spielern hinterließ, wurde er zusammen mit den Spielen, die für ihn entwickelt wurden, eingestellt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Watara Supervision, également connue sous le nom de QuickShot Supervision au Royaume-Uni, est une console de jeu portable monochrome originaire d'Asie, lancée en 1992 pour concurrencer le Game Boy de Nintendo. Elle était livrée avec un jeu appelé Crystball, similaire à Breakout. L'une des caractéristiques uniques du Supervision était qu'il pouvait être relié à un téléviseur par un câble de liaison. Les jeux joués de cette manière s'affichaient en quatre couleurs, un peu comme le Super Game Boy de Nintendo pour la SNES. Une liaison TV en couleur était également en préparation, mais le Supervision n'ayant pas fait grande impression auprès des joueurs, elle a été annulée, de même que les jeux qui étaient en cours de développement pour lui.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Watara Supervision, noto anche come QuickShot Supervision nel Regno Unito, è una console portatile monocromatica di origine asiatica, introdotta nel 1992 come concorrente a prezzo ridotto del Game Boy di Nintendo. Veniva fornita con un gioco chiamato Crystball, simile a Breakout. Una caratteristica unica del Supervision era la possibilità di collegarlo a un televisore tramite un cavo di collegamento. I giochi giocati in questo modo venivano visualizzati in quattro colori, proprio come il Super Game Boy add-on di Nintendo per il SNES. Era in progetto anche un collegamento televisivo a colori, ma a causa dell'insuccesso del Supervision tra i giocatori fu cancellato, insieme ai giochi che erano in fase di sviluppo per esso.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Watara Supervision – console portátil de videogame produzida pela empresa Watara e lançada na Ásia em 1992. Seu objetivo era ser uma alternativa mais barata ao Game Boy.

Apesar do preço inferior, a console tinha um visor de qualidade inferior ao do Game Boy e uma pequena biblioteca de jogos, sendo a maioria clones de sucessos conhecidos. O hardware foi lançado com diversas marcas, como QuickShot (Reino Unido), Electrolab (Argentina), Tiger Boy (Taiwan) e Sherion (Polônia). A console era vendida junto com o jogo Crystball, um clone de Breakout.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
