<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2004</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Super Mario War</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Super Mario War is an open-source, platform-adventure video game and level editor first released in 2004. It is based upon gameplay elements and audiovisual media that are unofficially cloned from Nintendo's Super Mario series.

The game centers on players fighting each other by one player jumping on the other player's head, or by making use of items, which can be picked up during gameplay.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Super Mario War to opensource'owa platformowa gra przygodowa i edytor poziomów, wydana po raz pierwszy w 2004 roku. Opiera się na elementach rozgrywki i materiałach audiowizualnych, które zostały nieoficjalnie sklonowane z serii Super Mario firmy Nintendo.

W grze gracze walczą ze sobą, skacząc na głowę drugiego gracza lub używając przedmiotów, które można zbierać podczas rozgrywki.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игра с открытым исходным кодом, основана на материалах, которые неофициально клонированы из серии игр Nintendo Super Mario.

Мультиплеерный одноэкранный платформер на четверых игроков с множеством режимов, редактором уровней и ботами.

Способ устранения наших врагов будет тот же самый, как и во всех играх Mario , то есть, прыжки на голову, а в конце каждого уровня должен остаться только один персонаж.</text>
			<text lang="es">Super Mario War es un videojuego de aventuras y plataformas de código abierto y un editor de niveles publicado por primera vez en 2004. Se basa en elementos de juego y medios audiovisuales clonados extraoficialmente de la serie Super Mario de Nintendo.

El juego se centra en la lucha entre jugadores, saltando uno sobre la cabeza del otro o utilizando objetos que se pueden recoger durante el juego.</text>
			<text lang="de">Super Mario War ist ein Open-Source-Plattform-Adventure-Videospiel und ein Level-Editor, der erstmals 2004 veröffentlicht wurde. Es basiert auf Gameplay-Elementen und audiovisuellen Medien, die inoffiziell von Nintendos Super-Mario-Serie geklont wurden.

Im Mittelpunkt des Spiels steht der Kampf der Spieler gegeneinander, indem ein Spieler auf den Kopf des anderen Spielers springt oder Gegenstände einsetzt, die während des Spiels aufgesammelt werden können.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Super Mario War est un jeu vidéo de plate-forme et d'aventure à code source ouvert, ainsi qu'un éditeur de niveaux, sorti pour la première fois en 2004. Il est basé sur des éléments de gameplay et des médias audiovisuels qui sont officieusement clonés de la série Super Mario de Nintendo.

Les joueurs s'affrontent en sautant sur la tête de l'autre joueur ou en utilisant des objets qui peuvent être ramassés pendant le jeu.</text>
			<text lang="it">Super Mario War è un videogioco open-source di avventura a piattaforme e un editor di livelli pubblicato per la prima volta nel 2004. Si basa su elementi di gioco e supporti audiovisivi clonati non ufficialmente dalla serie Super Mario di Nintendo.

Il gioco prevede che i giocatori si affrontino saltando sulla testa dell'altro giocatore o utilizzando gli oggetti che possono essere raccolti durante il gioco.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
