<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.36</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.45 0.49</origin>
			<pos>0.4815 0.402</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2015 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.36</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.45 0.49</origin>
			<pos>0.4815 0.402</pos>
			<maxSize>0.215</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2015 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Starpath</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Starpath Supercharger</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Starpath Supercharger (originally called the Arcadia Supercharger) is an expansion peripheral cartridge created by Starpath, for playing cassette-based proprietary games on the Atari 2600 video game console.

The device consists of a long cartridge with a handle on the end, and an audio cassette cable. It adds 6 KB to the Atari 2600's 128 bytes of RAM (increasing it 49-fold to 6,272 bytes of RAM), allowing for the creation of specially compatible games which are larger and have higher resolution graphics than normal cartridges.
A cable coming out of the side of the cartridge plugs into the earphone jack of any standard cassette player, for loading all Supercharger games from standard audio cassettes.</text>
			<text lang="it">Lo Starpath Supercharger (originariamente chiamato Arcadia Supercharger) è una cartuccia periferica di espansione creata da Starpath, per la riproduzione di giochi proprietari basati su cassette sulla console per videogiochi Atari 2600.

La periferica consiste in una lunga cartuccia con una maniglia all'estremità e un cavo per cassette audio. Aggiunge 6 KB ai 128 byte di RAM dell'Atari 2600 (aumentandoli di 49 volte fino a 6.272 byte di RAM), consentendo la creazione di giochi appositamente compatibili, più grandi e con grafica a risoluzione più elevata rispetto alle normali cartucce.
Un cavo che fuoriesce dal lato della cartuccia si inserisce nella presa auricolare di qualsiasi lettore di cassette standard, per caricare tutti i giochi Supercharger da cassette audio standard.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Starpath Supercharger (initialement appelé Arcadia Supercharger) est une cartouche périphérique d'extension créée par Starpath, pour jouer à des jeux propriétaires sur cassette sur la console de jeux vidéo Atari 2600.

Le périphérique se compose d'une longue cartouche avec une poignée à l'extrémité et d'un câble pour cassette audio. Il ajoute 6 Ko aux 128 octets de RAM de l'Atari 2600 (ce qui multiplie par 49 le nombre d'octets de RAM pour atteindre 6 272 octets), ce qui permet de créer des jeux spécialement compatibles qui sont plus grands et ont une résolution graphique plus élevée que les cartouches normales.
Un câble sortant sur le côté de la cartouche se branche sur la prise écouteur de n'importe quel lecteur de cassettes standard, pour charger tous les jeux Supercharger à partir de cassettes audio standard.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Starpath Supercharger (ursprünglich Arcadia Supercharger genannt) ist ein von Starpath entwickeltes Erweiterungsmodul für proprietäre Spiele auf Kassettenbasis für die Videospielkonsole Atari 2600.

Das Gerät besteht aus einer langen Kassette mit einem Griff am Ende und einem Audiokassettenkabel. Es erweitert den 128 Byte großen Arbeitsspeicher des Atari 2600 um 6 KB (und erhöht ihn damit um das 49-fache auf 6.272 Byte RAM), was die Erstellung von speziell kompatiblen Spielen ermöglicht, die größer sind und eine höhere Grafikauflösung haben als normale Kassetten.
Ein Kabel, das an der Seite der Kassette herauskommt, kann in die Kopfhörerbuchse eines normalen Kassettenspielers eingesteckt werden, um alle Supercharger-Spiele von normalen Audiokassetten zu laden.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Starpath Supercharger (originalmente llamado Arcadia Supercharger) es un cartucho periférico de expansión creado por Starpath, para jugar a juegos propietarios basados en casetes en la consola de videojuegos Atari 2600.

El dispositivo consiste en un cartucho largo con un asa en el extremo y un cable de casete de audio. Añade 6 KB a los 128 bytes de RAM de la Atari 2600 (multiplicándolos por 49 hasta alcanzar los 6.272 bytes de RAM), lo que permite crear juegos especialmente compatibles que son más grandes y tienen gráficos de mayor resolución que los cartuchos normales.
Un cable que sale del lateral del cartucho se conecta a la toma de auriculares de cualquier reproductor de casetes estándar, para cargar todos los juegos Supercharger desde casetes de audio estándar.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Starpath Supercharger (первоначальное название Arcadia Supercharger) - периферийный картридж расширения, созданный компанией Starpath для воспроизведения кассетных игр на видеоигровой консоли Atari 2600.

Устройство состоит из длинного картриджа с ручкой на конце и кабеля для аудиокассет. Он добавляет 6 КБ к 128 байтам оперативной памяти Atari 2600 (увеличивая ее в 49 раз до 6272 байт), что позволяет создавать специально совместимые игры, которые имеют больший размер и более высокое разрешение графики, чем обычные картриджи.
Кабель, выходящий из боковой части картриджа, подключается к разъему для наушников любого стандартного кассетного плеера, что позволяет загружать все игры Supercharger со стандартных аудиокассет.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Starpath Supercharger (pierwotnie nazywany Arcadia Supercharger) to rozszerzenie kartridża peryferyjnego stworzone przez firmę Starpath, służące do odtwarzania zastrzeżonych gier opartych na kasetach na konsoli do gier wideo Atari 2600.

Urządzenie składa się z długiego kartridża z uchwytem na końcu i kabla kasety audio. Dodaje 6 KB do 128 bajtów pamięci RAM Atari 2600 (zwiększając ją 49-krotnie do 6272 bajtów pamięci RAM), umożliwiając tworzenie specjalnie kompatybilnych gier, które są większe i mają grafikę o wyższej rozdzielczości niż zwykłe kartridże.
Kabel wychodzący z boku kartridża podłącza się do gniazda słuchawkowego dowolnego standardowego odtwarzacza kasetowego, umożliwiając ładowanie wszystkich gier Supercharger ze standardowych kaset audio.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Starpath Supercharger (originalmente chamado de Arcadia Supercharger) é uma expansão de cartucho periférico criada pela Starpath, usada para jogar jogos proprietários baseados em fitas na consola de videojogos Atari 2600.

O dispositivo consiste num cartucho comprido com uma pega na extremidade e um cabo de cassete de áudio. Ele adiciona 6 KB aos 128 bytes de RAM do Atari 2600 (aumentando-a 49 vezes para 6272 bytes de RAM), permitindo a criação de jogos especificamente compatíveis, que são maiores e têm gráficos de maior resolução do que os cartuchos normais.
O cabo que sai do lado do cartucho conecta-se à tomada de auscultadores de qualquer gravador de cassetes padrão, permitindo o carregamento de todos os jogos Supercharger a partir de cassetes de áudio padrão.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>