<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.25</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.385</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.385" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1995</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Funtech Entertainment</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Super A'Can</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Super A'Can is a home video game console released exclusively in Taiwan in 1995 by Funtech/Dunhuang Technology.
It is based around the Motorola 68000 microchip, which is also used in the Sega Genesis and Neo Geo. Twelve games have been confirmed to exist for the system.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Super A'Can to domowa konsola do gier wideo wydana wyłącznie na Tajwanie w 1995 roku przez firmę Funtech/Dunhuang Technology. Opiera się na mikroprocesorze Motorola 68000, który jest również używany w konsolach Sega Genesis i Neo Geo. Potwierdzono istnienie dwunastu gier na ten system.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Домашняя игровая приставка, выпущенная исключительно на Тайване в 1995 году компанией Funtech/Dunhuang Technology. Она основана на микрочипе Motorola 68000, который также используется в Sega Genesis и Neo Geo. Было подтверждено существование двенадцати игр для системы.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Super A'Can es una videoconsola doméstica lanzada exclusivamente en Taiwán en 1995 por Funtech/Dunhuang Technology.
Está basada en el microchip Motorola 68000, que también se utiliza en la Sega Genesis y la Neo Geo. Se ha confirmado la existencia de doce juegos para este sistema.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Super A'Can ist eine Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch, die 1995 von Funtech/Dunhuang Technology exklusiv in Taiwan veröffentlicht wurde.
Sie basiert auf dem Motorola 68000 Mikrochip, der auch im Sega Genesis und Neo Geo verwendet wird. Zwölf Spiele wurden für das System bestätigt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Super A'Can est une console de jeu vidéo de salon commercialisée exclusivement à Taiwan en 1995 par Funtech/Dunhuang Technology.
Elle est basée sur la puce Motorola 68000, également utilisée dans la Sega Genesis et la Neo Geo. Douze jeux ont été confirmés pour ce système.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Super A'Can è una console per videogiochi domestica rilasciata esclusivamente a Taiwan nel 1995 da Funtech/Dunhuang Technology.
È basata sul microchip Motorola 68000, utilizzato anche nel Sega Genesis e nel Neo Geo. È stata confermata l'esistenza di dodici giochi per il sistema.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Super A'Can é um console doméstico de videogame lançado exclusivamente em Taiwan em 1995 pela Funtech/Dunhuang Technology. É baseado no microprocessador Motorola 68000, que também é usado nos consoles Sega Genesis e Neo Geo. A existência de doze jogos para este sistema foi confirmada.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
