<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.33</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.44</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.395</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.395" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/pce-cd.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/pce-cd.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.33</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.44</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.395</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.395" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1992</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Nec</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>TurboDuo</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The NEC TurboDuo, released in 1992, was an innovative video game console that combined the capabilities of the TurboGrafx-16 and its CD-ROM add-on, the TurboGrafx-CD, into a single, sleek unit. This console was developed through a collaboration between NEC and Hudson Soft and was known for its ability to play both HuCard cartridges and CD-ROM² discs, offering a wide range of games that utilized the enhanced storage and multimedia capabilities of CDs.

The TurboDuo was the North American version of Japan's PC Engine Duo and featured an upgraded BIOS and additional RAM (192 KB), which enabled compatibility with a broader range of games, including the new Super CD-ROM² titles.
Despite its technical strengths and a lineup of quality games, the TurboDuo struggled to gain significant market share in North America due to poor marketing and competition from more established brands like Sega and Nintendo. However, it remains a beloved system among retro gaming enthusiasts for its unique library and the nostalgic value it holds.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il TurboDuo di NEC, uscito nel 1992, era un'innovativa console per videogiochi che combinava le capacità del TurboGrafx-16 e del suo componente aggiuntivo CD-ROM, il TurboGrafx-CD, in un'unica ed elegante unità. Questa console, sviluppata grazie alla collaborazione tra NEC e Hudson Soft, era nota per la sua capacità di riprodurre sia cartucce HuCard che dischi CD-ROM², offrendo un'ampia gamma di giochi che sfruttavano le migliori capacità di memorizzazione e multimediali dei CD.

Il TurboDuo era la versione nordamericana del PC Engine Duo giapponese ed era dotato di un BIOS aggiornato e di una RAM aggiuntiva (192 KB), che consentiva la compatibilità con una gamma più ampia di giochi, compresi i nuovi titoli Super CD-ROM².
Nonostante i suoi punti di forza tecnici e una serie di giochi di qualità, il TurboDuo ha faticato a conquistare quote di mercato significative in Nord America a causa di un marketing scadente e della concorrenza di marchi più affermati come Sega e Nintendo. Tuttavia, rimane una console molto amata dagli appassionati di giochi retro per la sua libreria unica e per il valore nostalgico che possiede.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le NEC TurboDuo, sorti en 1992, était une console de jeux vidéo innovante qui combinait les capacités du TurboGrafx-16 et de son complément CD-ROM, le TurboGrafx-CD, en une seule unité élégante. Cette console a été développée dans le cadre d'une collaboration entre NEC et Hudson Soft et était connue pour sa capacité à lire à la fois les cartouches HuCard et les disques CD-ROM², offrant une large gamme de jeux qui utilisaient les capacités de stockage et de multimédia améliorées des CD.
				n BIOS amélioré et d'une mémoire vive supplémentaire (192 Ko), ce qui lui permettait d'être compatible avec un plus grand nombre de jeux, y compris les nouveaux titres Super CD-ROM².
Malgré ses atouts techniques et une gamme de jeux de qualité, la TurboDuo a eu du mal à gagner des parts de marché significatives en Amérique du Nord en raison d'un marketing médiocre et de la concurrence de marques plus établies comme Sega et Nintendo. Cependant, elle reste une console très appréciée des amateurs de jeux rétro pour sa bibliothèque unique et la valeur nostalgique qu'elle représente.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der NEC TurboDuo, der 1992 auf den Markt kam, war eine innovative Videospielkonsole, die die Fähigkeiten des TurboGrafx-16 und seiner CD-ROM-Erweiterung, dem TurboGrafx-CD, in einem einzigen, schlanken Gerät vereinte. Diese Konsole wurde in Zusammenarbeit zwischen NEC und Hudson Soft entwickelt und war dafür bekannt, dass sie sowohl HuCard-Cartridges als auch CD-ROM²-Discs abspielen konnte und eine breite Palette von Spielen bot, die die erweiterten Speicher- und Multimedia-Fähigkeiten von CDs nutzten.

Der TurboDuo war die nordamerikanische Version des japanischen PC Engine Duo und verfügte über ein verbessertes BIOS und zusätzlichen Arbeitsspeicher (192 KB), der die Kompatibilität mit einer breiteren Palette von Spielen ermöglichte, einschließlich der neuen Super CD-ROM²-Titel.
Trotz seiner technischen Stärken und einer Reihe von Qualitätsspielen hatte das TurboDuo aufgrund von schlechtem Marketing und der Konkurrenz etablierterer Marken wie Sega und Nintendo Mühe, in Nordamerika einen bedeutenden Marktanteil zu gewinnen. Dennoch bleibt es ein beliebtes System unter Retro-Gaming-Enthusiasten für seine einzigartige Bibliothek und den nostalgischen Wert, den es besitzt.</text>
			<text lang="es">La NEC TurboDuo, lanzada en 1992, fue una innovadora consola de videojuegos que combinaba las capacidades de la TurboGrafx-16 y su complemento CD-ROM, la TurboGrafx-CD, en una única y elegante unidad. Esta consola se desarrolló gracias a la colaboración entre NEC y Hudson Soft y era conocida por su capacidad para reproducir tanto cartuchos HuCard como discos CD-ROM², ofreciendo una amplia gama de juegos que utilizaban las capacidades mejoradas de almacenamiento y multimedia de los CD.

El TurboDuo era la versión norteamericana del PC Engine Duo japonés y contaba con una BIOS mejorada y RAM adicional (192 KB), lo que permitía la compatibilidad con una gama más amplia de juegos, incluidos los nuevos títulos de Super CD-ROM².
A pesar de sus virtudes técnicas y de una gama de juegos de calidad, la TurboDuo tuvo dificultades para hacerse con una cuota de mercado significativa en Norteamérica debido a un marketing deficiente y a la competencia de marcas más consolidadas como Sega y Nintendo. Sin embargo, sigue siendo un sistema muy querido entre los entusiastas de los juegos retro por su biblioteca única y el valor nostálgico que tiene.</text>
			<text lang="ru">NEC TurboDuo, выпущенная в 1992 году, была инновационной игровой приставкой, объединившей возможности TurboGrafx-16 и ее дополнения CD-ROM, TurboGrafx-CD, в одном элегантном устройстве. Эта консоль была разработана в сотрудничестве между NEC и Hudson Soft и была известна своей способностью воспроизводить как картриджи HuCard, так и диски CD-ROM², предлагая широкий спектр игр, которые использовали расширенные возможности хранения и мультимедиа компакт-дисков.

TurboDuo был североамериканской версией японского PC Engine Duo и отличался обновленным BIOS и дополнительной оперативной памятью (192 КБ), что обеспечивало совместимость с более широким спектром игр, включая новые игры для Super CD-ROM².
Несмотря на свои технические преимущества и линейку качественных игр, TurboDuo не смогла завоевать значительную долю рынка в Северной Америке из-за плохого маркетинга и конкуренции со стороны более известных брендов, таких как Sega и Nintendo. Тем не менее, эта система остается любимой среди любителей ретро-игр благодаря своей уникальной библиотеке и ностальгической ценности.</text>
			<text lang="pl">NEC TurboDuo, wydana w 1992 roku, była innowacyjną konsolą do gier wideo, która łączyła możliwości TurboGrafx-16 i jego dodatku CD-ROM, TurboGrafx-CD, w jednym, eleganckim urządzeniu. Konsola ta została opracowana we współpracy firm NEC i Hudson Soft i była znana ze swojej zdolności do odtwarzania zarówno kartridży HuCard, jak i dysków CD-ROM², oferując szeroką gamę gier, które wykorzystywały ulepszoną pamięć masową i możliwości multimedialne płyt CD.

TurboDuo był północnoamerykańską wersją japońskiego PC Engine Duo i posiadał ulepszony BIOS i dodatkową pamięć RAM (192 KB), co umożliwiło kompatybilność z szerszą gamą gier, w tym z nowymi tytułami Super CD-ROM².
Pomimo swoich mocnych stron technicznych i linii wysokiej jakości gier, TurboDuo walczył o zdobycie znaczącego udziału w rynku w Ameryce Północnej z powodu słabego marketingu i konkurencji ze strony bardziej uznanych marek, takich jak Sega i Nintendo. Pozostaje jednak ukochanym systemem wśród entuzjastów gier retro ze względu na swoją unikalną bibliotekę i nostalgiczną wartość.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>