<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/pcengine.png</path>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/pcengine.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.50 0.395</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.395" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1989</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>TurboGrafx-16 / PC Engine</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.35</pos>
			<text>The TurboGrafx-16, known as the PC Engine in Japan and France, is a 16-bit fourth-generation home video game console designed by Hudson Soft and sold by NEC Home Electronics. It was released in Japan in 1987 and in North America in 1989. The Japanese model was imported and distributed in France in 1989, and the United Kingdom and Spain received a version based on the American model known as simply TurboGrafx. It was the first console released in the 16-bit era, although it used a modified 8-bit CPU. In Japan, the system was launched as a competitor to the Famicom, but the delayed United States release meant that it ended up competing with the Sega Genesis and later the Super Nintendo Entertainment System.

The TurboGrafx-16 has an 8-bit CPU, a 16-bit video color encoder, and a 16-bit video display controller. The GPUs are capable of displaying 482 colors simultaneously, out of 512. With dimensions of just 14 cm × 14 cm × 3.8 cm (5.5 in × 5.5 in × 1.5 in), the Japanese PC Engine is the smallest major home game console ever made. Games were released on HuCard cartridges and later the CD-ROM optical format with the TurboGrafx-CD add-on.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">La PC-Engine (PCエンジン, Piishii Enjin), connue sous le nom TurboGrafx-16 en Amérique du Nord, est une console de jeux vidéo 8 bits fabriquée par NEC et commercialisée à partir de 1987 au Japon. En dehors de son pays natal et du territoire nord-américain, la gamme de consoles a connu une existence relativement confidentielle, car peu ou pas distribuée.

En avance sur son temps, la PC-Engine possède un processeur central 8 bits et un processeur graphique 16 bits, ainsi elle est considérée comme une console de quatrième génération. Conçue pour être modulaire et évolutive, c'est aussi la première console de jeux de l'histoire à utiliser dès décembre 1988, le support des CD-ROMs, grâce à un lecteur en option. Après le premier modèle d'origine, elle fut déclinée dans de nombreuses versions pour finir par accepter quatre formats de jeux différents : HuCard, CD-ROM², Super CD-ROM² et Arcade CD-ROM².</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">8-16 разрядная игровая приставка, выпущенная NEC в Японии 30 октября 1987 года, в Северной Америке в конце августа 1989 года под именем TurboGrafx-16. В регионе PAL приставка не продавалась, если не считать релиза в 1990 году в Великобритании. Эта версия называлась TurboGrafx и была выпущена в очень ограниченном количестве. Неофициально эта версия продавалась во Франции и Бенилюксе.

PC Engine была 8-разрядной приставкой с двойным 16-разрядным графическим процессором, с возможностью отображения 482 цветов одновременно.

PC Engine по тем временам была системой нового поколения. Носителем был картридж в формате HuCard. Компания NEC первая стала выпускать игры на компакт-дисках, в которые можно было играть, используя дополнительное устройство — Turbografx CD.

Небольшие размеры PC Engine — всего 14 см x 14 см x 3.8 см (5.5 дюймов x 5.5 дюймов x 1.5 дюйма) — позволили ей стать рекордсменом в звании самой маленькой игровой приставки из когда-либо созданных, по версии книги рекордов Гиннесса в области компьютерных игр (англ. Guinness World Records Gamer’s Edition, 2008).

В 2009 году PC Engine была помещена на тринадцатое место в списке «25 игровых приставок всех времён» по версии сайта IGN.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>