<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.498 0.47</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.218 0.47" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.42</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.498 0.47</pos>
			<maxSize>0.2</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.218 0.47" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1978</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Tiger Electronics</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Handheld games</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Tiger is most well known for their low-end handheld electronic game systems with LCD screens. Each unit contains a fixed image printed onto the handheld that can be seen through the screen. Static images then light up individually in front of the background that represent characters and objects, similar to numbers on a calculator or digital clock.

In addition to putting out some of its own games, Tiger was able to secure licenses from many of the time's top selling companies to sell their own versions of games such as Capcom's Street Fighter II, Sega's Sonic 3D Blast, and Konami's Castlevania II: Simon's Quest. Later, Tiger introduced what they called "wrist games". These combined a digital watch with a scaled-down version of a Tiger handheld game.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Tiger jest najbardziej znany ze swoich niskopółkowych, ręcznych systemów gier elektronicznych z ekranami LCD. Każde urządzenie zawiera stały obraz wydrukowany na ekranie, przez który można obserwować to, co dzieje się na ekranie. Statyczne obrazy podświetlają się indywidualnie przed tłem, które reprezentują postacie i obiekty, podobnie jak liczby na kalkulatorze lub zegarze cyfrowym.

Oprócz wydawania własnych gier, Tiger był w stanie zabezpieczyć licencje od wielu najlepiej sprzedających się firm w tamtym czasie, aby sprzedawać własne wersje gier, takich jak Street Fighter II firmy Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast firmy Sega i Castlevania II: Simon's Quest firmy Konami. Później Tiger wprowadził coś, co nazwał "grami na rękę". Łączyły one zegarek cyfrowy na rękę z pomniejszoną wersją gry firmy Tiger.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Компания Tiger наиболее известна своими портативными электронными игровыми системами низкого класса с ЖК-экранами. Каждое устройство содержит неподвижное изображение, напечатанное на портативном устройстве, которое можно увидеть через экран. Затем на фоне экрана загораются статические изображения, которые представляют собой символы и объекты, похожие на цифры на калькуляторе или цифровых часах.

Помимо выпуска некоторых собственных игр, Tiger удалось получить лицензии от многих самых продаваемых компаний того времени на продажу собственных версий игр, таких как Street Fighter II от Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast от Sega и Castlevania II: Simon's Quest от Konami. Позже компания Tiger представила так называемые "наручные игры". Они объединяли цифровые часы с уменьшенной версией портативной игры Tiger.</text>
			<text lang="es">Tiger es más conocida por sus sistemas de juegos electrónicos portátiles de gama baja con pantallas LCD. Cada unidad contiene una imagen fija impresa en el dispositivo portátil que puede verse a través de la pantalla. Las imágenes estáticas se iluminan individualmente delante del fondo y representan personajes y objetos, como los números de una calculadora o un reloj digital.

Además de sacar algunos de sus propios juegos, Tiger consiguió licencias de muchas de las empresas más vendidas de la época para vender sus propias versiones de juegos como Street Fighter II de Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast de Sega y Castlevania II: Simon's Quest de Konami. Más tarde, Tiger introdujo lo que llamaron "juegos de muñeca". Combinaban un reloj digital con una versión reducida de un juego de mano de Tiger.</text>
			<text lang="de">Tiger ist vor allem für seine elektronischen Handheld-Spielsysteme mit LCD-Bildschirmen im unteren Preissegment bekannt. Jedes Gerät enthält ein festes, auf das Handheld gedrucktes Bild, das durch den Bildschirm hindurch gesehen werden kann. Statische Bilder leuchten dann einzeln vor dem Hintergrund auf, die Zeichen und Objekte darstellen, ähnlich wie die Zahlen auf einem Taschenrechner oder einer Digitaluhr.

Tiger brachte nicht nur eigene Spiele auf den Markt, sondern sicherte sich auch Lizenzen von vielen der damals meistverkauften Unternehmen, um ihre eigenen Versionen von Spielen wie Street Fighter II von Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast von Sega und Castlevania II: Simon's Quest von Konami zu verkaufen. Später führte Tiger die so genannten "Handgelenkspiele" ein. Diese kombinierten eine Digitaluhr mit einer verkleinerten Version eines Tiger-Handheld-Spiels.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Tiger est surtout connu pour ses systèmes de jeux électroniques portables bas de gamme dotés d'écrans LCD. Chaque unité contient une image fixe imprimée sur l'ordinateur de poche qui peut être vue à travers l'écran. Des images statiques s'allument ensuite individuellement devant l'arrière-plan pour représenter des personnages et des objets, comme les chiffres d'une calculatrice ou d'une horloge numérique.

En plus de produire ses propres jeux, Tiger a pu obtenir des licences de la part de nombreuses sociétés les plus vendues à l'époque pour vendre leurs propres versions de jeux tels que Street Fighter II de Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast de Sega et Castlevania II : Simon's Quest de Konami. Plus tard, Tiger a introduit ce qu'il a appelé les "jeux de poignet". Ceux-ci combinaient une montre numérique avec une version réduite d'un jeu portable de Tiger.</text>
			<text lang="it">Tiger è nota soprattutto per i suoi dispositivi portatili di fascia bassa con schermo LCD. Ogni unità contiene un'immagine fissa stampata sul dispositivo portatile che può essere vista attraverso lo schermo. Le immagini statiche si illuminano singolarmente davanti allo sfondo e rappresentano personaggi e oggetti, simili ai numeri di una calcolatrice o di un orologio digitale.

Oltre a produrre alcuni dei propri giochi, Tiger fu in grado di ottenere licenze da molte delle aziende più vendute dell'epoca per vendere le proprie versioni di giochi come Street Fighter II di Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast di Sega e Castlevania II: Simon's Quest di Konami. In seguito, Tiger introdusse i cosiddetti "giochi da polso". Questi combinavano un orologio digitale con una versione ridotta di un dispositivo portatile Tiger.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Tiger é mais conhecido por seus sistemas de jogos eletrônicos de baixo custo, manuais, com telas LCD. Cada dispositivo possui uma imagem estática impressa na tela, através da qual você pode observar o que acontece na tela. As imagens estáticas são retroiluminadas individualmente contra um fundo que representa personagens e objetos, de forma semelhante aos números em uma calculadora ou um relógio digital.

Além de lançar seus próprios jogos, a Tiger conseguiu obter licenças de várias das empresas de maior sucesso da época para vender suas próprias versões de jogos, como Street Fighter II da Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast da Sega e Castlevania II: Simon's Quest da Konami. Mais tarde, a Tiger introduziu algo que chamou de "jogos de mão". Eles combinavam um relógio digital de pulso com uma versão reduzida de um jogo da Tiger.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
