<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme defaultView="Icons">
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text/>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Epic MegaGames</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Tyrian</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Tyrian is a vertically scrolling shooter developed by Eclipse Software for MS-DOS and published in 1995 by Epic MegaGames. Tyrian was programmed by Jason Emery, illustrated by Daniel Cook, and its music composed by Alexander Brandon and Andras Molnar.

The game was re-released as freeware in 2004. A free and open-source port of the game started in April 2007.</text>
			<text lang="it">Tyrian è uno sparatutto a scorrimento verticale sviluppato da Eclipse Software per MS-DOS e pubblicato nel 1995 da Epic MegaGames. Tyrian è stato programmato da Jason Emery, illustrato da Daniel Cook e la sua musica è stata composta da Alexander Brandon e Andras Molnar.

Il gioco è stato ripubblicato come freeware nel 2004. Un porting gratuito e open-source del gioco è stato avviato nell'aprile 2007.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Tyrian est un jeu de tir à défilement vertical développé par Eclipse Software pour MS-DOS et publié en 1995 par Epic MegaGames. Tyrian a été programmé par Jason Emery, illustré par Daniel Cook, et sa musique a été composée par Alexander Brandon et Andras Molnar.

Le jeu a été réédité en tant que freeware en 2004. Un portage libre et gratuit du jeu a été lancé en avril 2007.</text>
			<text lang="de">Tyrian ist ein vertikal scrollender Shooter, der von Eclipse Software für MS-DOS entwickelt und 1995 von Epic MegaGames veröffentlicht wurde. Tyrian wurde von Jason Emery programmiert, von Daniel Cook illustriert, und die Musik wurde von Alexander Brandon und Andras Molnar komponiert.

Das Spiel wurde 2004 als Freeware wiederveröffentlicht. Eine freie und quelloffene Portierung des Spiels begann im April 2007.</text>
			<text lang="es">Tyrian es un shooter de desplazamiento vertical desarrollado por Eclipse Software para MS-DOS y publicado en 1995 por Epic MegaGames. Tyrian fue programado por Jason Emery, ilustrado por Daniel Cook, y su música compuesta por Alexander Brandon y Andras Molnar.

El juego se reeditó como freeware en 2004. En abril de 2007 se inició un port libre y de código abierto del juego.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Tyrian - это вертикально-прокручивающийся шутер, разработанный Eclipse Software для MS-DOS и изданный в 1995 году Epic MegaGames. Tyrian была запрограммирована Джейсоном Эмери, проиллюстрирована Дэниелом Куком, а музыка написана Александром Брэндоном и Андрашем Молнаром.

В 2004 году игра была переиздана в виде бесплатного программного обеспечения. В апреле 2007 года был запущен бесплатный порт игры с открытым исходным кодом.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Tyrian to przewijana w pionie strzelanka opracowana przez Eclipse Software dla MS-DOS i wydana w 1995 roku przez Epic MegaGames. Tyrian został zaprogramowany przez Jasona Emery'ego, zilustrowany przez Daniela Cooka, a muzykę skomponowali Alexander Brandon i Andras Molnar.

Gra została ponownie wydana jako freeware w 2004 roku. Wolny i open-source'owy port gry został wydany w kwietniu 2007 roku.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Tyrian é um jogo de tiro com rolagem vertical desenvolvido pela Eclipse Software para MS-DOS e lançado em 1995 pela Epic MegaGames. Tyrian foi programado por Jason Emery, ilustrado por Daniel Cook, e a música foi composta por Alexander Brandon e Andras Molnar.

O jogo foi relançado como freeware em 2004. Uma versão gratuita e de código aberto do jogo foi lançada em abril de 2007.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>