<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.36</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.45 0.49</origin>
			<pos>0.4815 0.402</pos>
			<maxSize>0.215</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2015 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.36</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.45 0.49</origin>
			<pos>0.4815 0.402</pos>
			<maxSize>0.215</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2015 0.402" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1978</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Interton</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>VC 4000</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Interton Video Computer 4000 (officially abbreviated as Interton VC 4000) is an early 8-bit ROM cartridge-based second-generation home video game console that was released in Germany, England, France, Spain, Austria, the Netherlands and Australia in 1978 by German hearing aid manufacturer Interton. The console is the successor of the Interton Video 3001 and was sold for 298 Deutsche Mark and discontinued in 1983.

The Interton VC 4000's power comes from a Signetics 2650 CPU (which is the same as an Arcadia 2001) and a Signetics 2636 gaming controller. Both controllers contain a 12-button keypad, two fire buttons, and a joystick. Inside the systems control panel, there are four different buttons. The ON/OFF switch, RESET, SELECT, and START.

The console was produced by different companies and sold with different names. Not every console is compatible with others due to differences in the shapes and dimensions of the cartridge slots, but all of the systems are software compatible.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Interton Video Computer 4000 (w oficjalnym skrócie Interton VC 4000) to wczesna 8-bitowa, oparta na kasetach ROM domowa konsola do gier wideo drugiej generacji, która została wydana w Niemczech, Anglii, Francji, Hiszpanii, Austrii, Holandii i Australii w 1978 roku przez niemieckiego producenta aparatów słuchowych Interton. Konsola jest następcą Interton Video 3001 i była sprzedawana za 298 marek niemieckich, a jej produkcja została zakończona w 1983 roku.

Moc Interton VC 4000 pochodzi z procesora Signetics 2650 (który jest taki sam jak w Arcadia 2001) oraz kontrolera gier Signetics 2636. Oba kontrolery zawierają 12-przyciskową klawiaturę, dwa przyciski fire oraz joystick. Wewnątrz panelu sterowania systemu znajdują się cztery różne przyciski. Włącznik/wyłącznik, RESET, SELECT i START.

Konsola była produkowana przez różne firmy i sprzedawana pod różnymi nazwami. Nie każda konsola jest kompatybilna z innymi ze względu na różnice w kształcie i wymiarach gniazd kartridży, ale wszystkie systemy są kompatybilne z oprogramowaniem.</text>
			<text lang="ru">8-битная игровая приставка второго поколения, выпущенная немецкой компанией Interton в 1978 году по цене около 300 DM. Является единственной консолью, разработанной и выпущенной полностью в Германии.

VC 4000 была разработана ещё в 1974 году, однако выпущена лишь 4 годами позже. До неё Interton в середине 1970-х выпустил несколько лицензионных Понг-приставок, вроде Atari Pong — например, Interton 3001. За пределами Германии популярности не имела. Выпуск приставки остановился в 1983 году.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Interton Video Computer 4000 (abreviada oficialmente como Interton VC 4000) es una consola de videojuegos doméstica de segunda generación basada en cartuchos ROM de 8 bits que fue lanzada en Alemania, Inglaterra, Francia, España, Austria, Países Bajos y Australia en 1978 por el fabricante alemán de audífonos Interton. La consola es la sucesora de la Interton Video 3001, se vendió por 298 marcos alemanes y se dejó de fabricar en 1983.

La potencia de la Interton VC 4000 proviene de una CPU Signetics 2650 (que es la misma que la de la Arcadia 2001) y un mando de juegos Signetics 2636. Ambos controladores contienen un teclado de 12 botones, dos botones de disparo y un joystick. Dentro del panel de control del sistema, hay cuatro botones diferentes. El interruptor ON/OFF, RESET, SELECT y START.

La consola fue producida por diferentes compañías y vendida con diferentes nombres. No todas las consolas son compatibles entre sí debido a las diferencias en las formas y dimensiones de las ranuras de los cartuchos, pero todos los sistemas son compatibles con el software.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Interton Video Computer 4000 (offiziell abgekürzt als Interton VC 4000) ist eine frühe 8-Bit-ROM-Cartridge-basierte Heimvideospielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die 1978 vom deutschen Hörgerätehersteller Interton in Deutschland, England, Frankreich, Spanien, Österreich, den Niederlanden und Australien herausgebracht wurde. Die Konsole ist der Nachfolger des Interton Video 3001 und wurde für 298 Deutsche Mark verkauft und 1983 eingestellt.

Die Leistung des Interton VC 4000 stammt von einer Signetics 2650 CPU (die die gleiche ist wie die des Arcadia 2001) und einem Signetics 2636 Gaming Controller. Beide Controller enthalten eine 12-Tasten-Tastatur, zwei Feuertasten und einen Joystick. Im Inneren des Systemsteuerungsfeldes befinden sich vier verschiedene Tasten. Der EIN/AUS-Schalter, RESET, SELECT und START.

Die Konsole wurde von verschiedenen Unternehmen hergestellt und unter verschiedenen Namen verkauft. Nicht jede Konsole ist mit anderen kompatibel, da sich die Formen und Abmessungen der Kassettenschächte unterscheiden.</text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Interton Video Computer 4000 (officiellement abrégé en Interton VC 4000) est une console de jeu vidéo domestique de deuxième génération, basée sur une cartouche ROM 8 bits, qui a été commercialisée en Allemagne, en Angleterre, en France, en Espagne, en Autriche, aux Pays-Bas et en Australie en 1978 par le fabricant allemand d'appareils auditifs Interton. La console est le successeur de l'Interton Video 3001 et a été vendue au prix de 298 Deutsche Mark et abandonnée en 1983.

La puissance de l'Interton VC 4000 provient d'un processeur Signetics 2650 (identique à celui de l'Arcadia 2001) et d'un contrôleur de jeu Signetics 2636. Les deux contrôleurs contiennent un clavier à 12 boutons, deux boutons de tir et un joystick. À l'intérieur du panneau de contrôle du système, il y a quatre boutons différents. L'interrupteur ON/OFF, RESET, SELECT et START.

La console a été produite par différentes sociétés et vendue sous différents noms. Toutes les consoles ne sont pas compatibles entre elles en raison des différences de formes et de dimensions des emplacements des cartouches, mais tous les systèmes sont compatibles sur le plan logiciel.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'Interton Video Computer 4000 (ufficialmente abbreviato in Interton VC 4000) è una console per videogiochi domestica di seconda generazione basata su cartucce ROM a 8 bit, commercializzata in Germania, Inghilterra, Francia, Spagna, Austria, Paesi Bassi e Australia nel 1978 dal produttore tedesco di apparecchi acustici Interton. La console è il successore della Interton Video 3001 ed è stata venduta al prezzo di 298 marchi tedeschi e dismessa nel 1983.

La console Interton VC 4000 è alimentata da una CPU Signetics 2650 (la stessa dell'Arcadia 2001) e da un controller Signetics 2636. Entrambi i controller contengono una tastiera a 12 pulsanti, due pulsanti di fuoco e un joystick. All'interno del pannello di controllo del sistema sono presenti quattro diversi pulsanti. L'interruttore ON/OFF, RESET, SELECT e START.

La console è stata prodotta da diverse aziende e venduta con nomi diversi. Non tutte le console sono compatibili con le altre a causa delle differenze nelle forme e nelle dimensioni degli slot per le cartucce, ma tutti i sistemi sono compatibili con il software.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
