<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.498 0.412</pos>
			<maxSize>0.33</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.218 0.412" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.4</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.498 0.412</pos>
			<maxSize>0.32</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.218 0.412" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Smith Engineering</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Vectrex</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Vectrex is a vector display-based home video game console–the only one ever designed and released for the home market, developed by Smith Engineering. It was first released for the North America market in November 1982 and then Europe and Japan in 1983. Originally manufactured by General Consumer Electronics, it was later licensed to Milton Bradley after they acquired the company. Bandai released the system in Japan.

The Vectrex, in contrast to other video-game systems available at the time, featured an integrated monochrome CRT monitor and did not need to be hooked up to a television set as it provided its own built-in display. A detachable wired control pad was mounted at, and could be folded into, the lower base of the console. Games included translucent color sheet overlays that could be placed over the monochrome screen. A number of peripherals were produced, such as a pair of 3D goggles known as the "3D Imager" and a "light-pen" that allowed the player to draw directly on the screen. A built-in game, Mine Storm, was playable without inserting a cartridge.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Vectrex – ośmiobitowa konsola gier wideo wyprodukowana przez Western Technologies/Smith Engineering, początkowo dystrybuowana na licencji General Consumer Electric, potem przez Milton Bradley Company. Konsola miała premierę w listopadzie 1982, a jej cena wówczas wynosiła 199 USD. Po przejęciu firmy GCE przez Milton Bradley cena została obniżona do 150 dolarów, a przed zapaścią rynku gier wideo w 1983 cena wynosiła 100 dolarów. Vectrex znikł z rynku na początku 1984. W Polsce pojawił się w połowie lat 80. i był przedstawiany w programie Sonda.

W przeciwieństwie do stacjonarnych konsoli, które generowały grafikę rastrową i wyświetlały ją na ekranie telewizora, Vectrex miał zintegrowany monitor wyświetlający grafikę wektorową. Monochromatyczny monitor Vectreksa korzystał z przezroczystych plastikowych nakładek na ekran, ozdabiających pole gry za pomocą statycznych pokolorowanych obszarów. Wówczas wiele z popularnych automatów korzystało z grafiki wektorowej, a GCE zależało, by Vectrex znalazł się właśnie w tej grupie – na konsolę pojawiły się wysokiej jakości porty takich gier jak Space Wars czy Armor Attack.

Vectrex miał wbudowaną grę Minestorm, która była klonem Asteroids. Poza gamepadami, urządzeniami wskazującymi wyprodukowanymi dla konsoli były pióro świetlne i "3D imager", będący rodzajem trójwymiarowych gogli.

Vectrex został wydany w Japonii pod nazwą Bandai Vectrex Kousokusen.

Vectrex razem z Atari 5200 i ColecoVision był jedną z pierwszych konsoli które miały ekran startowy – cechę, która w epoce konsoli bazujących na nośnikach CD stała się standardem.</text>
			<text lang="ru">8-разрядная игровая консоль, разработанная General Consumer Electric (GCE), позже купленная Milton Bradley Company. «Vectrex» уникальна тем, что это единственная игровая система, использующая векторный графический монитор; ни одна другая система ни до, ни после неё, не использовала подобную конфигурацию. «Vectrex» продавалась потребителям с 1982 года по цене в 199 долл.; продажи устройства прекратились в 1984, во время спада на рынке игровых консолей.

В отличие от большинства других игровых консолей, подключаемых к бытовому телевизору для передачи растрового изображения (то есть игровых приставок), «Vectrex» имел свой встроенный монитор, изображающий векторную графику. Монитор был монохромным, но на экран накладывалась полупрозрачная раскрашенная плёнка, своя для каждой игры, что давало иллюзию цвета, а также уменьшало эффект от мерцания изображения, присущий векторным мониторам.

В систему была встроена одна игра — «MineStorm» (подобие аркадной игры Asteroids), другие игры поставлялись на картриджах.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Vectrex es una videoconsola doméstica con pantalla vectorial, la única diseñada y lanzada al mercado doméstico, desarrollada por Smith Engineering. Salió a la venta en Norteamérica en noviembre de 1982 y en Europa y Japón en 1983. Originalmente fabricada por General Consumer Electronics, fue posteriormente licenciada a Milton Bradley tras la adquisición de la empresa. Bandai lanzó el sistema en Japón.

El Vectrex, a diferencia de otros sistemas de videojuegos disponibles en la época, contaba con un monitor CRT monocromo integrado y no necesitaba conectarse a un televisor, ya que disponía de su propia pantalla integrada. En la base inferior de la consola había un mando de control con cable desmontable que podía plegarse. Los juegos incluían láminas translúcidas en color que podían colocarse sobre la pantalla monocroma. Se fabricaron varios periféricos, como unas gafas 3D conocidas como "3D Imager" y un "lápiz óptico" que permitía al jugador dibujar directamente en la pantalla. Un juego incorporado, Mine Storm, permitía jugar sin necesidad de insertar un cartucho.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Vectrex ist eine auf einem Vektordisplay basierende Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch - die einzige, die jemals für den Heimgebrauch entworfen und veröffentlicht wurde und von Smith Engineering entwickelt wurde. Es wurde erstmals im November 1982 für den nordamerikanischen Markt und 1983 für Europa und Japan veröffentlicht. Ursprünglich von General Consumer Electronics hergestellt, wurde es später an Milton Bradley lizenziert, nachdem diese das Unternehmen übernommen hatten. Bandai brachte das System in Japan heraus.

Im Gegensatz zu anderen damals erhältlichen Videospielsystemen verfügte das Vectrex über einen integrierten monochromen CRT-Monitor und musste nicht an ein Fernsehgerät angeschlossen werden, da es über einen eigenen eingebauten Bildschirm verfügte. Ein abnehmbares kabelgebundenes Steuerkreuz war am unteren Ende der Konsole angebracht und konnte dort eingeklappt werden. Zu den Spielen gehörten durchsichtige Farbfolien, die über den monochromen Bildschirm gelegt werden konnten. Es wurde eine Reihe von Peripheriegeräten hergestellt, wie z. B. eine 3D-Brille, bekannt als "3D Imager", und ein "Lichtstift", mit dem der Spieler direkt auf dem Bildschirm zeichnen konnte. Ein eingebautes Spiel, Mine Storm, konnte ohne Einlegen einer Kassette gespielt werden.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Vectrex est une console de jeu vidéo de salon à écran vectoriel, la seule jamais conçue et commercialisée pour le marché domestique, développée par Smith Engineering. Elle a été commercialisée pour la première fois en Amérique du Nord en novembre 1982, puis en Europe et au Japon en 1983. Fabriquée à l'origine par General Consumer Electronics, elle a ensuite fait l'objet d'une licence accordée à Milton Bradley après le rachat de la société. Bandai a commercialisé le système au Japon.

Le Vectrex, contrairement aux autres systèmes de jeux vidéo disponibles à l'époque, était doté d'un écran CRT monochrome intégré et n'avait pas besoin d'être relié à un téléviseur puisqu'il disposait de son propre écran intégré. Un pavé de commande filaire amovible était monté sur la base inférieure de la console et pouvait être replié dans celle-ci. Les jeux comprenaient des feuilles de couleur translucides qui pouvaient être placées sur l'écran monochrome. Un certain nombre de périphériques ont été produits, tels qu'une paire de lunettes 3D connue sous le nom de "3D Imager" et un "light-pen" qui permettait au joueur de dessiner directement sur l'écran. Un jeu intégré, Mine Storm, pouvait être joué sans insérer de cartouche.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Vectrex è una console per videogiochi domestica basata su display vettoriali, l'unica mai progettata e rilasciata per il mercato domestico, sviluppata da Smith Engineering. È stata commercializzata per la prima volta in Nord America nel novembre 1982 e poi in Europa e Giappone nel 1983. Originariamente prodotta da General Consumer Electronics, fu poi data in licenza a Milton Bradley dopo l'acquisizione della società. Bandai distribuì il sistema in Giappone.

Il Vectrex, a differenza di altri sistemi di videogiochi disponibili all'epoca, era dotato di un monitor CRT monocromatico integrato e non aveva bisogno di essere collegato a un televisore, in quanto forniva il proprio display incorporato. Un pad di controllo a filo staccabile era montato e poteva essere ripiegato sulla base inferiore della console. I giochi includevano fogli traslucidi a colori che potevano essere posizionati sopra lo schermo monocromatico. Furono prodotte diverse periferiche, come un paio di occhiali 3D noti come "3D Imager" e una "light-pen" che permetteva al giocatore di disegnare direttamente sullo schermo. Un gioco integrato, Mine Storm, era giocabile senza inserire una cartuccia.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Vectrex – um console de videogame de 8 bits produzido pela Western Technologies/Smith Engineering, inicialmente distribuído sob licença da General Consumer Electric, depois pela Milton Bradley Company. O console estreou em novembro de 1982, e seu preço na época era de US$ 199. Após a aquisição da GCE pela Milton Bradley, o preço foi reduzido para US$ 150, e antes do colapso do mercado de videogames em 1983, o preço era de US$ 100. O Vectrex desapareceu do mercado no início de 1984. Na Polônia, ele apareceu no meio da década de 1980 e foi apresentado no programa Sonda.

Ao contrário dos consoles de mesa que geravam gráficos rasterizados e os exibiam na tela da televisão, o Vectrex tinha um monitor integrado que exibia gráficos vetoriais. O monitor monocromático do Vectrex utilizava sobreposições de plástico transparentes na tela, decorando o campo de jogo com áreas coloridas estáticas. Naquela época, muitos dos fliperamas populares usavam gráficos vetoriais, e a GCE queria que o Vectrex fizesse parte desse grupo – o console recebeu ports de alta qualidade de jogos como Space Wars e Armor Attack.

O Vectrex tinha o jogo Minestorm embutido, que era um clone de Asteroids. Além dos gamepads, os dispositivos apontadores produzidos para o console eram uma caneta de luz e o "3D imager", um tipo de óculos 3D.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
