<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
			<maxSize>0.16</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
			<maxSize>0.15</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1998</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Dreamcast</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Visual Memory Unit</text>
		</text>
		<!-- Support different names for regional consoles/computers -->
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="eu"/>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="us">
			<text>Dreamcast Visual Memory System</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true" region="jp"/>
		<!-- -->
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Visual Memory Unit is a memory card used by Sega's Dreamcast console. Unlike other memory cards, the VMU has a small LCD display and a set of buttons that resemble those on a Game Boy portable console. The VMU plugs directly into the joypad. During play, a small screen displays game information, pictures, and hints.

Some games, such as Sonic Adventure, allow you to copy special software to the VMU so that you can play the game without connecting to a console. In addition, the memory card allows you to see the current time thanks to the built-in clock. The VMU is available in several colors, the most common being blue (made of transparent blue plastic) and white.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Visual Memory Unit (pol. Wizualna Jednostka Pamięci) – karta pamięci wykorzystywana przez konsolę Dreamcast firmy Sega. W odróżnieniu od innych kart pamięci, VMU posiada mały wyświetlacz LCD i zestaw przycisków, które przypominają te z przenośnej konsoli Game Boy. VMU wpina się bezpośrednio do joypadu. Podczas gry na małym ekranie pojawiają się informacje dotyczące gry, obrazki, tudzież podpowiedzi.

Niektóre gry, takie jak Sonic Adventure umożliwiają skopiowanie specjalnego oprogramowania na VMU, dzięki czemu możliwe jest granie na niej bez potrzeby połączenia z konsolą. Oprócz tego karta pamięci umożliwia zobaczenie aktualnej godziny dzięki wbudowanemu zegarowi. VMU dostępny jest w kilku kolorach, najczęściej występujące to niebieski (wykonany z przezroczystego, niebieskiego plastiku) i biały.</text>
			<text lang="ru">VMU - это карта памяти, используемая в консоли Dreamcast компании Sega. В отличие от других карт памяти, VMU имеет небольшой ЖК-дисплей и набор кнопок, напоминающих кнопки на портативной консоли Game Boy. VMU подключается непосредственно к джойпаду. Во время игры на небольшом экране отображается информация об игре, изображения и подсказки.

Некоторые игры, например Sonic Adventure, позволяют скопировать специальное программное обеспечение на VMU, чтобы вы могли играть в игру без подключения к консоли. Кроме того, карта памяти позволяет видеть текущее время благодаря встроенным часам. VMU выпускается в нескольких цветах, наиболее распространенными из которых являются синий (из прозрачного синего пластика) и белый.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Visual Memory Unit es una tarjeta de memoria utilizada por la consola Dreamcast de Sega. A diferencia de otras tarjetas de memoria, la VMU tiene una pequeña pantalla LCD y un conjunto de botones que se asemejan a los de una consola portátil Game Boy. La VMU se conecta directamente al joypad. Durante el juego, una pequeña pantalla muestra información sobre el juego, imágenes y pistas.

Algunos juegos, como Sonic Adventure, permiten copiar un software especial en la VMU para poder jugar sin necesidad de conectarse a una consola. Además, la tarjeta de memoria te permite ver la hora actual gracias al reloj incorporado. La VMU está disponible en varios colores, siendo los más comunes el azul (fabricada en plástico azul transparente) y el blanco.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Visual Memory Unit ist eine Speicherkarte, die in der Dreamcast-Konsole von Sega verwendet wird. Im Gegensatz zu anderen Speicherkarten hat die VMU ein kleines LCD-Display und eine Reihe von Tasten, die denen auf einer tragbaren Game Boy-Konsole ähneln. Die VMU wird direkt in das Joypad eingesteckt. Während des Spiels werden auf einem kleinen Bildschirm Spielinformationen, Bilder und Hinweise angezeigt.

Bei einigen Spielen, wie z. B. Sonic Adventure, können Sie spezielle Software auf die VMU kopieren, so dass Sie das Spiel spielen können, ohne eine Konsole anschließen zu müssen. Darüber hinaus können Sie auf der Speicherkarte dank der eingebauten Uhr die aktuelle Uhrzeit ablesen. Die VMU ist in verschiedenen Farben erhältlich, die gängigsten sind blau (aus transparentem blauem Kunststoff) und weiß.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Visual Memory Unit (VMU) est une carte mémoire utilisée par la console Dreamcast de Sega. Contrairement aux autres cartes mémoire, la VMU possède un petit écran LCD et un ensemble de boutons qui ressemblent à ceux d'une console portable Game Boy. Le VMU se branche directement sur le joypad. Pendant le jeu, un petit écran affiche des informations sur le jeu, des images et des conseils.

Certains jeux, comme Sonic Adventure, permettent de copier un logiciel spécial sur le VMU afin de pouvoir jouer sans se connecter à une console. De plus, la carte mémoire permet de connaître l'heure actuelle grâce à l'horloge intégrée. Le VMU est disponible en plusieurs couleurs, les plus courantes étant le bleu (en plastique bleu transparent) et le blanc.</text>
			<text lang="it">La Visual Memory Unit è una scheda di memoria utilizzata dalla console Dreamcast di Sega. A differenza delle altre schede di memoria, la VMU è dotata di un piccolo display LCD e di una serie di pulsanti che ricordano quelli della console portatile Game Boy. La VMU si collega direttamente al joypad. Durante il gioco, un piccolo schermo visualizza informazioni sul gioco, immagini e suggerimenti.

Alcuni giochi, come Sonic Adventure, consentono di copiare un software speciale sulla VMU per poter giocare senza collegarsi alla console. Inoltre, la scheda di memoria consente di visualizzare l'ora corrente grazie all'orologio incorporato. La VMU è disponibile in diversi colori, i più comuni dei quali sono il blu (in plastica trasparente blu) e il bianco.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
