<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.25</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.43</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.335</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.335" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.25</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.43</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.335</pos>
			<maxSize>0.22</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.335" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1984</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Philips</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>VG-5000 μ</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The VG5000 μ is a computer created by Philips in 1984. It was manufactured in Le Mans by Radiotechnique (RTS) and marketed under the Philips, Radiola and Schneider brands.

Not compatible with any other machines, it offered VG5000 BASIC (derived from Microsoft BASIC-80) as the operating system upon boot. Graphic ability was limited to a semigraphic symbol display, with the equivalent resolution of 320 x 250 in 8 colors. There are about forty games available for the system.</text>
			<text lang="pl">VG5000 μ to komputer stworzony przez firmę Philips w 1984 roku. Był produkowany w Le Mans przez firmę Radiotechnique (RTS) i sprzedawany pod markami Philips, Radiola i Schneider.

Nie był kompatybilny z żadnymi innymi maszynami, oferował VG5000 BASIC (wywodzący się z Microsoft BASIC-80) jako system operacyjny po uruchomieniu. Możliwości graficzne były ograniczone do półgraficznego wyświetlacza symboli, o równoważnej rozdzielczości 320 x 250 w 8 kolorach. Dla systemu dostępnych jest około czterdziestu gier.</text>
			<text lang="ru">VG5000 μ - компьютер, созданный компанией Philips в 1984 году. Он производился в Ле-Мане компанией Radiotechnique (RTS) и продавался под марками Philips, Radiola и Schneider.

Не совместимый ни с какими другими машинами, он предлагал в качестве операционной системы при загрузке VG5000 BASIC (производный от Microsoft BASIC-80). Графические возможности ограничивались полуграфическим символьным дисплеем с эквивалентным разрешением 320 x 250 при 8 цветах. Для системы доступно около сорока игр.</text>
			<text lang="es">El VG5000 μ es un ordenador creado por Philips en 1984. Fue fabricado en Le Mans por Radiotechnique (RTS) y comercializado bajo las marcas Philips, Radiola y Schneider.

No era compatible con ninguna otra máquina y ofrecía VG5000 BASIC (derivado de Microsoft BASIC-80) como sistema operativo al arrancar. La capacidad gráfica se limitaba a una pantalla semigráfica de símbolos, con una resolución equivalente de 320 x 250 en 8 colores. Hay unos cuarenta juegos disponibles para el sistema.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der VG5000 μ ist ein Computer, der 1984 von Philips entwickelt wurde. Er wurde in Le Mans von Radiotechnique (RTS) hergestellt und unter den Marken Philips, Radiola und Schneider vertrieben.

Er war nicht mit anderen Rechnern kompatibel und bot beim Booten VG5000 BASIC (abgeleitet von Microsoft BASIC-80) als Betriebssystem. Die grafischen Möglichkeiten beschränkten sich auf eine semigrafische Symbolanzeige mit einer Auflösung von 320 x 250 in 8 Farben. Es sind etwa vierzig Spiele für das System verfügbar.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le VG5000 μ est un ordinateur créé par Philips en 1984. Il était fabriqué au Mans par Radiotechnique (RTS) et commercialisé sous les marques Philips, Radiola et Schneider.

Non compatible avec d'autres machines, il proposait le VG5000 BASIC (dérivé du Microsoft BASIC-80) comme système d'exploitation au démarrage. La capacité graphique était limitée à un affichage de symboles semi-graphiques, avec une résolution équivalente à 320 x 250 en 8 couleurs. Une quarantaine de jeux sont disponibles pour ce système.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il VG5000 μ è un computer creato da Philips nel 1984. È stato prodotto a Le Mans da Radiotechnique (RTS) e commercializzato con i marchi Philips, Radiola e Schneider.

Non compatibile con altre macchine, offriva il VG5000 BASIC (derivato dal Microsoft BASIC-80) come sistema operativo all'avvio. La capacità grafica era limitata a un display di simboli semigrafici, con una risoluzione equivalente a 320 x 250 a 8 colori. Sono disponibili circa quaranta giochi per il sistema.</text>
			<text lang="pt">VG5000 μ era um computador criado pela empresa Philips em 1984. Era produzido em Le Mans pela empresa Radiotechnique (RTS) e vendido sob as marcas Philips, Radiola e Schneider.

Não era compatível com nenhuma outra máquina, oferecia VG5000 BASIC (derivado do Microsoft BASIC-80) como sistema operacional após a inicialização. As capacidades gráficas eram limitadas a um display de símbolos semi-gráfico, com resolução equivalente a 320 x 250 em 8 cores. Cerca de quarenta jogos estão disponíveis para o sistema.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
