<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme defaultView="Icons">
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text/>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Collection</text>
			<text lang="pl">Kolekcja</text>
			<text lang="ru">Коллекция</text>
			<text lang="es">Recopilación</text>
			<text lang="fr">Collection</text>
			<text lang="it">Collezione</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Video Game Music</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Video Game Music player is a utility from MAME used to natively playback video game music from their sources. Notably, it is not playing from a recording of the audio but actually emulating the chips used to play the music itself. Certain sound systems can be very CPU intensive, such as the Q-sound audio board.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Odtwarzacz muzyki z gier wideo to narzędzie MAME służące do natywnego odtwarzania muzyki z gier wideo z ich źródeł. Warto zauważyć, że nie jest to odtwarzanie z nagrania audio, ale emulacja chipów używanych do odtwarzania samej muzyki. Niektóre systemy dźwiękowe mogą bardzo obciążać procesor, takie jak karta dźwiękowa Q-sound.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Video game music player - это утилита из MAME, предназначенная для нативного воспроизведения музыки видеоигр из их источников. Примечательно, что она воспроизводит не запись звука, а эмулирует микросхемы, используемые для воспроизведения самой музыки. Некоторые звуковые системы могут быть очень требовательны к процессору, например, аудиоплата Q-sound.</text>
			<text lang="es">El reproductor de música de videojuegos es una utilidad de MAME utilizada para reproducir de forma nativa música de videojuegos desde sus fuentes. En concreto, no reproduce desde una grabación de audio, sino que emula los chips utilizados para reproducir la música. Ciertos sistemas de sonido pueden ser muy intensivos en CPU, como la placa de audio Q-sound.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Videospiel-Musikplayer ist ein Dienstprogramm von MAME zur nativen Wiedergabe von Videospielmusik aus deren Quellen. Dabei wird nicht von einer Audioaufnahme abgespielt, sondern es werden die Chips emuliert, die zum Abspielen der Musik selbst verwendet werden. Bestimmte Soundsysteme können sehr rechenintensiv sein, wie z. B. das Q-Sound Audio Board.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le lecteur de musique de jeu vidéo est un utilitaire de MAME utilisé pour lire nativement la musique de jeu vidéo à partir de leurs sources. Notamment, il ne joue pas à partir d'un enregistrement audio mais émule les puces utilisées pour jouer la musique elle-même. Certains systèmes audio peuvent être très gourmands en ressources processeur, comme la carte audio Q-sound.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il lettore di musica per videogiochi è un'utility del MAME utilizzata per riprodurre in modo nativo la musica dei videogiochi dalle loro sorgenti. In particolare, non viene riprodotta da una registrazione dell'audio, ma emula i chip utilizzati per riprodurre la musica stessa. Alcuni sistemi audio possono essere molto intensivi per la CPU, come la scheda audio Q-sound.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
