<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.255</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.39" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.35</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.45</origin>
			<pos>0.499 0.389</pos>
			<maxSize>0.24</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.219 0.389" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1992</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Tandy/Memorex</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Video Information System</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>The Tandy Memorex Video Information System (VIS) is an interactive, multimedia CD-ROM player produced by the Tandy Corporation starting in 1992. It is similar in function to the Philips CD-i and Commodore CDTV systems (particularly the CDTV, since both the VIS and CDTV were adaptations of existing computer platforms and operating systems to the set-top-box design).

The VIS systems were sold only at Radio Shack, under the Memorex brand, both of which Tandy owned at the time.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Tandy Memorex Video Information System (VIS) to interaktywny, multimedialny odtwarzacz CD-ROM produkowany przez Tandy Corporation od 1992 roku. Jest on podobny pod względem funkcji do systemów Philips CD-i i Commodore CDTV (zwłaszcza CDTV, ponieważ zarówno VIS, jak i CDTV były adaptacjami istniejących platform komputerowych i systemów operacyjnych do konstrukcji set-top-box).

Systemy VIS były sprzedawane wyłącznie w Radio Shack, pod marką Memorex, której właścicielem była wówczas firma Tandy.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Tandy Memorex Video Information System (VIS) - интерактивный мультимедийный проигрыватель CD-ROM, выпускаемый корпорацией Tandy с 1992 года. По своим функциям он аналогичен системам Philips CD-i и Commodore CDTV (особенно CDTV, поскольку и VIS, и CDTV представляли собой адаптацию существующих компьютерных платформ и операционных систем к дизайну телевизионной приставки).

Системы VIS продавались только в магазине Radio Shack под маркой Memorex, который в то время принадлежал компании Tandy.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Tandy Memorex Video Information System (VIS) es un reproductor multimedia interactivo de CD-ROM producido por Tandy Corporation a partir de 1992. Su funcionamiento es similar al de los sistemas CD-i de Philips y CDTV de Commodore (especialmente el CDTV, ya que tanto el VIS como el CDTV eran adaptaciones de plataformas informáticas y sistemas operativos existentes al diseño de los descodificadores).

Los sistemas VIS sólo se vendían en Radio Shack, bajo la marca Memorex, ambas propiedad de Tandy en aquella época.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Tandy Memorex Video Information System (VIS) ist ein interaktives, multimediales CD-ROM-Abspielgerät, das von der Tandy Corporation ab 1992 hergestellt wurde. Es ähnelt in seiner Funktion dem Philips CD-i und dem Commodore CDTV System (insbesondere dem CDTV, da sowohl das VIS als auch das CDTV Anpassungen bestehender Computerplattformen und Betriebssysteme an das Design einer Set-Top-Box waren).

Die VIS-Systeme wurden nur bei Radio Shack unter der Marke Memorex verkauft, die damals beide zu Tandy gehörten.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Tandy Memorex Video Information System (VIS) est un lecteur de CD-ROM interactif et multimédia produit par la Tandy Corporation à partir de 1992. Son fonctionnement est similaire à celui des systèmes Philips CD-i et Commodore CDTV (en particulier le CDTV, puisque le VIS et le CDTV étaient des adaptations de plates-formes informatiques et de systèmes d'exploitation existants à la conception d'un boîtier décodeur).

Les systèmes VIS n'étaient vendus que chez Radio Shack, sous la marque Memorex, qui appartenait à l'époque à Tandy.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Tandy Memorex Video Information System (VIS) è un lettore di CD-ROM interattivo e multimediale prodotto dalla Tandy Corporation a partire dal 1992. Il suo funzionamento è simile a quello dei sistemi Philips CD-i e Commodore CDTV (in particolare il CDTV, poiché sia il VIS che il CDTV erano adattamenti di piattaforme informatiche e sistemi operativi esistenti al design di set-top-box).

I sistemi VIS erano venduti solo presso Radio Shack, con il marchio Memorex, entrambi di proprietà di Tandy all'epoca.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Tandy Memorex Video Information System (VIS) é um reprodutor de CD-ROM interativo e multimídia produzido pela Tandy Corporation a partir de 1992. Ele é semelhante em funcionalidade aos sistemas Philips CD-i e Commodore CDTV (especialmente o CDTV, visto que tanto o VIS quanto o CDTV eram adaptações de plataformas de computador e sistemas operacionais existentes para uma construção de set-top-box).

Os sistemas VIS eram vendidos exclusivamente na Radio Shack, sob a marca Memorex, que na época era propriedade da Tandy.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
