<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.41</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.465</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.36</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.473</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.3925</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.41" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise169.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.41</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.465</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.351</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.466</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.389</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.41" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>1998</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>GameHouse</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>GameHouse is a platform offering a variety of casual games like puzzles, Mahjong, hidden objects, and more.

The site also features exclusive games, popular series, and curated recommendations like &quot;most played&quot; or &quot;new arrivals.&quot; For extra benefits, you can become a member and unlock even more features.</text>
			<text lang="pt">A GameHouse é uma plataforma que oferece uma variedade de jogos casuais, como puzzles, Mahjong, objectos escondidos e muito mais.

O site também inclui jogos exclusivos, séries populares e recomendações selecionadas como &quot;mais jogados&quot; ou &quot;recém-chegados&quot;. Para obter vantagens adicionais, pode tornar-se membro e desbloquear ainda mais funcionalidades.</text>
			<text lang="it">GameHouse è una piattaforma che offre una varietà di giochi casual come puzzle, mahjong, oggetti nascosti e altro ancora.

Il sito offre anche giochi esclusivi, serie popolari e raccomandazioni curate come &quot;i più giocati&quot; o &quot;i nuovi arrivi&quot;. Per ottenere ulteriori vantaggi, è possibile diventare membri e sbloccare ancora più funzioni.</text>
			<text lang="fr">GameHouse est une plateforme offrant une variété de jeux occasionnels tels que les puzzles, le Mahjong, les objets cachés et bien d'autres encore.

Le site propose également des jeux exclusifs, des séries populaires et des recommandations comme &quot;les plus joués&quot; ou &quot;les nouveaux arrivants&quot;. Pour bénéficier d'avantages supplémentaires, vous pouvez devenir membre et débloquer encore plus de fonctionnalités.</text>
			<text lang="de">GameHouse ist eine Plattform, die eine Vielzahl von Gelegenheitsspielen wie Puzzles, Mahjong, versteckte Objekte und mehr anbietet.

Die Website bietet auch exklusive Spiele, beliebte Serien und Empfehlungen wie &quot;meistgespielt&quot; oder &quot;neu eingetroffen&quot;. Um zusätzliche Vorteile zu erhalten, können Sie Mitglied werden und noch mehr Funktionen freischalten.</text>
			<text lang="es">GameHouse es una plataforma que ofrece una gran variedad de juegos casuales como puzles, Mahjong, objetos ocultos y mucho más.

El sitio también ofrece juegos exclusivos, series populares y recomendaciones curadas como &quot;los más jugados&quot; o &quot;los recién llegados&quot;. Para obtener ventajas adicionales, puedes hacerte miembro y desbloquear aún más funciones.</text>
			<text lang="ru">GameHouse - это платформа, предлагающая разнообразные казуальные игры, такие как пазлы, маджонг, скрытые объекты и многое другое.

На сайте также представлены эксклюзивные игры, популярные серии, а также курируемые рекомендации, такие как &quot;самые играемые&quot; или &quot;новые поступления&quot;. Чтобы получить дополнительные преимущества, вы можете стать членом клуба и открыть для себя еще больше возможностей.</text>
			<text lang="pl">GameHouse to platforma oferująca różnorodne gry casualowe, takie jak puzzle, Mahjong, ukryte obiekty i inne.
				
Witryna oferuje również ekskluzywne gry, popularne serie i wyselekcjonowane rekomendacje, takie jak &quot;najczęściej grane&quot; lub &quot;nowości&quot;. Aby uzyskać dodatkowe korzyści, możesz zostać członkiem i odblokować jeszcze więcej funkcji.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
