<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.41</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.465</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.36</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.473</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.3925</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.41" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise169.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.41</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.465</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.351</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.466</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.389</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.41" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2000</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Electronic Arts</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>PopCap Games</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>PopCap Games, Inc. is an American video game developer based in Seattle, and a subsidiary of Electronic Arts. The company was founded in 2000 by John Vechey, Brian Fiete and Jason Kapalka.

Originally founded under the name "Sexy Action Cool", their first title was a strip poker game that served as a revenue stream for future titles. PopCap has developed several games for computers, consoles and mobile devices, with their most popular games being Bejeweled and Plants vs. Zombies games. PopCap was sold to Electronic Arts in 2011.</text>
			<text lang="pl">PopCap Games, Inc. to amerykański producent gier wideo z siedzibą w Seattle i spółka zależna Electronic Arts. Firma została założona w 2000 roku przez Johna Vecheya, Briana Fiete i Jasona Kapalkę.

Pierwotnie założona pod nazwą "Sexy Action Cool", ich pierwszym tytułem była gra w pokera ze striptizem, która posłużyła jako źródło dochodów dla przyszłych tytułów. PopCap opracował kilka gier na komputery, konsole i urządzenia mobilne, a ich najpopularniejsze gry to Bejeweled i Plants vs. Zombies. PopCap zostało sprzedane Electronic Arts w 2011 roku.</text>
			<text lang="ru">PopCap Games, Inc. - американский разработчик видеоигр, базирующийся в Сиэтле и являющийся дочерней компанией Electronic Arts. Компания была основана в 2000 году Джоном Вечи, Брайаном Фите и Джейсоном Капалкой.

Первой игрой, созданной под названием "Sexy Action Cool", была игра в покер на раздевание, которая послужила источником дохода для будущих игр. PopCap разработала несколько игр для компьютеров, консолей и мобильных устройств, самыми популярными из которых стали Bejeweled и Plants vs. Zombies. В 2011 году компания PopCap была продана Electronic Arts.</text>
			<text lang="es">PopCap Games, Inc. es una empresa estadounidense de desarrollo de videojuegos con sede en Seattle y filial de Electronic Arts. La empresa fue fundada en 2000 por John Vechey, Brian Fiete y Jason Kapalka.

Fundada originalmente bajo el nombre de "Sexy Action Cool", su primer título fue un juego de strip póquer que sirvió como fuente de ingresos para futuros títulos. PopCap ha desarrollado varios juegos para ordenadores, consolas y dispositivos móviles, siendo sus juegos más populares Bejeweled y Plants vs. Zombies. PopCap fue vendida a Electronic Arts en 2011.</text>
			<text lang="de">PopCap Games, Inc. ist ein amerikanischer Videospielentwickler mit Sitz in Seattle und eine Tochtergesellschaft von Electronic Arts. Das Unternehmen wurde im Jahr 2000 von John Vechey, Brian Fiete und Jason Kapalka gegründet.

Ursprünglich unter dem Namen "Sexy Action Cool" gegründet, war ihr erster Titel ein Strip-Poker-Spiel, das als Einnahmequelle für zukünftige Titel diente. PopCap hat mehrere Spiele für Computer, Konsolen und mobile Geräte entwickelt, wobei die beliebtesten Spiele Bejeweled und Plants vs. Zombies sind. Im Jahr 2011 wurde PopCap an Electronic Arts verkauft.</text>
			<text lang="fr">PopCap Games, Inc. est un développeur américain de jeux vidéo basé à Seattle et une filiale d'Electronic Arts. La société a été fondée en 2000 par John Vechey, Brian Fiete et Jason Kapalka.

Fondée à l'origine sous le nom de "Sexy Action Cool", son premier titre était un jeu de strip-poker qui servait de source de revenus pour les titres à venir. PopCap a développé plusieurs jeux pour ordinateurs, consoles et appareils mobiles, ses jeux les plus populaires étant Bejeweled et Plants vs Zombies. PopCap a été vendu à Electronic Arts en 2011.</text>
			<text lang="it">PopCap Games, Inc. è uno sviluppatore di videogiochi americano con sede a Seattle e una filiale di Electronic Arts. La società è stata fondata nel 2000 da John Vechey, Brian Fiete e Jason Kapalka.

Inizialmente fondata con il nome di "Sexy Action Cool", il loro primo titolo è stato uno strip poker che è servito come fonte di guadagno per i titoli futuri. PopCap ha sviluppato diversi giochi per computer, console e dispositivi mobili; i suoi giochi più popolari sono Bejeweled e Piante contro Zombi. PopCap è stata venduta a Electronic Arts nel 2011.</text>
			<text lang="pt">A PopCap Games, Inc. é uma produtora americana de jogos eletrônicos com sede em Seattle e subsidiária da Electronic Arts. A empresa foi fundada em 2000 por John Vechey, Brian Fiete e Jason Kapalka.

Originalmente fundada como "Sexy Action Cool", seu primeiro título foi um jogo de pôquer com striptease, que serviu como fonte de renda para títulos futuros. A PopCap desenvolveu vários jogos para computadores, consoles e dispositivos móveis, sendo seus jogos mais populares Bejeweled e Plants vs. Zombies. A PopCap foi vendida para a Electronic Arts em 2011.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
