<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.32</pos>
			<maxSize>0.27</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.32" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>1987</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.03</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.25</pos>
			<text>Sharp
X1</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.40</pos>
			<text>Is a series of home computers released by Sharp Corporation from 1982 to 1988. It is based on a Zilog Z80 CPU.

Despite the fact that the Computer Division of Sharp Corporation had released the MZ series, suddenly the Television Division released a new computer series called the X1. At the time the original X1 was released, all other home computers generally had a BASIC language in ROM. However the X1 did not have a BASIC ROM, and it had to load the Hu-BASIC interpreter from a cassette tape. On the plus side however, this concept meant that a free RAM area was available that was as big as possible when not using BASIC. This policy was originally copied from the Sharp MZ series, and they were called clean computers in Japan. The cabinet shape of X1 was also much more stylish than others at that time and a range of cabinet colors (including Red) was selectable.

The RGB display monitor for the X1 had a television tuner, and a computer screen could be super-imposed on TV. All the TV functions could be controlled from a computer program. The character font was completely programmable (A.K.A. PCG) with 4bit color, and was effectively used in many games. The entirety of the VRAM memory was mapped on to the I/O area, so it was controlled without bank switching. Since X1 had these features, it was very powerful for game software.

While X1 was struggling to sell, the PC8801 (from NEC) was quickly becoming popular in the Japanese market. In 1984, Sharp released the X1 turbo series with high resolution graphics (640x400, while X1 had 640x200). It had many improvements, but the clock speed was still only 4 MHz. In 1986, Sharp released the X1 turbo Z series with a 4096 color analog RGB monitor. An X1 twin, which had a PC-Engine in the cabinet, was finally released as the last machine of the X1 series in 1987. Then this series was succeeded by the X68000 series.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Sharp X1 est le nom donné à une série de micro-ordinateurs japonais créé par Sharp Corporation de 1982 à 1988. Ils intègrent tous un processeur Zilog Z80.

Bien que ce soit la division de Sharp consacrée aux ordinateurs personnels qui a créé la série des MZ (tels que le MZ-80K), cette fois c'est la division pour la création de télévision qui s'est occupée de cette nouvelle série. À l'époque à laquelle le premier X1 est sorti, la plupart des ordinateurs personnels possédaient une mémoire morte programmée en BASIC. Cependant, le X1 n'utilisait pas le langage BASIC mais chargeait directement l'interprète depuis une cassette audio. De plus, ce concept permettait l'accès à un espace pour la mémoire vive via l'enregistrement des données. Le design du X1 était aussi plus stylisé que ses concurrents de la même époque et un choix de différentes couleurs était disponible.

Le moniteur d'ordinateur disposait d'un tuner, et un écran d'ordinateur pouvait être superposé à la télévision. Toutes les fonctions télévisuelles étaient alors contrôlables depuis un programme informatique. L'intégralité de la mémoire vidéo était située dans la zone des entrées-sorties. L'ensemble de ces éléments faisait du X1 une plate-forme de jeu de qualité pour son époque.

Alors que Sharp se battait pour vendre son X1, le PC-88 de NEC gagna en notoriété sur le marché japonais. En 1984, Sharp réalisa la série des X1 Turbo dotés d'une meilleure résolution graphique (640x400, tandis que celle du X1 originale était 640x200). Cette série connut de nombreuses améliorations mais la fréquence d'horloge stagna à 4 MHz. En 1986, Sharp sortit une nouvelle gamme, les X1 Turbo Z avec une gamme de 4 096 couleurs. Enfin, en 1987, un clone du X1 fut créé en tant que dernière série. Il intégrait les fonctionnalités de la console PC-Engine.

Le Sharp X1 a ensuite été remplacé par la série des Sharp X68000.</text>
			<text lang="de">Ist die Bezeichnung einer Serie von Heimcomputern des japanischen Herstellers Sharp aus dem Zeitraum 1982 bis 1988. Die Reihe baut auf dem Mikroprozessor Zilog Z80 auf.
In den Endzügen der MZ80-Baureihe brachte Sharps TV-Division ab 1982 den X1 auf den Markt (CZ-800C). Diese erste Variante weist Ähnlichkeiten auf zur MZ80-Variante des MZ2000, ist jedoch nicht mit diesem kompatibel. Auffälligstes Merkmal war zunächst die rote Gehäusefarbe. Weiterhin bestehen Anschlussmöglichkeiten an Radio- oder TV-Empfänger. Die Hardware setzte sich zusammen aus einer auf 4 MHz getakteten Z80A-CPU mit 64 kB RAM, 4 kB VRAM (maximal erweiterbar auf 48 kB) und einer Grafikauflösung von 640 × 200 Bildpunkten. Als Massenspeicher wurde ein Kassettenlaufwerk verwendet.

Gemäß Sharps Clean-Computer-Konzept, das auch bei der MZ-Baureihe zur Anwendung kam, besitzt der Rechner kein integriertes BASIC-ROM oder ein sonstiges Betriebssystem. Stattdessen musste das Betriebssystem über einen Datenträger eingelesen werden (Tape Basic, Disk Basic). Dadurch hatte der Nutzer die freie Wahl des Betriebssystems, das beim Start in den Arbeitsspeicher geladen wurde. Im Gegenzug verzögerte sich dadurch die Startzeit bis zur vollen Einsatzbereitschaft des Geräts. Das Gerät war als Multimedia-System konzipiert und konnte in Verbindung mit dem X1-Monitor Text oder Grafiken über dem Fernsehbild einblenden.

Der X1 stand in Konkurrenz vor allem zu NECs PC-8801. 1984 veröffentlichte Sharp den X1 turbo mit einer höheren Auflösung von 640 × 400 Bildpunkten. 1986 folgte der X1 turbo Z mit einem analogen RGB-Monitor mit 4096 Farben. Als letztes Modell erschien 1987 der X1 twin, mit einer integrierten PC-Engine-Spielkonsole, einschließlich eines HuCard-Lesers. Der Benutzer konnte jederzeit zwischen den beiden Systemen umschalten, ein wechselseitiger Datenaustausch zwischen den beiden Systemen war jedoch nicht möglich. Auch ist der X1 twin nicht kompatibel zu den in den Folgejahren veröffentlichten Hardwareerweiterungen der Spielkonsole.

1987 erschien mit dem X68000 ein technischer Nachfolger, 1988 wurde die X1-Serie schließlich eingestellt.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Линейка домашних компьютеров, производимых компанией Sharp Corporation с 1982 по 1988 год. Она была основана на центральном процессоре Z80.

Несмотря на то, что «компьютерный отдел» корпорации Sharp выпустил компьютеры серии MZ, неожиданно «телевизионный отдел» выпустил новую линейку компьютеров под названием X1. На момент выпуска исходного X1 все другие домашние компьютеры обычно имели вариант языка BASIC в ПЗУ. Несмотря на это, у X1 не было «вшитого» BASIC, интерпретатор Hu-BASIC приходилось загружать с кассеты. Этот подход имел то достоинство, что свободная область памяти имела наибольший размер, когда BASIC не использовался. Эта политика была заимствована у компьютеров серии Sharp MZ, которые в Японии называли «чистыми компьютерами». Дизайн корпуса X1 также был более стильным, чем у других компьютеров того времени. Предлагался также выбор цвета корпуса, в том числе можно было купить этот компьютер в красном корпусе.

RGB-монитор, служивший дисплеем для X1, имел встроенный ТВ-тюнер, и изображение, отображаемое компьютером, могло накладываться на телевизионное. Всеми функциями телевизора можно управлять программно. Символы шрифта были полностью программируемыми. Система использовала 4-битный цвет. Эти особенности эффективно использовались во многих играх. Вся память VRAM была отображена в область ввода-вывода, так что ей можно было управлять без смены банков памяти. Эти особенности, присущие X1 делали его весьма мощным игровым компьютером.

В то время как продажи X1 были невысокими, на японском рынке быстро становился популярным NEC PC-8801 (выпускаемый NEC). В 1984 году Sharp выпустила линейку X1 turbo, которая поддерживала графику с высоким разрешением (640x400, в то время, как X1 поддерживал лишь разрешение 640х200). Было много и других улучшений, но тактовая частота всё ещё оставалась равной 4 МГц. В 1986 году Sharp выпустила X1 turbo серии Z с аналоговым RGB-монитором, поддерживающую отображение до 4096 цветов. X1 twin, в корпусе которого был смонтирован PC-Engine, был выпущен в 1987 году как последняя машина серии X1. Серию X1 сменила серия X68000.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>