<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3905</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.46</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.385</pos>
			<maxSize>0.375</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.49</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.42</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.385" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise169.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.3905</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.465</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.385</pos>
			<maxSize>0.365</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.48</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.4</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.385" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2005</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Microsoft</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Xbox Live Arcade</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Xbox Live Arcade (XBLA) was a digital video game distribution service available on the Xbox 360 console. It offered a wide variety of downloadable games, ranging from classic arcade titles to innovative indie games.

XBLA provided gamers with an easy way to discover and play new games, often featuring unique and creative gameplay experiences.
It was known for its affordable pricing and frequent promotions, making it a popular choice for gamers looking to expand their library with diverse and entertaining titles.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Xbox Live Arcade (XBLA) era um serviço de distribuição digital de jogos de vídeo disponível na consola Xbox 360. Oferecia uma grande variedade de jogos descarregáveis, desde títulos clássicos de arcada a jogos indie inovadores.

A XBLA proporcionava aos jogadores uma forma fácil de descobrir e jogar novos jogos, muitas vezes com experiências de jogo únicas e criativas.
Era conhecida pelos seus preços acessíveis e promoções frequentes, o que a tornava uma escolha popular para os jogadores que procuravam expandir a sua biblioteca com títulos diversificados e divertidos.</text>
			<text lang="it">Xbox Live Arcade (XBLA) è stato un servizio di distribuzione digitale di videogiochi disponibile sulla console Xbox 360. Offriva un'ampia varietà di giochi scaricabili, che spaziavano dai classici titoli arcade agli innovativi giochi indie.

XBLA offriva ai giocatori un modo semplice per scoprire e giocare a nuovi giochi, spesso caratterizzati da esperienze di gioco uniche e creative.
Era noto per i suoi prezzi accessibili e le frequenti promozioni, che lo rendevano una scelta popolare per i giocatori che desideravano ampliare la propria libreria con titoli diversi e divertenti.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Xbox Live Arcade (XBLA) était un service de distribution de jeux vidéo numériques disponible sur la console Xbox 360. Il proposait une grande variété de jeux téléchargeables, allant de titres d'arcade classiques à des jeux indépendants innovants.
XBLA permettait aux joueurs de découvrir et de jouer facilement à de nouveaux jeux, proposant souvent des expériences de jeu uniques et créatives.
Il était connu pour ses prix abordables et ses promotions fréquentes, ce qui en faisait un choix populaire pour les joueurs cherchant à enrichir leur bibliothèque de titres divers et divertissants.</text>
			<text lang="de">Xbox Live Arcade (XBLA) war ein digitaler Vertriebsservice für Videospiele, der für die Konsole Xbox 360 verfügbar war. Er bot eine große Auswahl an herunterladbaren Spielen, die von klassischen Arcade-Titeln bis hin zu innovativen Indie-Spielen reichten.

XBLA bot Spielern eine einfache Möglichkeit, neue Spiele zu entdecken und zu spielen, die oft einzigartige und kreative Gameplay-Erfahrungen boten.
XBLA war bekannt für seine erschwinglichen Preise und die häufigen Werbeaktionen, was es zu einer beliebten Wahl für Spieler machte, die ihre Bibliothek mit vielfältigen und unterhaltsamen Titeln erweitern wollten.</text>
			<text lang="es">Xbox Live Arcade (XBLA) era un servicio de distribución digital de videojuegos disponible en la consola Xbox 360. Ofrecía una amplia variedad de juegos descargables, desde títulos arcade clásicos a innovadores juegos indie.

XBLA ofrecía a los jugadores una forma sencilla de descubrir y jugar a nuevos títulos, a menudo con experiencias de juego únicas y creativas.
Era conocida por sus precios asequibles y sus frecuentes promociones, lo que la convertía en una opción popular para los jugadores que buscaban ampliar su biblioteca con títulos diversos y entretenidos.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Xbox Live Arcade (XBLA) - это сервис цифровой дистрибуции видеоигр, доступный на консоли Xbox 360. Он предлагал широкий выбор загружаемых игр - от классических аркад до инновационных инди-игр.

XBLA предоставлял геймерам возможность легко находить и играть в новые игры, часто отличающиеся уникальным и креативным геймплеем.
Она была известна своими доступными ценами и частыми акциями, что сделало ее популярным выбором среди геймеров, желающих пополнить свою библиотеку разнообразными и интересными играми.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Xbox Live Arcade (XBLA) była usługą cyfrowej dystrybucji gier wideo dostępną na konsoli Xbox 360. Oferowała szeroką gamę gier do pobrania, od klasycznych tytułów zręcznościowych po innowacyjne gry niezależne.

XBLA zapewniała graczom łatwy sposób na odkrywanie i granie w nowe gry, często oferujące unikalne i kreatywne wrażenia z rozgrywki.
Serwis był znany z przystępnych cen i częstych promocji, dzięki czemu był popularnym wyborem dla graczy chcących poszerzyć swoją bibliotekę o różnorodne i zabawne tytuły.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
