<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="background1" extra="true">
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="background" extra="true">
			<zIndex>90</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="1.5 0.5" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.95 0.5" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.5 0.385</pos>
			<maxSize>0.365</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.22 0.385" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.2</pos>
			<text>2005</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.255</pos>
			<text>Microsoft</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.04</fontSize>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<pos>0.49 0.30</pos>
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<text>Xbox 360</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>FFFFFF</color>
			<fontSize>0.065</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="x" from="0.5" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<size>0.5 0</size>
			<pos>0.49 0.4</pos>
			<text>The Xbox 360 is a home video game console developed by Microsoft. As the successor to the original Xbox, it is the second console in the Xbox series. It competed with Sony's PlayStation 3 and Nintendo's Wii as part of the seventh generation of video game consoles. It was officially unveiled on MTV on May 12, 2005, with detailed launch and game information announced later that month at the 2005 Electronic Entertainment Expo.

The Xbox 360 features an online service, Xbox Live, which was expanded from its previous iteration on the original Xbox and received regular updates during the console's lifetime. Available in free and subscription-based varieties, Xbox Live allows users to: play games online; download games (through Xbox Live Arcade) and game demos; purchase and stream music, television programs, and films through the Xbox Music and Xbox Video portals; and access third-party content services through media streaming applications. In addition to online multimedia features, it allows users to stream media from local PCs. Several peripherals have been released, including wireless controllers, expanded hard drive storage, and the Kinect motion sensing camera. The release of these additional services and peripherals helped the Xbox brand grow from gaming-only to encompassing all multimedia, turning it into a hub for living-room computing entertainment.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Xbox 360 – konsola gier wideo wyprodukowana przez firmę Microsoft. Została opracowana we współpracy z IBM, ATI i NEC. Xbox 360 to następca konsoli Xbox, konkuruje z Sony PlayStation 3 i Nintendo Wii w ramach siódmej generacji gier konsolowych. Platforma zintegrowana jest z usługą Xbox Live, usługą pozwalającą graczom na rywalizację w trybie online i pobieranie treści, takich jak gry zręcznościowe, dema gier, filmy z gier, programy telewizyjne oraz filmy. Konsola została wprowadzona do sprzedaży: w USA 22 listopada 2005, w Europie 2 grudnia 2005, w Japonii 10 grudnia 2005, w Czechach i Polsce 3 listopada 2006. 20 kwietnia 2016 Microsoft poinformował o zaprzestaniu produkcji konsoli Xbox 360.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Xbox 360 est une console de jeux vidéo développée par Microsoft, en coopération avec IBM, ATI Technologies, Samsung et SiS. Elle succède à la Xbox, et elle concurrence, dans la lignée des consoles de jeux vidéo de septième génération, la Wii de Nintendo et la PlayStation 3 de Sony.

En date du 23 avril 2016, les chiffres donnent 85,80 millions d'exemplaires vendus à travers le monde. Trois modèles de la console peuvent être distingués — le modèle initial commercialisé d'abord aux États-Unis le 22 novembre 2005, la version légère et silencieuse appelée Xbox 360 S commercialisée le 16 juillet 2010 en Europe, et la troisième version, la Xbox 360 E commercialisée en 2013.

La console offre une rétro-compatibilité avec une partie des titres parus sur Xbox ainsi que de nouvelles idées comme celle des pseudos de base qui passe de un seul à plusieurs qui pourront être générés par la console . La Xbox One lui succède fin 2013.

Après 10 ans d'existence, Phil Spencer annonce le 20 avril 2016 que la production de cette console s'arrête afin de liquider les stocks jusqu'à épuisement. Néanmoins, le SAV ainsi que les serveurs Xbox Live continueront de fonctionner jusqu'à une date indéterminée.</text>
			<text lang="de">Descpriptions. Pls send me it in Discord</text>
			<text lang="ru">Вторая по счёту игровая приставка компании Microsoft, которая последовала за Xbox. Конкурентами Xbox 360 среди игровых платформ седьмого поколения являются PlayStation 3 от Sony Computer Entertainment и Wii от Nintendo. Некоторые из основных функций Xbox 360 представлены сервисом Xbox Live, позволяющим играть через Интернет, а также загружать разнообразный контент — видеоигры, демоверсии, трейлеры, музыку, ТВ-шоу и т. п.

Xbox 360 была официально анонсирована на канале MTV 12 мая 2005 года, а более детальная информация о приставке была представлена в том же месяце на выставке Electronic Entertainment Expo (E3). Все доступные на время выпуска приставки были успешно проданы в каждой стране, кроме Японии. По состоянию на июнь 2010 года, существует 41,7 миллиона приставок Xbox 360 по всему миру.

В 2009 году на веб-сайте компьютерной тематики IGN Xbox 360 была названа шестой величайшей игровой приставкой всех времён, попав в список из 25 позиций. На крупнейшей выставке игр Electronic Entertainment Expo 2013 был представлен обновлённый дизайн Xbox 360.</text>
			<fontPath>./../../_inc/fonts/ubuntu_condensed.ttf</fontPath>
			<color>666666</color>
			<fontSize>0.025</fontSize>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
			<zIndex>140</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="y" from="0.8" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" to="0" begin="0" duration="0" mode="linear"/>
				<animation property="opacity" from="0" to="1" begin="3000" duration="1000" mode="EaseIn"/>
			</storyboard>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>