<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.436</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<pos>0.4998 0.424</pos>
			<maxSize>0.402</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.529</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.441</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2198 0.424" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video-left" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.76</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.59</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.3 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.412 0.652</pos>
			<maxSize>0.198</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.198</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.198</maxSize>
			<rotation>0</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.132 0.652" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video-right" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space169.png</path>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.54</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.51</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.67 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.622 0.530</pos>
			<maxSize>0.248</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.329</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.275</maxSize>
			<rotation>0</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.342 0.530" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<default>./../../_inc/anim/video/CRT_Noise169.mp4</default>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.438</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.48</origin>
			<pos>0.4995 0.425</pos>
			<maxSize>0.396</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.528</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.44</maxSize>
			<zIndex>25</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.2195 0.425" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<video name="videobox2" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}-right.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}-right.mp4</path>
			<audio>false</audio>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.54</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.51</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.67 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.622 0.530</pos>
			<maxSize>0.241</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.326</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.272</maxSize>
			<zIndex>27</zIndex>
			<rotation>0</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.342 0.530" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<video name="videobox3" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}-left.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${system.theme}-left.mp4</path>
			<audio>false</audio>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.8</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.6</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.3 0.5</origin>
			<pos>0.411 0.64</pos>
			<maxSize>0.144</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.195</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.162</maxSize>
			<zIndex>27</zIndex>
			<rotation>0</rotation>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.131 0.64" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2017</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Microsoft</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Xbox Game Pass</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Game Pass is a subscription service as part of Xbox and offered by Microsoft. Launched on June 1, 2017, the service allows users to download and play video games for Xbox video game consoles or Microsoft Windows PCs from a rotating library, with the games remaining accessible as long as the user has an active subscription. Game Pass subscribers also receive discounts on purchases of games from the service's library and their respective downloadable content (DLC).

The service consists of two products; Xbox Game Pass for Xbox One, Series X, and Series S consoles, and PC Game Pass for PCs running Windows 10 and Windows 11. Xbox Game Pass and PC Game Pass are available as separate subscription products. A premium tier known as Game Pass Ultimate includes access to both services, an on-demand cloud gaming service available on console, PC, and mobile platforms, and Xbox Live Gold subscription benefits.
The service features titles from Xbox Game Studios and other third-party publishers. Since January 2018, all new Xbox Game Studios titles have been available to Game Pass subscribers immediately upon their release. Microsoft has also offered access to Electronic Arts's EA Play service for PC Game Pass and Game Pass Ultimate subscribers.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Game Pass to usługa subskrypcji będąca częścią Xbox i oferowana przez Microsoft. Uruchomiona 1 czerwca 2017 roku usługa umożliwia użytkownikom pobieranie i granie w gry wideo na konsole Xbox lub komputery PC z systemem Microsoft Windows z rotacyjnej biblioteki, przy czym gry pozostają dostępne tak długo, jak użytkownik ma aktywną subskrypcję. Subskrybenci Game Pass otrzymują również zniżki na zakup gier z biblioteki usługi i ich odpowiedniej zawartości do pobrania (DLC).

Usługa składa się z dwóch produktów: Xbox Game Pass dla konsol Xbox One, Series X i Series S oraz PC Game Pass dla komputerów PC z systemem Windows 10 i Windows 11. Xbox Game Pass i PC Game Pass są dostępne jako oddzielne produkty subskrypcyjne. Warstwa premium znana jako Game Pass Ultimate obejmuje dostęp do obu usług, usługi gier w chmurze na żądanie dostępnej na konsolach, komputerach PC i platformach mobilnych oraz korzyści z subskrypcji Xbox Live Gold.
Usługa obejmuje tytuły od Xbox Game Studios i innych zewnętrznych wydawców. Od stycznia 2018 roku wszystkie nowe tytuły Xbox Game Studios są dostępne dla subskrybentów Game Pass natychmiast po ich wydaniu. Microsoft oferuje również dostęp do usługi EA Play firmy Electronic Arts dla subskrybentów PC Game Pass i Game Pass Ultimate.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Game Pass - это сервис подписки, входящий в состав Xbox и предлагаемый компанией Microsoft. Запущенный 1 июня 2017 г., сервис позволяет пользователям загружать и играть в видеоигры для игровых приставок Xbox или ПК под управлением Microsoft Windows из ротируемой библиотеки, при этом игры остаются доступными до тех пор, пока пользователь имеет активную подписку. Подписчики Game Pass также получают скидки на покупку игр из библиотеки сервиса и соответствующего загружаемого контента (DLC).

Сервис состоит из двух продуктов: Xbox Game Pass для консолей Xbox One, Series X и Series S и PC Game Pass для компьютеров под управлением Windows 10 и Windows 11. Xbox Game Pass и PC Game Pass доступны в виде отдельных продуктов по подписке. Премиальный уровень под названием Game Pass Ultimate включает в себя доступ к обоим сервисам, облачный игровой сервис по требованию, доступный на консолях, ПК и мобильных платформах, а также преимущества подписки Xbox Live Gold.
В сервисе представлены игры от Xbox Game Studios и других сторонних издателей. С января 2018 года все новые игры Xbox Game Studios становятся доступны подписчикам Game Pass сразу после выхода. Для подписчиков PC Game Pass и Game Pass Ultimate компания Microsoft также предоставила доступ к сервису EA Play от Electronic Arts.</text>
			<text lang="es">Game Pass es un servicio de suscripción que forma parte de Xbox y es ofrecido por Microsoft. Lanzado el 1 de junio de 2017, el servicio permite a los usuarios descargar y jugar a videojuegos para videoconsolas Xbox o PC con Microsoft Windows desde una biblioteca rotatoria, permaneciendo los juegos accesibles mientras el usuario tenga una suscripción activa. Los suscriptores de Game Pass también reciben descuentos en la compra de juegos de la biblioteca del servicio y sus respectivos contenidos descargables (DLC).

El servicio consta de dos productos: Xbox Game Pass para las consolas Xbox One, Series X y Series S, y PC Game Pass para PC con Windows 10 y Windows 11. Xbox Game Pass y PC Game Pass están disponibles como productos de suscripción independientes. Un nivel premium conocido como Game Pass Ultimate incluye acceso a ambos servicios, un servicio de juego en la nube bajo demanda disponible en consola, PC y plataformas móviles, y ventajas de suscripción a Xbox Live Gold.
El servicio incluye títulos de Xbox Game Studios y otros editores de terceros. Desde enero de 2018, todos los nuevos títulos de Xbox Game Studios están disponibles para los suscriptores de Game Pass inmediatamente después de su lanzamiento. Microsoft también ha ofrecido acceso al servicio EA Play de Electronic Arts para los suscriptores de PC Game Pass y Game Pass Ultimate.</text>
			<text lang="de">Game Pass - это сервис подписки, входящий в состав Xbox и предлагаемый компанией Microsoft. Запущенный 1 июня 2017 г., сервис позволяет пользователям загружать и играть в видеоигры для игровых приставок Xbox или ПК под управлением Microsoft Windows из ротируемой библиотеки, при этом игры остаются доступными до тех пор, пока пользователь имеет активную подписку. Подписчики Game Pass также получают скидки на покупку игр из библиотеки сервиса и соответствующего загружаемого контента (DLC).

Сервис состоит из двух продуктов: Xbox Game Pass для консолей Xbox One, Series X и Series S и PC Game Pass для компьютеров под управлением Windows 10 и Windows 11. Xbox Game Pass и PC Game Pass доступны в виде отдельных продуктов по подписке. Премиальный уровень под названием Game Pass Ultimate включает в себя доступ к обоим сервисам, облачный игровой сервис по требованию, доступный на консолях, ПК и мобильных платформах, а также преимущества подписки Xbox Live Gold.
В сервисе представлены игры от Xbox Game Studios и других сторонних издателей. С января 2018 года все новые игры Xbox Game Studios становятся доступны подписчикам Game Pass сразу после выхода. Для подписчиков PC Game Pass и Game Pass Ultimate компания Microsoft также предоставила доступ к сервису EA Play от Electronic Arts.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Game Pass est un service d'abonnement faisant partie de Xbox et proposé par Microsoft. Lancé le 1er juin 2017, le service permet aux utilisateurs de télécharger et de jouer à des jeux vidéo pour les consoles de jeux vidéo Xbox ou les PC Microsoft Windows à partir d'une bibliothèque tournante, les jeux restant accessibles tant que l'utilisateur a un abonnement actif. Les abonnés au Game Pass bénéficient également de réductions sur l'achat de jeux de la bibliothèque du service et de leur contenu téléchargeable (DLC) respectif.

Le service se compose de deux produits : Xbox Game Pass pour les consoles Xbox One, Series X et Series S, et PC Game Pass pour les PC fonctionnant sous Windows 10 et Windows 11. Xbox Game Pass et PC Game Pass sont disponibles sous forme d'abonnements distincts. Un niveau supérieur appelé Game Pass Ultimate comprend l'accès aux deux services, un service de jeu en nuage à la demande disponible sur les consoles, les PC et les plateformes mobiles, ainsi que les avantages de l'abonnement Xbox Live Gold.
Le service propose des titres de Xbox Game Studios et d'autres éditeurs tiers. Depuis janvier 2018, tous les nouveaux titres Xbox Game Studios sont disponibles pour les abonnés Game Pass dès leur sortie. Microsoft a également offert l'accès au service EA Play d'Electronic Arts aux abonnés PC Game Pass et Game Pass Ultimate.</text>
			<text lang="it">Game Pass è un servizio in abbonamento parte di Xbox e offerto da Microsoft. Lanciato il 1° giugno 2017, il servizio consente agli utenti di scaricare e giocare a videogiochi per console Xbox o PC Microsoft Windows da una libreria a rotazione; i giochi restano accessibili finché l'utente ha un abbonamento attivo. Gli abbonati a Game Pass ricevono inoltre sconti sull'acquisto di giochi dalla libreria del servizio e sui rispettivi contenuti scaricabili (DLC).

Il servizio si compone di due prodotti: Xbox Game Pass per le console Xbox One, Series X e Series S e PC Game Pass per i PC con Windows 10 e Windows 11. Xbox Game Pass e PC Game Pass sono disponibili come prodotti in abbonamento separati. Un livello premium, noto come Game Pass Ultimate, include l'accesso a entrambi i servizi, un servizio di cloud gaming on-demand disponibile su console, PC e piattaforme mobili e i vantaggi dell'abbonamento a Xbox Live Gold.
Il servizio offre titoli di Xbox Game Studios e di altri editori di terze parti. Da gennaio 2018, tutti i nuovi titoli di Xbox Game Studios sono disponibili per gli abbonati a Game Pass immediatamente dopo l'uscita. Microsoft ha anche offerto l'accesso al servizio EA Play di Electronic Arts agli abbonati a PC Game Pass e Game Pass Ultimate.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
