<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysart" extra="true">
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/fpinball.png</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/4K/fpinball.png</path>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video" extra="true">
			<color>000000</color>
			<path>./../../_inc/images/space43.png</path>
			<zIndex>2</zIndex>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.395</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.455</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.405</pos>
			<maxSize>0.245</maxSize>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.405" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox" extra="true">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/fpinball.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/fpinball.mp4</path>
			<path>./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/anim/video/${synonym}.mp4</path>
			<delay>0</delay>
			<effect>none</effect>
			<origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.5 0.395</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.5 0.455</origin>
			<pos>0.501 0.408</pos>
			<maxSize>0.23</maxSize>
			<zIndex>26</zIndex>
			<storyboard>
				<animation property="pos" to="0.221 0.408" begin="2000" duration="1000" mode="linear"/>
			</storyboard>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate" extra="true">
			<text>2016</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer" extra="true">
			<text>Zaccaria</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName" extra="true">
			<text>Pinball</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc" extra="true">
			<text>Zaccaria, (later briefly reorganized under Mr. Game before ending production) was an Italian company of pinball and arcade machines that existed in Bologna from 1974 until 1990. The factory was sold to tecnoplay.

The company was founded as a manufactory for pinball arcade games in Bologna by the three brothers Marino, Franco and Natale Zaccaria. The logo consists of their initials. Zaccaria was led by Marino Zaccaria, a former manager of a bar near Bologna.

At their best time, Zaccaria was the third largest company of pinball machines in the world after Bally and Williams. The company also entered into the video arcade game sector in the late 1970s. Therefore, they licensed games and developed some games with their own designs.

There are at least 47 different Zaccaria pinball machines known to exist although some are just variations of the same game.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Zaccaria, (później na krótko zreorganizowana pod nazwą Mr. Game przed zakończeniem produkcji) była włoską firmą produkującą pinballe i automaty arcade, która istniała w Bolonii od 1974 do 1990 roku. Fabryka została sprzedana firmie tecnoplay.

Firma została założona jako manufaktura gier zręcznościowych pinball w Bolonii przez trzech braci Marino, Franco i Natale Zaccaria. Logo składa się z ich inicjałów. Zaccaria była prowadzona przez Marino Zaccaria, byłego kierownika baru w pobliżu Bolonii.

W najlepszym okresie Zaccaria była trzecią co do wielkości firmą produkującą automaty do pinballa na świecie po Bally i Williamsie. Firma weszła również w sektor gier zręcznościowych pod koniec lat 70-tych. W związku z tym licencjonowała gry i opracowała kilka gier według własnych projektów.

Znanych jest co najmniej 47 różnych automatów do pinballa Zaccaria, choć niektóre z nich to tylko wariacje tej samej gry.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Zaccaria (позже реорганизованная в Mr. Game, а затем прекратившая производство) - итальянская компания по производству пинбольных и аркадных автоматов, существовавшая в Болонье с 1974 по 1990 год. Завод был продан компании tecnoplay.

Компания была основана как производство аркадных игр для пинбола в Болонье тремя братьями Марино, Франко и Натале Заккариа. Логотип состоит из их инициалов. Компанию Zaccaria возглавил Марино Заккария, бывший менеджер бара в окрестностях Болоньи.

В свои лучшие времена Zaccaria была третьей по величине компанией по производству пинбольных автоматов в мире после Bally и Williams. В конце 1970-х годов компания также вошла в сектор видеоаркадных игр. Поэтому они лицензировали игры и разрабатывали некоторые игры по собственным проектам.

Известно по меньшей мере 47 различных пинбольных автоматов Zaccaria, хотя некоторые из них являются лишь разновидностями одной и той же игры.</text>
			<text lang="es">Zaccaria, (más tarde reorganizada brevemente bajo Mr. Game antes de poner fin a la producción) fue una empresa italiana de pinball y máquinas recreativas que existió en Bolonia desde 1974 hasta 1990. La fábrica fue vendida a tecnoplay.

La empresa fue fundada en Bolonia por los hermanos Marino, Franco y Natale Zaccaria. El logotipo está formado por sus iniciales. Zaccaria estaba dirigida por Marino Zaccaria, antiguo gerente de un bar cercano a Bolonia.

En su mejor momento, Zaccaria fue la tercera empresa de pinballs del mundo, por detrás de Bally y Williams. La empresa también se introdujo en el sector de los videojuegos arcade a finales de la década de 1970. Para ello, licenciaron juegos y desarrollaron algunos con diseños propios.

Se tiene constancia de la existencia de al menos 47 pinballs Zaccaria diferentes, aunque algunos no son más que variaciones del mismo juego.</text>
			<text lang="de">Zaccaria (später kurzzeitig in Mr. Game umbenannt, bevor die Produktion eingestellt wurde) war ein italienisches Unternehmen für Flipper- und Spielhallenautomaten, das von 1974 bis 1990 in Bologna ansässig war. Die Fabrik wurde an tecnoplay verkauft.

Das Unternehmen wurde von den drei Brüdern Marino, Franco und Natale Zaccaria als Manufaktur für Flipper- und Arcade-Spiele in Bologna gegründet. Das Logo besteht aus ihren Initialen. Geführt wurde Zaccaria von Marino Zaccaria, einem ehemaligen Manager einer Bar in der Nähe von Bologna.

In der Blütezeit war Zaccaria nach Bally und Williams das drittgrößte Unternehmen für Flipperautomaten in der Welt. In den späten 1970er Jahren stieg das Unternehmen auch in den Sektor der Video-Arcade-Spiele ein. Dazu lizenzierte es Spiele und entwickelte einige Spiele mit eigenen Designs.

Es sind mindestens 47 verschiedene Zaccaria-Flipper bekannt, wobei es sich bei einigen nur um Varianten desselben Spiels handelt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Zaccaria, (plus tard brièvement réorganisée sous le nom de Mr. Game avant d'arrêter la production) était une société italienne de flippers et de machines d'arcade qui a existé à Bologne de 1974 à 1990. L'usine a été vendue à tecnoplay.

La société a été fondée à Bologne par les trois frères Marino, Franco et Natale Zaccaria en tant que fabricant de flippers et de jeux d'arcade. Le logo est constitué de leurs initiales. Zaccaria était dirigé par Marino Zaccaria, ancien gérant d'un bar près de Bologne.

À son apogée, Zaccaria était la troisième plus grande entreprise de flippers au monde, après Bally et Williams. La société s'est également lancée dans le secteur des jeux d'arcade vidéo à la fin des années 1970. C'est ainsi qu'elle a acquis des licences pour des jeux et en a développé certains avec ses propres conceptions.

Il existe au moins 47 flippers Zaccaria différents, bien que certains ne soient que des variantes d'un même jeu.</text>
			<text lang="it">Zaccaria, (poi brevemente riorganizzata sotto il nome di Mr. Game prima di terminare la produzione) è stata un'azienda italiana di flipper e arcade che è esistita a Bologna dal 1974 al 1990. La fabbrica è stata venduta a tecnoplay.

L'azienda è stata fondata come fabbrica di flipper arcade a Bologna dai tre fratelli Marino, Franco e Natale Zaccaria. Il logo è costituito dalle loro iniziali. Zaccaria era guidata da Marino Zaccaria, ex gestore di un bar nei pressi di Bologna.

Nel momento migliore, Zaccaria era la terza azienda di flipper al mondo dopo Bally e Williams. Alla fine degli anni '70 l'azienda entrò anche nel settore dei videogiochi arcade. Per questo motivo, ha concesso licenze per i giochi e ne ha sviluppati alcuni con progetti propri.

Si conosce l'esistenza di almeno 47 flipper Zaccaria diversi, anche se alcuni sono solo varianti dello stesso gioco.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Zaccaria, (mais tarde brevemente reorganizada como Mr. Game antes de encerrar a produção) foi uma empresa italiana fabricante de fliperamas e jogos de arcade que existiu em Bolonha de 1974 a 1990. A fábrica foi vendida para a tecnoplay.

A empresa foi fundada como uma manufatura de fliperamas em Bolonha por três irmãos, Marino, Franco e Natale Zaccaria. O logotipo é composto por suas iniciais. A Zaccaria era dirigida por Marino Zaccaria, ex-gerente de um bar perto de Bolonha.

Em seu auge, a Zaccaria foi a terceira maior empresa de fliperama do mundo, atrás apenas da Bally e da Williams. A empresa também entrou no setor de jogos de arcade no final da década de 1970. Para isso, licenciou jogos e desenvolveu vários jogos de acordo com seus próprios projetos.

São conhecidos pelo menos 47 fliperamas Zaccaria diferentes, embora alguns sejam apenas variações do mesmo jogo.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
