<theme>
   <formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
   <include>./../theme.xml</include>
 	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1">
			<text>Manufacturer : Ludvig Strigeus</text>
			<text lang="pl">Producent : Ludvig Strigeus</text>
			<text lang="fr">Constructeur : Ludvig Strigeus</text>
			<text lang="de">Hersteller : Ludvig Strigeus</text>
			<text lang="ru">Производитель : Ludvig Strigeus</text>
			<pos>0.03 0.76</pos>
		</text>
		<text name="info2">
			<text>Year of Release : 2001</text>
			<text lang="pl">Rok wydania : 2001</text>
			<text lang="fr">Année de sortie : 2001</text>
			<text lang="de">Jahr der Veröffentlichung : 2001</text>
			<text lang="ru">Год выпуска : 2001</text>
			<pos>0.03 0.78</pos>
		</text>
		<text name="info3">
			<text></text>
			<text>Scummvm is a collection of game engine recreations. Originally designed to play LucasArts adventure games that use the SCUMMM system, it also supports a variety of non-SCUMM games by companies like Revolution Software and Adventure Soft. It was originally written by Ludvig Strigeus. Released under the terms of the GNU General Public License, ScummVM is a free software.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Scummvm to zbiór silników gier. Pierwotnie zaprojektowany do grania w gry przygodowe LucasArts, które używają systemu SCUMMM, obsługuje także różne gry inne niż SCUMM takich firm jak Revolution Software i Adventure Soft. Pierwotnie napisał ją Ludvig Strigeus. Wydany na zasadach GNU General Public Licence, ScummVM jest darmowym oprogramowaniem.</text>
			<text lang="fr"> </text>
			<text lang="de"> </text>
			<text lang="ru">Самый популярный и эффективный эмулятор классических приключений, позволяет насладиться магией 90-х годов. Приложение само по себе не является игрой, но позволяет всем играть в такие старые игры, как Broken Sword, Monkey Island, Indiana Jones and Atlantis, Flight of the Amazon Queen и The Day Tentacle, а также многие другие.</text>
			<pos>0.03 0.76</pos>
			<size>0.40 0.20</size>
			<lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
